All right.
好的。
Hello. Hello.
你好。 你好。
Hi, guys.
嗨，大家好。
Good morning.
早上好。
And this is a little stuffy today, so you might hear that a bit.
今天有点闷，所以你可能会听到一点。
Sorry about that.
对于那个很抱歉。
Good morning, everybody. How's it going?
大家早上好。 怎么样了？
What's up?
怎么了？
I just had today Hmm.
我今天刚吃过嗯。
Because I'm ready to cook, and, you know, so's my.
因为我已经准备好做饭了，而且，你知道，我的也是。
So is my little friend down here.
我的小朋友也在下面。
Hold on. You want to say hi?
坚持，稍等。 你想打个招呼吗？
I say hi.
我打声招呼。
Hmm. I'll think he knows why I put him under your desk this time.
唔。 我想他知道我这次为什么把他放在你的桌子底下。
What is he doing under the desk?
他在桌子底下做什么？
You don't have to know.
你不必知道。
Got a substitute?
有替身吗？
I only did that because he.
我这样做只是因为他。
Told me before we got word.
在我们得到消息之前告诉我。
Forgot your dream started out.
忘记你的梦想开始了。
Last time we collabs, he did the same shit to me.
上次我们合作时，他对我做了同样的事情。
And he shoved me under the fucking desk.
他把我推到他妈的桌子下面。
Like, what was that? Wow. So I just like it.
比如，那是什么？ 哇。 所以我只是喜欢它。
My way of getting some sweet little revenge.
我得到一些甜蜜的小报复的方式。
That's all that
仅此而已
Yeah, he just.
是的，他只是。
He just spoke and said, look it
他只是说话并说，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上，向上。
I'll take even those. Look at him.
我什至会接受那些。 看着他。
Look at his looking so silly. OK,
看他这么傻的样子。 好的，
I'm talking to his shot right now, too. OK.
我现在也在谈论他的投篮。 好的。
But yeah.
但是，是的。
So today we're just going to be playing some some overcooked.
所以今天我们只是要玩一些煮过头的东西。
This is the first time I've ever played overcooked.
这是我第一次玩过头。
I've never played this game before.
我以前从未玩过这个游戏。
It's going to be.
它将会成为。
It's going to be something.
这将是一些事情。
I heard. It's stressful.
我听说。 压力很大。
I heard this game is pretty stressful, and it can be kind of hard
听说这个游戏压力很大，可能有点难
I mean, I don't think that's the only thing that's going to be hard today.
我的意思是，我不认为这是今天唯一困难的事情。
But don't
但是不要等到厨师长，好吗？
I mean, I'm the chef. What am I talking about?
我的意思是，我是厨师。 我在说什么？
I'm the chef. Yeah,
我是厨师。 是的，
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Also, I'm going to be taking a lot of sips of my tea because.
另外，我要喝很多茶，因为。
Oh, my goodness, my throat is really feeling that today.
哦，天哪，我的喉咙今天真的有这种感觉。
So all.
所以所有。
Yeah, I don't know what to expect.
是的，我不知道会发生什么。
Vox wants a collab, something I was sud sure.
Vox 想要合作，我很确定。
We said overcooked.
我们说煮过头了。
And I mean, I don't know what's going to happen, but so I'm excited
我的意思是，我不知道会发生什么，但我很高兴能在厨房里乱搞，度过那些可笑的时光。
It's fucking raw.
真他妈生吃。
Just pop out of nowhere, so. OK, hold on.
只是突然冒出来，所以。 好的，稍等。
I think I can switch over the screen.
我想我可以切换屏幕。
Also, good morning, everybody. Good morning.
还有，大家早上好。 早上好。
Good evening. I'm
晚上好。 我是
sorry about that.
对于那个很抱歉。
Oh, I only fixed that.
哦，我只是解决了这个问题。
I forget what I make myself. Beer. You're just like our.
我忘记了我自己做了什么。 啤酒。 你和我们一样。
We're just everything, so. OK, I'm good to go now.
我们就是一切，所以。 好的，我现在可以走了。
I'm giggles CFR boxes. Ready? OK,
我在咯咯笑 CFR 盒子。 准备好？ 好的，
yeah.
是的。
I hope you're having a good evening, everybody, and thank you for coming by.
希望大家晚上过得愉快，谢谢大家的光临。
All right.
好的。
Why you do that?
你为什么这么做？
Hello? Hello.
你好？ 你好。
Why did you just increase in size?
为什么你只是增加尺寸？
Very small. Oh, the fuck out of it.
很小。 哦，他妈的。
You were kaiju.
你是怪兽。
No, no. OK, so there's a thing.
不，不。 好的，所以有一件事。
There's a thing.
有一件事。
I press a button, and it makes my face super big.
我按下一个按钮，它让我的脸变得超级大。
It's like I'm coming to give you a big kiss on the face, you know?
就像我要来给你一个大大的吻一样，你知道吗？
And then.
进而。
And then I had to return it, but then I realised it was.
然后我不得不退回它，但后来我意识到它是。
Oh, shit. Advocacy that I hope he didn't like.
妈的。 我希望他不喜欢的宣传。
I did I was just talking with my child.
我做到了，我只是在和我的孩子说话。
I was like, ooh, I wonder when he's going to one.
我当时想，哦，我想知道他什么时候去。
You wonder when we're going to get to chat.
你想知道我们什么时候可以聊天。
I wonder when we're going to get to stop the game.
我想知道我们什么时候才能停止比赛。
And then you went like, Hello? Hello.
然后你说，你好？ 你好。
And then straight towards the screen I was scared.
然后直奔屏幕，我被吓到了。
I was fucking terrified. Oh, I'm so sorry.
我他妈吓坏了。 哦，我很抱歉。
Now it's all right, everyone say hi. Shoot.
现在没事了，大家打个招呼。 射击。
I shot the way. That's me.
我拍的路。 那是我。
I fuck you.
我操你。
So cute.
太可爱了。
I look.
我看。
I woke up, like, an hour ago, all right. OK?
我醒了，就像，一个小时前，好吧。 好的？
And I can't really blame you for that.
我真的不能为此责怪你。
We on. We're on different time zones.
我们上。 我们在不同的时区。
He's he's.
他是他的。
He's coping with a lot of a lot of shit.
他正在应付很多很多狗屎。
I woke. I woke up a while ago.
我醒了。 我前一阵子醒了。
I did. And then.
我做到了。 进而。
Yeah, you got early sleep, didn't you?
是啊，你早睡了，不是吗？
Like, I got very.
就像，我得到了很多。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
You are big, man. Look.
你很大，伙计。 看。
Yeah, look at me. Healthy man, right?
是的，看着我。 健康的人，对吧？
Very healthy, man.
非常健康，伙计。
So you you've touched this game before.
所以你之前接触过这个游戏。
I haven't such a question. About one yeah.
我没有这样的问题。 大约一个是的。
You're going to be like my my mentor or like, was it going to be the
你会像我的导师一样，会不会是
the Gordon Fiori?
戈登费奥里？
I'll be my baby.
我会是我的宝贝。
Baby Xbox Ramsay, you'll be my apprentice.
宝贝 Xbox Ramsay，你将成为我的学徒。
And together, we'll make it through this chef themed adventure.
我们将一起完成这个以厨师为主题的冒险。
OK, so you have to invite me, so.
好的，所以你必须邀请我，所以。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Yeah, grab me, grab me from.
是的，抓住我，抓住我。
They go.
他们去。
You invite me where I did.
你邀请我去哪里。
Although there's storm.
虽然有风雨。
Oh, you did all right.
哦，你做得很好。
Oh, so you did.
哦，你做到了。
So you did.
所以你做到了。
OK. Am I in you are.
好的。 我在你里面吗。
Pug. Oh, you are.
帕格。 哦，你是。
Hey, let's go.
嘿，我们走吧。
Look, he's the puppy. The world.
看，他是小狗。 世界。
The dog is pretty damn cute.
这只狗实在是太可爱了。
And he is really cute.
而且他真的很可爱。
I like the smile on the turtle.
我喜欢乌龟的笑容。
They didn't have a monkey, so I went for the turtle.
他们没有猴子，所以我去找乌龟。
Or they don't have a monkey boy.
或者他们没有猴童。
They don't have a monkey.
他们没有猴子。
No, they don't have a monkey, huh?
不，他们没有猴子，对吧？
All right.
好的。
OK, now what else do they have?
好的，现在他们还有什么？
They have, like, weird looking people till.
他们有，就像，奇怪的人直到。
They've got some human beings and they've got bunch of animals.
他们有一些人，他们有一群动物。
Oh, I like that dog.
哦，我喜欢那条狗。
Yeah, there's a kitten oh.
是的，有一只小猫哦。
Is a grandma is a right mouse.
是奶奶是鼠标右键。
Panda pirate lady pirate man.
熊猫海盗女士海盗男人。
What?
什么？
They all look at that shark fuck is that.
他们都看着那个鲨鱼他妈的就是那个。
Oh, that's a shark.
哦，那是一条鲨鱼。
How do you know these animals so well?
你怎么这么了解这些动物？
Sharks are not difficult. To. Recognise me.
鲨鱼并不难。 到。 认出我。
That's a shark. I thought that was like a lizard.
那是一条鲨鱼。 我还以为是蜥蜴呢。
Yeah, I was like, oh, my God, that's.
是的，我当时想，哦，天哪，就是这样。
That's a chameleon.
那是变色龙。
Look at the fucking fin on the back. You dig?
看后面那该死的鳍。 你挖？
Oh, there's a oh, yeah, there is a fin.
哦，有一个哦，是的，有一个鳍。
OK, well, you know, improving your point. Good, good on you.
好吧，好吧，你知道，改进你的观点。 好，看好你。
You know, your animals. On the back. Did all right?
你知道，你的动物。 在后面。 没事吧？
I struggle in the garden.
我在花园里挣扎。
I'm attached to the turtle now.
我现在依附于乌龟。
All right, story.
好吧，故事。
All right, chef.
好的，厨师。
Game.
游戏。
Where are we going?
我们去哪？
We're playing the story.
我们正在播放故事。
Yes. OK, this play the story mapped
是的。  OK，本剧剧情映射
out. OK, pick paint tutorial.
出去。 好的，选择油漆教程。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Yes, yes, yes.
对对对。
So pay attention.
所以要注意。
So essentially the way it works is we go to work together to make dishes.
所以基本上它的工作方式是我们一起做菜。
Mm hmm. Hmm, hmm.
嗯嗯。 嗯，嗯。
The following is based on actual events only the names, places and vegetables
以下是根据实际发生的事件，只是名称、地点和蔬菜有所改变。
Thanks enough
非常感谢
just off the tee time.
刚刚开球时间。
Oh, what the fuck?
哦，什么鬼？
Who's this guy.
他是谁。
You. Are?
你。 是？
Is that a cookie long?
那个饼干长吗？
OK, that's a fucking onion, you dickhead.
好吧，那是一个他妈的洋葱，你这个白痴。
I thought, OK, I was going to say coconut next.
我想，好吧，接下来我要说椰子了。
How is. How the fuck am I supposed to know it's an onion?
怎么。 我他妈怎么知道是洋葱？
That's how you.
你就是这样。
Caramelised the cookie.
将饼干焦糖化。
It's an onion. You take an. Onion.
这是一个洋葱。 你拿一个。 洋葱。
Look at it. Covered look. The fabled.
看它。 覆盖的样子。 传说中的。
No, I'm not America on
不，我不是美国
blue.
蓝色的。
Oh, oh, I can do that. OK.
哦，哦，我可以做到。 好的。
He literally leapt at the chance and everything was super.
他真的抓住了这个机会，一切都很棒。
He literally the. One.
他从字面上。 一。
This is one.
这是一。
Line. OK, I need a one line.
线。 好的，我需要一条线。
Is. What. I'm.
是。 什么。 我是。
What do you mean it's dangerous?
你说它很危险是什么意思？
Don't be silly.
别傻了。
This book holds the secret to everlasting culinary greatness in a large bowl.
这本书在一个大碗中掌握了永恒烹饪的秘诀。
Dissolve the sugar.
溶解糖。
In warm water, then stir in. Yeast.
在温水中，然后搅拌。酵母。
You will go down to.
你会去。
Proof until yeast resembles a rich.
直到酵母类似于丰富的证明。
Creamy foam.
奶油泡沫。
Foam. Apple
泡沫。 苹果从那一刻起真是一段疯狂的时光。
Who makes it sold an.
谁让它卖了。
Oil and mixes the flour
油和混合面粉
in the dough covered with a damp cloth.
在用湿布覆盖的面团中。
Well, this is just the recipe for making bread
好吧，这只是制作面包的秘诀，并且允许这样做。
Right?
对？
You see that right back there?
你在后面看到了吗？
Oh, it's night of the living bread.
哦，这是生活面包的夜晚。
That's the.
那就是。
Dough fucking cheese.
面团他妈的奶酪。
Rise, rise up, huh?
起来，起来，嗯？
Yeah.
是的。
No, no, no.
不不不。
This wasn't supposed to happen.
这是不应该发生的。
It can't be. It's
不可能。 它是
beyond bread.
超越面包。
We're resorting to food puns already.
我们已经在诉诸食物双关语了。
I mean,
我是说，
look, this is a cooking.
看，这是一道菜。
It is a cooking game.
这是一个烹饪游戏。
You know, it is like it is a game. Where is it going to be?
你知道，这就像一个游戏。 它会在哪里？
You could use my best chefs or could be the ones that happened to be here.
您可以使用我最好的厨师，也可以是碰巧在这里的厨师。
See if you could.
看看你能不能。
Find them all. Well, they seem hungry.
全部找到。 好吧，他们似乎饿了。
So we got to feed them.
所以我们必须喂它们。
I got to feed them.
我得喂它们。
I got to fuck me. Wait.
我得操我。 等待。
All right.
好的。
Grab you. Want to shop inside, grab the lettuce.
抓住你。 想在里面购物，抢生菜。
I can't throw the lettuce.
我不能扔生菜。
As a space to grab.
作为抢占空间。
And now I've got to put it over here
现在我必须把它放在这里，这样我就无法访问你的东西了，对吧？
I can't.
我不能。
I can't move the lettuce yeah.
我不能移动生菜是的。
Because you're on the other side.
因为你在另一边。
Oh, I'm the dog.
哦，我是狗。
I'm the dog. You've got something here for you.
我是狗。 你有东西给你。
I'll grab the lettuce and I'll take it to the chopping board.
我会抓住生菜，然后把它带到砧板上。
I'll space.
我会空间。
OK. I'll take you to the chopping board and space again,
好的。 我再带你去砧板和空间，然后剁好。
You have to figure out what the button is and to maybe chop.
你必须弄清楚按钮是什么，并且可能会砍掉。
E, e e e.
E，e e e。
OK, what now?
好的，现在呢？
E e chop.
E 印章。
What's answer?
什么是答案？
I'm pressing answer.
我正在按答案。
Yes. I shut the lettuce I'm chopping.
是的。 我关上了正在切的生菜。
I don't like about this.
我不喜欢这个。
I played on my switch the last time I played this.
上次玩这个的时候我在switch上玩过。
I can. Oh, all, all.
我可以。 哦，所有，所有。
No, that's not it.
不，不是这样。
Hold on. Wait,
坚持，稍等。 等待，
I'm pressing every button on my keyboard.
我正在按下键盘上的每个按钮。
By the way.
顺便一提。
Um, are very professional, as you can tell.
嗯，很专业，如你所见。
I can't chop lettuce.
我不能切生菜。
How much? I like gestures.
多少？ 我喜欢手势。
Yeah, ease the gestures I can.
是的，尽量放宽手势。
Trying to figure it out.
试图弄清楚。
G g no, no.
G g 不，不。
P answer control no mouse control.
P 应答控制 无鼠标控制。
It's control.
是控制。
All right, now you've got to get the chop. Let's put it on my side.
好吧，现在你必须得到印章。 让我们把它放在我身边。
Mm hmm. Hmm, hmm. How?
嗯嗯。 嗯，嗯。 如何？
Oh, just. Just down.
哦，只是。 就下来了。
Yep. Yeah, yeah. Good.
是的。 是啊是啊。 好的。
You put that down, then we've got to play a
你把它记下来，然后我们必须玩一个
and I put that on the thing, and we've got it.
我把它放在那个东西上，我们得到了它。
All right. Oh, that's it.
好的。 哦，就是这样。
Why did I just want to kind of let us talk.
为什么我只是想让我们谈谈。
OK, now you got to do with the chop.
好的，现在你要处理印章了。
I'm going to chop. Oh, my God. You're giving me two ingredients at once.
我要砍了。 我的天啊。 你一次给我两种原料。
What is this?
这是什么？
Yeah, and remember, uh, remember.
是的，记住，嗯，记住。
Remember that you are also times like in the real game.
请记住，您在真正的游戏中也是如此。
Everything that happens were timed. Yeah.
发生的一切都是定时的。 是的。
All you have to do is you have to do, like, a lot of dishes
你所要做的就是你必须在短时间内做很多菜。 你个混蛋。
You motherfucker.
你个混蛋。
Hold on a week.
坚持一周。
You can give me a snack to give me something.
你可以给我点心给我点东西。
Something with some cucumber.
一些黄瓜的东西。
Do, do, do. Take my cucumber.
做，做，做。 拿走我的黄瓜。
Where's your cucumber? Try him. Try.
你的黄瓜在哪里？ 试试他。 尝试。
Take, take, take my massive green fucking cucumber.
拿，拿，拿我的大绿色他妈的黄瓜。
Oh, damn.
哦，该死的。
It's chocolate. You take the time.
它是巧克力。 你慢慢来。
I'll fucking
我会他妈的
lie in the brain.
躺在大脑里。
You take a wave.
你来一波。
I didn't know you. Could take out of the bag.
我不认识你。 可以从包里拿出来。
I. I can't take out of the bean.
I. 我拿不出来豆子。
I got to get you another fucking cucumber.
我得再给你弄个该死的黄瓜。
You know, I didn't know that was a bean.
你知道，我不知道那是一颗豆子。
Told me a fucking cucumber.
告诉我一个他妈的黄瓜。
Hold on, hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up over at the shop.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持到商店。
The, the the the the tomato.
番茄。
That's the tomato.
那就是番茄。
That's the that's the middle.
那就是中间。
That's the
那就是
way you started.
你开始的方式。
That is I just get the lettuce.
那就是我刚得到生菜。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
I literally just gave you a letter.
我真的只是给了你一封信。
Said you and Callie, who were just.
你和凯莉说，他们是正义的。
Like it was out.
好像出来了一样。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I oh, I can't.
我哦，我不能。
I forgot.
我忘了。
I forgot how to chop only shit no more.
我忘了怎么只砍狗屎了。
I wonder why there's so many more orders now. What's happening?
我想知道为什么现在有这么多订单。 怎么了？
Because they're fucking hungry, you dickhead.
因为他们他妈的饿了，你这个白痴。
Why is it still coming?
为什么还是来了？
Holy fucking home, James.
神圣的家，詹姆斯。
Chill. Chill for one second.
寒意。 冷却一秒钟。
The UN bread aside.
联合国的面包放在一边。
Why are you not helping?
你为什么不帮忙？
Where's your chicken?
你的鸡在哪里？
She's actually God damn on this side.
在这一边，她实际上是该死的。
Kill shit you do.
杀了你做的事。
Why am I doing all the chopping for all my God chopping.
为什么我要为我所有的上帝砍伐而砍伐。
Bones are on your side, you fucking idiot.
骨头都在你身边，你这个白痴。
Well, now.
现在好了。
OK, ok, ok. You got.
好好好。 你得到了。
Let us go now. Roger.
现在让我们走吧。 罗杰。
I need another lettuce.
我需要另一个生菜。
I need another fucking lettuce. Always always.
我需要另一个该死的生菜。 永远永远。
Always. There's four orders. Why is there. For orders for.
总是。 有四个命令。 为什么会有。 对于订单。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We were seconds.
我们是秒。
You do were down there, right?
你确实在下面，对吧？
There's 30 seconds.
还有30秒。
Why are there 30 seconds?
为什么有 30 秒？
I didn't know we were being times already.
我不知道我们已经是时代了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I can help.
我能帮上忙。
Holy shit.
天啊。
We got teamwork.
我们得到了团队合作。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Tomato, we can get laid up.
番茄，我们可以躺着了。
Give me the tomato.
把番茄给我。
Yeah. Where you young about the tomato.
是的。 你对番茄年轻的地方。
Oh my God.
我的天啊。
How you got now you put down the tomato on the same table.
你现在是怎么得到的，你把番茄放在同一张桌子上。
Put on the table.
放在桌子上。
That is now.
就是现在。
You there's no way.
你没有办法。
There's no way.
不可能。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Box of logs, monster.
我的天啊。 一盒原木，怪物。
There's so many orders. There's so many orders.
有这么多订单。 有这么多订单。
Holy shit. We did it.
天啊。 我们做到了。
Yeah, I mean, we did eventually.
是的，我的意思是，我们最终做到了。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Oh, so ravenous.
哦，好贪吃。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Oh. Don't be a hero.
哦。 不要成为英雄。
Coming right back to the castle retreat.
马上回到城堡撤退。
My heart rate's high.
我的心率很高。
My dude, dude, my.
我的伙计，伙计，我的。
My blood pressure spikes during that.
在那期间我的血压飙升。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I was really. I was really enjoying being you.
我真的。 我真的很享受成为你。
That was the fucking tutorial.
那是他妈的教程。
Excuse me. What the fuck?
打扰一下。 什么鬼？
No, it may be my best traps, but you have.
不，这可能是我最好的陷阱，但你有。
Much to. Learn if you're to conquer that appetite.
多到。 了解您是否要征服这种胃口。
Man. Kevin, to keep those fiends from entering the castle.
男人。 凯文，防止那些恶魔进入城堡。
But now, if the unbridled spread from the castle grounds,
但是现在，如果肆无忌惮地从城内蔓延开来，
I fear for the onion kingdom, we must act quickly.
我担心洋葱王国，我们必须迅速行动。
Fuck me by oh.
操我哦。
As my boy. Kerrigan.
作为我的孩子。 凯瑞甘。
Why, of course. The Royal Stagecoach.
为什么，当然。 皇家驿马车。
She's just been. Upgraded. The royal sage.
她只是。 升级。 皇家圣人。
Oh, it seems.
哦，好像。
What's a guy that's up to you, Chef? To save our kingdom? Monaco Coupe.
什么是你的人，厨师？ 拯救我们的王国？ 摩纳哥跑车。
I guess it was a rough take. My wheels hit the road.
我想这是一个粗略的看法。 我的车轮撞上了马路。
Learn some new recipes for the love of onions.
学习一些新的洋葱食谱。
Learn to. Collaborate.
学会。 合作。
We spent three streams learning how to collaborate.
我们花了三个时间学习如何协作。
You can't see shit, you fucking caramelised.
你看不到狗屎，你他妈的焦糖。
I love this. This guy kind of reminds me of Dr.
我喜欢这个。 这个人让我想起了博士。
Hakim. He's got a moustache. He's got. A moustache.
哈基姆。 他留着小胡子。 他得到了。 小胡子。
Oh, we. Can walk.
哦，我们。 可以走路。
How do I slap you?
我怎么打你？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Get the fuck back here. Also, I know there's a button for Sprint.
他妈的回到这里。 另外，我知道有一个 Sprint 按钮。
I'm just trying to figure out what it is, because in the in the.
我只是想弄清楚它是什么，因为在里面。
It's like a dash.
它就像一个破折号。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Look, it's adorable.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。 看，很可爱。
I didn't see the.
我没看到。
Dog evil in front of the dog.
狗恶在狗面前。
The dog is like was.
这条狗就像以前一样。
He can't even talk to you.
他甚至不能和你说话。
What are you. Waiting?
你是做什么的。 等待？
Waiting for? Go I'm good.
等待？ 去吧，我很好。
Eat your moustache.
吃掉你的胡子。
My controller actually means be easy with the controller.
我的控制器实际上意味着使用控制器很容易。
I think control is a weird oops.
我认为控制是一个奇怪的哎呀。
All was that you? It was me.
都是你吗？ 那是我。
My, my, my, my, my, my, my, my.
我的，我的，我的，我的，我的，我的，我的，我的。
Our control is not working.
我们的控制不起作用。
My collaboration.
我的合作。
Collaboration. Oh, my, my, my, my.
合作。 哦，我的，我的，我的，我的。
I it's been doing that recently. We
我最近一直在这样做。 我们
someone said that you orgasm.
有人说你高潮了。
Oh, gosh, help out.
哦，天哪，救命啊。
Is that she fucking kidding insults.
她他妈是在开玩笑侮辱吗？
OK, yeah.
好的，是的。
So I guess control alt space and then the arrow keys.
所以我猜想先控制 alt 空格，然后再控制方向键。
Oh, are we driving?
哦，我们在开车吗？
No, you're. Driving. You and me, we're not.
不，你是。 驾驶。 你和我，我们不是。
We're on camper van.
我们在露营车上。
Oh. Yeah?
哦。 是的？
Yeah. You're the one at the wheel.
是的。 你是那个在方向盘上的人。
You ran over a civilian, you fucking swat over the umbrella.
你跑到一个平民身上，你他妈的扑倒了雨伞。
We're doing our job. I got you.
我们正在做我们的工作。 我接到你了。
See what you did for what I do.
看看你为我做了什么。
They didn't do anything they're customers.
他们没有做任何他们是客户的事情。
You know, there are customers at a point signs. I'm ready to
你知道，有客户在一个点的迹象。 我准备好了
be ready on the customers.
为客户做好准备。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This man, we're going to lose our business.
这个人，我们将失去我们的生意。
Well, it's only like. Well, it's not about business.
好吧，它只是喜欢。 好吧，这与商业无关。
It's about defending the kingdom. Oh, shit. It's our business.
这是关于保卫王国的。 妈的。 这是我们的事。
All right. World.
好的。 世界。
One dash, one fucking mushroom kingdom. Here we go.
一个冲刺，一个他妈的蘑菇王国。 开始了。
Mushroom kingdom.
蘑菇王国。
OK, get me in there.
好的，让我进去。
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
All right. Sashimi.
好的。 生鱼片。
So you get the fish, you chop it.
所以你得到鱼，你砍它。
All right, so you fish, and you need shrimp,
好吧，所以你钓鱼，你需要虾，然后你把它切碎，然后你做生鱼片。
OK, that's not too bad.
好吧，这还不错。
All Look, we're actually. Together now.
看，我们实际上是。 现在在一起。
All right?
好的？
So now. All right, but but.
所以现在。 好吧，但是但是。
Boy, where's where's the.
男孩，哪里是哪里。
Shrimp?
虾？
I I'm trying, but.
我正在尝试，但是。
OK, but I do have the shrimp.
好的，但我确实有虾。
I said the shrimp are on your side.
我说虾在你这边。
OK. You got to put the shrimp on.
好的。 你必须把虾放在上面。
Chop them up, huh?
把它们剁碎吧？
What will happen?
会发生什么？
I put the shrimp out, but.
我把虾拿出来了，但是。
You did it. You did it. You gave him a meal.
你做到了。 你做到了。 你给了他一顿饭。
I gave him meal.
我给他吃饭。
Well, no, I gave him a plate.
嗯，不，我给了他一个盘子。
Huh? I said there's some that is just shrimp.
嗯？ 我说有些只是虾。
They just want raw shrimp.
他们只想要生虾。
Who wants raw shrimp?
谁要生虾？
Hold up I don't know if I can enjoy it.
顶一下，不知道能不能享受。
Give me a how do I put it down on the plate?
给我一个如何把它放在盘子里？
You remember.
你记得。
You got to hit space.
你必须打太空。
You got to hit space over the plate.
你必须在盘子上打空间。
We had to chop it first, like, God. Yes.
我们必须先砍它，就像，上帝。 是的。
Fucking chop the shrimp, you dumb arse.
他妈的切虾，你这个笨蛋。
OK, now.
现在没事了。
All right, so we need we need something to you,
好吧，所以我们需要一些东西给你，否则这会奏效，就像外面有很多盘子一样。
OK, OK, I'll just I'll just keep I'll just keep chopping.
好的，好的，我会，我会继续，我会继续砍。
I'll just keep chopping shrimp.
我只会继续切虾。
I think that's all, you know, I just drop the shrimp.
我想这就是全部，你知道，我只是把虾扔了。
I'll just shop shrimp shop shrimp, top shrimp.
我只会买虾店虾，顶级虾。
Oh, God. The keyboard controls are really weird.
天啊。 键盘控制真的很奇怪。
Do I pick up the plate? You see that? You.
我拿起盘子吗？ 你看到了吗？ 你。
I pick up the plate, and then the shrimp falls off onto the table.
我拿起盘子，然后虾掉到了桌子上。
What is that?
那是什么？
Could you guys tell that, too?
你们也能说说吗？
Right? You guys saw that soon? Fucking tell.
对？ 你们这么快就看到了？ 他妈的告诉。
You got these controls are really going to fuck with me.
你得到这些控制真的会惹恼我。
The game is like, griefing me.
游戏就像，让我伤心。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
Would you, like, push me on the other side of the room?
你愿意把我推到房间的另一边吗？
I was crazy.
我疯了。
Oh, what do you mean?
哦，你什么意思？
This is a real man's kitchen's.
这是一个真正的男人的厨房。
On we're collaborating together. What are you talking about?
关于我们正在合作。 你在说什么？
This is a real house kitchen.
这是一个真正的家庭厨房。
I'll collaborate with your mom.
我会和你妈妈合作。
You know what?
你知道吗？
My mom's dad oh, god.
我妈妈的爸爸哦，天哪。
No, she's not, actually. Boom! Oh.
不，她不是，事实上。 繁荣！ 哦。
My God.
我的上帝。
All right.
好的。
Imagine what they're cursing at us.
想象一下他们在诅咒我们什么。
Your mom. Oh.
你妈。 哦。
Why are they cursing at us? We're doing it.
他们为什么要诅咒我们？ 我们正在这样做。
This is there's only. So much you can handle.
仅此而已。 这么多你可以处理。
Calm down.
冷静下来。
Do you need help over there?
你在那边需要帮助吗？
By the way, it looks like you got a lot fish on your side.
顺便说一句，看起来你身边有很多鱼。
Are you fine?
你还好吗？
Yeah.
是的。
If you could come over and help me chop some fish,
如果你能过来帮我切些鱼，或者我把鱼切好，然后你就可以抓住它，你就可以抓住它。
You know what that's get?
你知道那是什么吗？
That's all that's good on. I could give you plates.
这就是所有的好处。 我可以给你盘子。
Well, I could give you plates.
好吧，我可以给你盘子。
Oh, my God. Yeah. There you go.
我的天啊。 是的。 你去吧。
Yeah, that's. That's a finished meal right there. You can grab those. Yeah, yeah.
是的，就是这样。 那是一顿完成的饭菜。 你可以抓住那些。 是啊是啊。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
I can help you out, OK?
我可以帮你，好吗？
You know, is not so bad. This one's not.
你知道，没有那么糟糕。 这个不是。
Elaborate.
精心制作的。
Elaborate on. OK.
详细说明。 好的。
And you just dropped it on the floor.
而你只是把它掉在了地板上。
Wait, can I serve this
等等，我可以提供这个吗？ 患病的
be Larry's sauce.
成为拉里的调味酱。
Drop it on the floor, though. Now.
不过，把它扔在地板上。 现在。
I'm not a shrimp.
我不是虾。
I'm not a shrimp. Oh, God. Oh, God.
我不是虾。 天啊。 天啊。
No, no, actually, actually, you got one.
不，不，实际上，实际上，你有一个。
More like you.
更像你。
One more, one more. Yeah, yeah.
再来一张，再来一张。 是啊是啊。
726. Oh, boy.
726.哦，男孩。
Not bad. Not bad at all.
不错。 一点也不差。
Look at us.
看着我们。
Look at us three. So let us look at that dog. God.
看看我们三个。 那么让我们看看那条狗。 上帝。
All right, all right. Well, making it. We're making it.
好吧，好吧。 嗯，成功了。 我们正在做。
That wasn't so bad.
那还不错。
Yeah, it was actually quite easy.
是的，这实际上很容易。
It was just chopping shrimp and fish
只是切虾和鱼，人们吃生虾吗？
I've never seen that.
我从来没有见过。
I guess so.
大概吧。
Or maybe they'd already been cooked and we were just chopping them.
或者也许它们已经煮熟了，我们只是在切它们。
Oh, OK. You know what? You do have a point there.
哦好的。 你知道吗？ 你确实有一点。
OK, I want. To fucking desert level. Did it?
好的，我想要。 到他妈的沙漠级别。 做到了？
It did it, Len. Thinking
做到了，莱恩。 思维
that it had it at a
它有它
weight. Where are we?
重量。 我们在哪？
New recipe.
新食谱。
Sushi sushi. Sushi.
寿司寿司。 寿司。
We need to chop fish.
我们需要切鱼。
And then you boil.
然后你煮沸。
This out of rock.
这出石头了。
It looks like a rock of rice.
它看起来像一块大米。
That's a that's a bowl of rice.
那是一碗饭。
That's a bowl of rice all. Or boiling the rock.
那就是一碗饭。 或煮沸岩石。
OK, OK, so.
好的，好的，所以。
So before we begin. Oh, my. God. Is pause.
所以在我们开始之前。 天啊。 上帝。 是暂停。
Pause, pause.
暂停，暂停。
OK, yeah, yeah.
好的，是的，是的。
Pause. OK, so the shopping bowls are on my side.
暂停。 好的，所以购物碗在我这边。
I will chop while meanwhile the boiling is on your side.
我会切，同时沸腾在你身边。
You should grab the the rice and boil it on your side.
你应该抓住米饭，一边煮一边煮。
OK, that would be kind of like splitting the thing up.
好吧，这有点像把事情分开。
And then when my stuff is done, I'll bring it over to you.
然后等我的东西完成后，我会把它带给你。
Actually, you should bring the rice to me and then I'll get the sushi.
其实，你应该把米饭给我，然后我去拿寿司。
OK, with.
好的，与。
Are are they ok? OK.
他们还好吗？ 好的。
I can see that. These people are getting in my way.
我知道。 这些人正在妨碍我。
Why are they working in the kitchen?
他们为什么在厨房工作？
The thing, the thing about overcooked
事情，关于煮过头的事情是它会惹你生气，并且在不同的阶段会有障碍。
Yeah. Bucket out the fucking kitchen.
是的。 铲除他妈的厨房。
Well, who are you people?
好吧，你们是什么人？
Who are you? Evil.
你是谁？ 邪恶的。
Oh, my God. I'm a chill in that right now.
我的天啊。 我现在对此很冷淡。
Do that right.
做对了。
Hold this.
握住这个。
We'll at this.
我们会在这。
I mean, sushi.
我的意思是，寿司。
Doesn't bad fucking.
他妈的不坏。
Syria. It's burning by the fucking rice.
叙利亚。 它被他妈的大米烧着了。
You ready? Did I make tonight make sushi? Does I just make sushi?
你准备好了吗？ 我今晚做了寿司吗？ 我只做寿司吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
No, no. Look at this. Look at that sushi.
不，不。 看这个。 看那个寿司。
Look at it. Sushi, go.
看它。 寿司，走。
I think I did it.
我想我做到了。
OK, where's my other porco?
好的，我的另一只猪呢？
Hello?
你好？
Oh, it's right here. Thank you.
哦，就在这里。 谢谢你。
OK, sir, please get the fuck out of the kitchen.
好的，先生，请他妈的滚出厨房。
I'm not still cooking as you have.
我不像你那样做饭。
Please, from your side.
请，从你身边。
Why is everything everywhere? I can like I can, like, throw shit.
为什么无处不在？ 我可以喜欢我可以，喜欢，扔屎。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
There we go. Off, off, off, off, off.
我们去吧。 关，关，关，关，关。
Off. All the.
离开。 一切。
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, dude, dude, what is happening? What is happening?
哦，伙计，伙计，发生了什么事？ 怎么了？
Hold on, hold on, hold on. Hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持。 坚持，稍等。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Oh, fucking idiot.
哦，该死的白痴。
God. That's a lot.
上帝。 那是很多。
It's a lot.
这是很多。
OK, what is. It's on.
好的，是什么。 它开着。
Oh, you know what? That looks pretty good. That's good. Rice.
哦，你知道吗？ 这看起来很不错。 那很好。 米。
Uncle Roger would be proud of
罗杰叔叔会为
I'd put more.
我会放更多。
More rice.
更多的米饭。
OK, I see.
好的我明白了。
I could just take it off of that. I'd take it off of the fucking.
我可以把它去掉。 我会把它从他妈的上拿下来。
So I'm getting used to controls now. Yeah. Yeah.
所以我现在习惯了控制。 是的。 是的。
Get out of the way.
走开。
Oh, my God. It's up. Like.
我的天啊。 它起来了。 像。
What do you mean, soccer players?
你是什​​么意思，足球运动员？
She's walking right in front of my fucking job.
她正走在我该死的工作前面。
To complain.
去抱怨。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
OK, give it, give it.
好，给，给。
Give it to me. Give it to me.
把它给我。 把它给我。
What happened to the rice?
米饭怎么了？
You just took away my rice. I put it on the fucking plate
你刚刚抢走了我的米饭。
because you're being too slow, you fucking pillock.
我把它放在他妈的盘子上，因为你太慢了，你他妈的笨蛋。
I didn't know there was a there's a point there.
我不知道那里有一个意义。
Oh, shit. Yes.
妈的。 是的。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Ah, more rice.
啊，更多的米饭。
More rice. I'm making I'm making more rice.
更多的米饭。 我正在做我正在做更多的米饭。
Wait, no, that's. That's fish. Harder.
等等，不，就是这样。 那是鱼。 更难。
Drop the fish.
放下鱼。
Ow, ow, ow, ow. Ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜 哦。
You're just throwing stuff at me.
你只是在向我扔东西。
How did you do that all by yourself?
你是怎么一个人做到的？
It's control. Actually, I figured it out.
是控制。 其实，我想通了。
Yeah, ok. OK, ok. All right.
是的，好的。 好的好的。 好的。
I got more rice. More rice. Oh.
我得到了更多的米饭。 更多的米饭。 哦。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Wait. No, I had to put this on a plate now, too.
等待。 不，我现在也必须把它放在盘子里。
OK, look at that. More rice. Yes.
好的，看那个。 更多的米饭。 是的。
You got to put the rice on that fucking.
你必须把米饭放在那个他妈的上。
Plate, you idiot.
盘子，你这个白痴。
Oh, I picked up the fish.
哦，我捡到了鱼。
What's the fish doing on the floor?
地板上的鱼在做什么？
What is that fish doing on the fucking floor?
那条鱼在他妈的地板上做什么？
Where did that come from?
那个是从哪里来的？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There's so much fish
有这么多鱼
I don't know where to put the play.
我不知道该把戏放在哪里。
Just put the fucking blades down, you stupid dog.
把他妈的刀片放下，你这个笨狗。
OK, ok, ok. OK.
好好好。 好的。
Everything I've seen here is you, ok?
我在这里看到的都是你，好吗？
Dude, I'm plugging right now.
哥们，我现在就挂了。
Oh, no, I'm not. No, not.
哦，不，我不是。 不，不是。
What, dude? All of my power.
什么，伙计？ 我所有的力量。
Never plugged in.
从来没有插过。
You all of fucking.
你们都他妈的。
My follow some mega improv.
我跟随一些大型即兴表演。
You've never plugged in you all fucking night.
你他妈的从来没有插上电源。
Do we fail, dude?
我们失败了吗，伙计？
Power way.
电源方式。
How how we were doing is listen, listen.
我们是怎么做的就是听，听。
You just it's not about fulfilling every order.
你只是不是要完成每一个订单。
It's about fulfilling enough orders.
这是关于完成足够的订单。
So if the orders run, the orders will keep coming until you run out of time.
因此，如果订单运行，订单将一直持续到您用完时间为止。
But all you have to do is make sure that none of them run out of time.
但是您所要做的就是确保它们中的任何一个都不会超时。
So you people, ok, ok,
所以你们这些人，好的，好的，如果一个订单失败了，那就是你开始移动点的时候。
No, chef.
不，厨师。
Chef bog
厨师沼泽
all you fuck.
你他妈的。
OK, that makes more sense now.
好的，现在这更有意义了。
I thought we had to fulfil all the fucking orders.
我以为我们必须履行所有他妈的命令。
So then when the tickets just kept. Coming and coming and.
所以当时的票就这样存了。 来来来和。
Coming and coming and coming and coming, I started.
来来来，来来去去，我开始了。
I kind of don't stop coming. You give me some road head
我有点不停地来。 你给我一些路头
road ahead.
前面的路。
Wait, what's road ahead?
等等，前面的路是什么？
Oh, he's so sweet. He gets.
哦，他好可爱。 他得到。
Is it like road?
像路吗？
Is it like road? Kill
像路吗？ 杀
and I definitely a horn.
我绝对是一个喇叭。
We are going to look that up real quick.
我们将很快查明这一点。
You got me curious. Oh, yeah, go ahead. Look it up.
你让我很好奇。 哦，是的，继续。 查一下。
Yeah, a road, right?
是的，一条路，对吧？
Don't look up for me. Actually, don't look up.
不要抬头看我。 其实不用抬头。
You could look me in the.
你可以看看我。
Road ahead the end of the road where men and goods must continue on foot.
道路的尽头是人和货物必须继续步行的道路。
Sir, the animals, heroic brands.
先生，动物，英雄品牌。
What That's not quite what I meant, but let's listen.
这不是我的意思，但让我们听着。
We'll just.
我们只会。
We'll just move on. We'll just move on.
我们将继续前进。 我们将继续前进。
And the acts of a man receiving.
和一个人接受的行为。
Hey, you go.
嘿，你走吧。
That's that box that's, you know.
那就是那个盒子，你知道的。
You know, I'm curious.
你知道，我很好奇。
I know you, Michael. I thought, you know.
我认识你，迈克尔。 我想，你知道的。
I had to think about it for a second. It's like I bought you.
我不得不考虑一下。 就像我买了你一样。
I just like to come.
我只是喜欢来。
Butcher girl as a as like the same.
屠夫少女就像一个一样。
If I. Am OK, what do I do now?
如果我没事，我现在该怎么办？
I don't get distracted by my fucking dick. All right?
我不会被我他妈的鸡巴分心。 好的？
I'm bigger, right? I'll put some rice. Inside
我更大了，对吧？ 我会放一些米饭。 里面
on. Your side.
在。 你的身边。
Put the rice in the saucepans, OK?
把米饭放在平底锅里，好吗？
All I have are we. What is this going to start?
我只有我们。 这是什么开始？
I'm going to start chopping the shrimp. I'm going to start chopping.
我要开始切虾了。 我要开始切菜了。
I'm about to start chopping.
我要开始切菜了。
Butter, and we're in business now.
黄油，我们现在在做生意。
Come on. Oh, shit. You're right. Oh, my God.
来吧。 妈的。 你说的对。 我的天啊。
I was going how to drop it.
我正想怎么放下它。
How do I drop it?
我该如何丢弃它？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh. Oh, my.
哦。 天啊。
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
No, no, no.
不不不。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Fuck him.
操他。
You're burning fucking rice, you idiot. OK, how do I.
你在烧大米，你这个白痴。 好的，我该怎么做。
How do I.
我如何。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
Can we use this?
我们可以用这个吗？
No, I've got to put it in the fucking bin.
不，我必须把它放在他妈的垃圾箱里。
Now, as you. Saucepan back, you idiot.
现在，和你一样。 平底锅回来，你这个白痴。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK, thank you. Thank you. OK. Ah.
好的谢谢。 谢谢你。 好的。 啊。
Oh, I have cucumbers on my side. You know what?
哦，我身边有黄瓜。 你知道吗？
I think you might need cucumbers.
我想你可能需要黄瓜。
I'm going to bring it over there till are
我要把它带到那里直到
I got it with this much.
我得到了这么多。
It's going to be a.
这将是一个。
Worry, boy.
担心，男孩。
Come on. Here you go. Here you go. Here you. Go.
来吧。 干得好。 干得好。 给你。 去。
There we go. We got rhythm going now. All right, all right. That's that's.
我们去吧。 我们现在有了节奏。 好吧，好吧。 就是这样。
OK. OK, now. Repugnant.
好的。 现在没事了。 令人反感。
I had to wash dishes. Now
我不得不洗碗。 现在
I'm full of fucking cucumber.
我全是他妈的黄瓜。
I don't know. I thought you needed cucumber.
我不知道。 我以为你需要黄瓜。
You any ingredients off the counters for the fucking cucumber?
你他妈的黄瓜的柜台上有什么配料吗？
What am I supposed to do with the shrimp?
我该怎么处理虾？
If you're talking about cucumbers, anything on your mind?
如果你在谈论黄瓜，你有什么想法吗？
No one's going to be fucking voodoo to that.
没有人会对此深恶痛绝。
I'm trying to give you like this shit.
我想给你这样的狗屎。
You come up because you filled up the whole thing.
你上来是因为你填满了整个事情。
With fucking cucumber.
用他妈的黄瓜。
It's a wash the dishes to wash the dishes till it's all going on, bro.
这是一个洗碗洗碗，直到一切顺利，兄弟。
Oh, here, go. OK, there.
哦，来了，走吧。 好的，那里。
Yeah, there's. There's some there's some.
是的，有。 有一些有一些。
What about a fella? First fucking order.
一个家伙呢？ 第一个他妈的订单。
Are we really?
我们真的吗？
Are we really? There's no way. There's no way.
我们真的吗？ 不可能。 不可能。
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
We're too good at this game.
我们太擅长这场比赛了。
I need more rice.
我需要更多的米饭。
Unless I could be an extra an extra special chef. There you go. Yeah.
除非我可以成为一个额外的特别厨师。 你去吧。 是的。
I need more rice and more rice. Any more rice?
我需要更多的米饭和更多的米饭。 还有米饭吗？
Here's another.
这是另一个。
Cucumber. There you go.
黄瓜。 你去吧。
WA wa wa wa wa wa. Wait, wait.
哇哇哇哇哇哇。 等等。
This is done.
这个完成了。
This rice is done. You Dick. You got to be quicker about it.
这饭做好了。 你迪克。 你得快点。
You've got to realise those things.
你得快点。 你必须意识到这些事情。
I was testing you.
我在考验你。
What do you mean
你是什​​么意思
you're testing you? You're really me, huh?
你在考验你吗？ 你真的是我，对吧？
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
You got to be quicker. When we got. That's bullshit, right?
你得快点。 当我们得到。 那是胡说八道，对吧？
You failed. I don't know what to do of this.
你失败了。 我不知道该怎么办。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
OK. Ah,
好的。 啊，
so we all.
所以我们都。
Know, and I'm just letting you know right now we are not passing this on.
知道，我现在只是让你知道我们不会传递这个。
This has been a fucking train wreck.
这该死的火车事故。
I have faith.
我有信仰。
Why are you giving me cooked rice again?
你怎么又给我煮饭了？
I didn't do that shit.
我没有做那种事。
Yes, you did.
是的，你做到了。
You brought back the cooked rice.
你把煮好的米饭带回来了。
We all make too many. Oh, my God, it.
我们都做太多了。 哦，我的上帝，它。
Nah, mate.
不，伙计。
We got this we still got this. I think
我们得到了这个，我们仍然得到了这个。 我认为
yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yeah. No, we're fucked. We're fucked. No, we're not. No, we're not.
是的。 不，我们完蛋了。 我们完蛋了。 不，我们不是。 不，我们不是。
We're not looking at this.
我们不看这个。
Look at this. Look at this. You've never seen.
看这个。 看这个。 你从未见过。
I'm guaranteed like one star maximum.
我保证像一颗星最多。
What happened?
发生了什么？
What is the old gab?
什么是老套路？
I'll tell to I'll tell you.
我会告诉我会告诉你的。
I'll tell you what happened is you can deliver your shit.
我会告诉你发生了什么是你可以交付你的狗屎。
I'm very disappointed in you, boy.
我对你很失望，男孩。
Deliver my shit.
交付我的狗屎。
You had the thingy on your side,
你有东西在你身边，对吧？ 声音。
Now, you kept it in the rice.
现在，你把它放在米饭里。
You had the conveyor belt on your side.
你身边有传送带。
What, you mean I couldn't deliver my shit? Yeah, I'm.
什么，你的意思是我不能提供我的狗屎？ 是的，我是。
I'm responsible. For the orders. You want to give me the rice.
我负责。 对于订单。 你想给我米饭。
I was giving you, right?
我是给你的，对吧？
What, you feel like you got this
什么，你觉得你得到了这个
much rice, all these shakes?
大米，所有这些震动？
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
You told back to me.
你回了我一句。
Boy, you're brand new in this field.
男孩，你在这个领域是全新的。
I've been here for decades. Give you.
我在这里已经有几十年了。 给你。
You can talk back to me, boy.
你可以跟我说话，男孩。
I gave up on you.
我放弃了你。
You want to rice?
你要饭吗？
You want rice?
你要米饭吗？
OK, you know why you want rice so bad?
好吧，你知道你为什么那么想要米饭吗？
I'm going to give you rice. I'm going to give you some fucking right.
我要给你米饭。 我要给你一些他妈的权利。
Give me your fucking money.
给我你他妈的钱。
There you go. OK, there's some rice to go.
你去吧。 好的，有一些米饭要去。
Give the rice. Give me more rice. Even more rice. Fuck you.
给米饭。 给我更多的米饭。 米饭还要多。 去你的。
Just kidding.
只是在开玩笑。
I love you, you know.
我爱你，你知道吗。
Of course he comes crawling back.
他当然是爬回来的。
What are you doing on my side?
你站在我这边做什么？
I already gave you rice.
我已经给你米饭了。
Fucking give me enough rice. I need three rice only.
他妈的给我足够的米饭。 我只需要三粒米饭。
There's only one dish with rice in it
只有一道菜里有米饭。 有。
No. There's two.
不，有两个。
You're a liar. Well, there are now.
你是个骗子。 嗯，现在有。
It just popped. Up.
它刚刚弹出。 向上。
No, I think you're a liar.
不，我认为你是个骗子。
I've been gassed lately, Larry, I.
我最近被毒死了，拉里，我。
You want me to go on, test my fucking patience like that, boy?
你想让我继续，像那样测试我他妈的耐心，男孩？
That's why I'll fucking test you. I'll fucking SAS here.
这就是为什么我要他妈的测试你。 我会在这里他妈的SAS。
I get on it again. Oh, you know, that was me.
我再接再厉。 哦，你知道，那是我。
My fucking dishes, bitch. Wash my. Fucking dishes.
我他妈的菜，婊子。 洗我的。 该死的菜。
What is wrong with you?
你怎么了？
I'm Leach caricature of you. What the hell?
我是你的利奇漫画。 我勒个去？
I'm. I'm
我是。 我是
like,
像，
give me.
给我吗。
Give me the rice. Give me the right. No.
给我米饭。 给我权利。 不。
Oh, that's good.
哦，那很好。
No. Pick up the bup bup.
不。拿起小疙瘩。
Bup. Bup.
呸。 呸。
What you. Doing is on my side. For you.
你什么。 做事就在我身边。 为你。
You like Popeye? Why do you take my pop for?
你喜欢大力水手吗？ 你为什么拿我的流行音乐？
Because you put it on my side.
因为你把它放在我身边。
There's no other room.
没有别的房间了。
I need a.
我需要一个。
Body. 3 hours.
身体。  3小时。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
I forgot about the cucumbers.
我忘了黄瓜。
I forgot. I fucking forgot about the cucumbers.
我忘了。 我他妈的忘记了黄瓜。
I'm not fucking cucumbers right now.
我现在不是他妈的黄瓜。
OK, here you go.
好的，给你。
On. Another help.
在。 另一个帮助。
I'll help
我会帮助
you're not fucking helping.
你他妈的不是在帮忙。
You're in my way.
你挡着我的路。
The right way.
正确的方式。
It's burning. It's raining, it's raining.
它在燃烧。 下雨了，下雨了。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔喔噢
Oh, shit.
妈的。
He didn't see that. It's OK.
他没有看到。 没关系。
What didn't I say? What did I say? You are
我没说什么？ 我说了什么？ 你是
going like I say anything.
就像我说什么。
I'm like I said. You got a move. A fast one. I mean, you know, you're not.
我就像我说的那样。 你有一个动作。 一个快的。 我的意思是，你知道，你不是。
You're not know.
你不知道。
If you. Mess up my restaurant, I will fucking kill.
如果你。 把我的餐厅搞砸了，我他妈会杀了。
You. Your restaurant? It's our. Restaurants.
你。 你的餐厅？ 这是我们的。 餐馆。
What was ours? You're my apprentice.
什么是我们的？ 你是我的徒弟。
You're our hey.
你是我们的嘿嘿。
You can serve for once in your life.
你可以在你的生活中服务一次。
Have you ever considered, like, you know, for once?
你有没有考虑过，比如，你知道，一次？
Maybe.
也许。
Maybe this is a collaborative effort where we're sharing.
也许这是我们共享的协作努力。
Nothing about collaboration.
与合作无关。
This is not a. Sharing. Of our age.
这不是一个。 分享。 我们这个年纪。
This is about you washing my fucking dishes, boy.
这是关于你洗我他妈的盘子，男孩。
Give me.
给我吗。
Just give me more rice.
给我更多的米饭。
Any more rice? Please, please, box, please.
还有米饭吗？ 请，请，请，请框。
Rice, rice, rice. Put it in the pot.
米饭，米饭，米饭。 把它放在锅里。
But I'll put it.
但我会说的。
I'll put you in the pot.
我会把你放进锅里。
Chef, chef, chef.
厨师，厨师，厨师。
Chef.
厨师。
You will be. Boiled. Chef.
你将会。 煮沸。 厨师。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
You will be boiled.
你会被煮的。
You know this is not fair. This is what is.
你知道这不公平。 这就是事实。
What is this, chef?
这是什么，厨师？
A culinary. Inequality did.
一个美食。 不平等确实如此。
Hold on. Here you go.
坚持，稍等。 干得好。
The inequality is the customers.
不平等是客户。
No, getting that fucking food.
不，得到那该死的食物。
I'm trying my best right now.
我现在正在尽我所能。
Give me a cucumber. Oh, my God.
给我一根黄瓜。 我的天啊。
You think you come back?
你以为你回来了？
I don't know how to put it. Oh, my God. Here.
我不知道该怎么说。 我的天啊。 这里。
You're here. Give me a fucking kick.
你在这里。 给我一个他妈的踢。
Grab the killer. Wow.
抓住凶手。 哇。
I didn't know what I did there. Holy shit. That was amazing.
我不知道我在那里做了什么。 天啊。 那太精彩了。
Oh, you're here. We're cucumber.
哦，你来了。 我们是黄瓜。
We're cucumber, we're cucumber. Here's right through.
我们是黄瓜，我们是黄瓜。 到这里就结束了。
All right.
好的。
You're fucking idiots, dude.
你是他妈的白痴，伙计。
We did it. Easy clap, easy clap.
我们做到了。 轻拍，轻拍。
Look at that. Holy shit.
看那个。 天啊。
All thanks to my leadership soon might.
这一切都归功于我的领导可能很快。
I might.
我可能。
I would like to say my cock grew, like, three inches after that one.
我想说我的鸡巴在那之后长了三英寸。
Oh, good. OK, can I take a look?
哦，很好。 好的，我可以看看吗？
Yeah. On here.
是的。 在这。
I'll bring you over take a look.
我带你过去看看。
Don't look that
不要那样看
shit.
拉屎。
All right.
好的。
That's four inches.
那是四英寸。
Think what you get.
想想你得到了什么。
Right was that I had in my head of Patrick's.
正确的是我在帕特里克的脑海中。
Patrick's Day. Through.
帕特里克节。 通过。
Take it or leave it
要么接受，要么离开它
switches.
开关。
Never switches. Yeah, that's me.
从不切换。 是的，就是我。
OK, so we got a lot of, like, collectables on the map and shit.
好的，所以我们在地图上得到了很多收藏品和狗屎。
OK, hold on.
好的，稍等。
And what the fuck I said that would be all right.
我他妈的说什么也没关系。
I want to find the switch.
我想找到开关。
I'm right here.
我就在这里。
You're not a fucking switch.
你不是他妈的开关。
You're a bomb. No,
你是一颗炸弹。 不，
people.
人们。
My my I was.
我的我是。
It told me to be more assertive.
它告诉我要更加自信。
Is something more assertive about my switch rights, too.
对我的切换权限也更加自信。
We got a. Balloons. We're buoyant.
我们得到了一个。 气球。 我们充满活力。
What a sick. Foot.
有什么病。 脚丫子。
I'm trying to untangle the subject, but
我试图解开这个主题，但换马。
Kevin one. What.
凯文一个。 什么。
Is Kevin one you were trying wrong.
凯文是你试错的人。
All right, so we're both separated again.
好吧，所以我们又分开了。
No new recipe.
没有新配方。
Oh, no. Why is it steamed?
不好了。 为什么要蒸？
Hams, old family recipe.
火腿，古老的家庭食谱。
Way it's steamed.
蒸的样子。
Chopped me or veg mixed with flour and then steam together.
将我切碎或将蔬菜与面粉混合，然后一起蒸。
This is like. Is it like bowels?
这就像。 像肠子吗？
Or we can bowels
或者我们可以大便
on what is this?
这是什么？
I'm OK.
我很好。
So what's the fire extinguisher?
那么什么是灭火器呢？
All right, so you got some flour.
好的，所以你有一些面粉。
What do I do with a.
我该怎么办。
For tomorrow's the meat and then steam it to get.
明天的肉再蒸就可以了。
All right, there's the flour. Thank you very.
好了，面粉来了。 非常感谢。
Much. Yeah, I don't want the other flour.
很多。 是的，我不想要其他面粉。
What's the flavour?
味道是什么？
This one's easy.
这个很容易。
It's easy for me.
这对我来说很容易。
Are you sure it's easy?
你确定这很容易吗？
I don't know. It's feeling and feeling a little.
我不知道。 这是感觉和感觉。
Feel a little sauce.
感觉有点酱。
Do this.
做这个。
I got an order for you. Got an order for you? What?
我有一个订单给你。 有订单给你吗？ 什么？
Our idea of this oh, no.
我们的想法哦，不。
Here, here, here, here.
这里，这里，这里，这里。
Here, right here. You'll never know.
在这里，就在这里。 你永远不会知道。
I thought I have to play.
我以为我必须玩。
I'll never much anything. Fuck you. God.
我什么都不会。 去你的。 上帝。
I learnt that from Mr..
我是从先生那里得知的。
You will never.
你永远不会。
You can't, right?
你不能，对吧？
You got to put me in bowls. OK.
你得把我放进碗里。 好的。
Here's the fish.
这里是鱼。
Oh, that's on.
哦，那是开着的。
Oh, I have to.
哦，我必须。
I have to let the order almost no cooking.
我不得不让订单几乎没有烹饪。
It's not cooking.
这不是做饭。
Fucking don't ask.
他妈的不问。
No, it's not. Wait, it's done.
不它不是。 等等，完成了。
Can I get a bowl, please?
请给我一碗好吗？
Needs a plate.
需要一个盘子。
Hold on, hold on. Bowl. Bowl. You need a bowl?
等一下，等一下。 碗。 碗。 你需要一个碗吗？
I got a bowl for you.
我给你准备了一碗。
I got a bowl for you. Here, here.
我给你准备了一碗。 这儿这儿。
There's a bowl.
有一个碗。
All right. Good ah.
好的。 好啊。
Oh, shit. Excuse me.
妈的。 打扰一下。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
I got another order for. Yeah.
我有另一个订单。 是的。
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
哦，等一下，等一下，等一下。
Oh, dude, I only have two steamers over here.
哦，伙计，我这里只有两艘汽船。
What do I do with the bowl?
我拿碗做什么？
Why do I have so many bowls for.
为什么我有这么多碗。
The bowls of mine?
我的碗？
Give me the bowls.
把碗给我。
I'm trying to give you fish. Hold on. There, there.
我想给你鱼。 坚持，稍等。 那里，那里。
There's a fish.
有一条鱼。
There's more fish. There's a bowl of flour.
还有更多的鱼。 有一碗面粉。
You gotta be honest with you.
你必须对你诚实。
I can't do anything with the fish that's about to burn.
我不能对即将燃烧的鱼做任何事情。
You got to put the fish straight in the steamer.
你得把鱼直接放进蒸笼里。
Oh, I had to put it right into the steamer.
哦，我必须把它直接放进蒸笼里。
Yeah, OK. OK.
是的，好的。 好的。
Oh, you're right. You're right.
哦，你是对的。 你说的对。
You're so right. You're so right. I always. Am.
你说的太对了。 你说的太对了。 我总是。 是。
Why is this order sitting on the fucking side?
为什么这个命令坐在他妈的一边？
I don't know. I was just about to get water.
我不知道。 我刚要喝水。
I have to do the dishes, too. No, you do the dishes.
我也要洗碗。 不，你洗碗。
Big boy. Go do the dishes.
大男孩。 去洗碗。
Fuck you.
去你的。
Oh, my God, dude.
哦，天哪，伙计。
OK, this is done.
好的，这就完成了。
This w plates are your powers.
这 w 板是你的力量。
Are all this is burning. This burning. Oh, my god.
难道这一切都在燃烧。 这种燃烧。 我的天啊。
Everything's burning, everything's burning, everything's burning.
一切都在燃烧，一切都在燃烧，一切都在燃烧。
VOCs.
挥发性有机化合物。
What I do, what I do.
我做什么，我做什么。
Here you go.
干得好。
More fish.
更多的鱼。
More dishes.
更多菜肴。
I think.
我认为。
I think
我认为
what is this for?
这个是来做什么的？
Wait.
等待。
What? What? Wait.
什么？ 什么？ 等待。
Why did you. Why did you take it?
为什么你。 你为什么拿它？
I think I forgot to put flour in that one.
我想我忘了在那个里面放面粉。
That's my bad.
那是我的错。
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。
The meal.
这餐。
Oh, my God. That's a steam. The shiatsu one.
我的天啊。 那是一种蒸汽。 指压按摩。
I got to take this off of your station.
我得把这个从你的站台上拿下来。
Oh, what is that?
哦，那是什么？
That's nothing. It's.
那没什么。 它的。
I fucked it up. I fucked it up. Why is that?
我搞砸了。 我搞砸了。 这是为什么？
Why is I. Well, what the hell?
为什么是我。好吧，到底是什么？
Listen, listen.
听，听。
True.
真的。
Culinary mastery is sometimes.
有时烹饪精通。
Sometimes I'll try to fuck it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
有时我会尝试去他妈的。 耶耶耶。
I'm going to get it. I'm gonna get it.
我会得到它。 我会得到它。
Oh, no, oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no, no.
哦，不，哦，不。 不好了。 不好了。 哦，不，不。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Ah, you thought I've done shit, you pillock.
啊，你以为我做错了，你这个笨蛋。
Are you faffing back there? What was that noise?
你在后面偷懒吗？ 那是什么声音？
I was rubbing my eyes because you're boring me, boy.
我揉了揉眼睛，因为你让我很无聊，男孩。
I'm trying my best. Rubbing my eyes I say.
我正在尽力而为。 我揉着眼睛说。
Sarah, please.
莎拉，请。
See? Well.
看？ 好。
Oh, oh, you see, I didn't know you got me.
哦，哦，你看，我不知道你得到了我。
Sarah got it. I'll come in the dishes. Sir.
莎拉明白了。 我会进来洗碗。 先生。
I thought I'm supposed to call you sir. You're the head shagging.
我想我应该叫你先生。 你是摇头。
The big salty surprise. But then.
最大的咸味惊喜。 但是之后。
Sir. Sir?
先生。 先生？
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
There's a chef.
有厨师。
Oh, chef.
哦，厨师。
Yes. Yes, Chef. Thank you. Chef. Yes, Chef. No, Chef.
是的。 是的，厨师。 谢谢你。 厨师。 是的，厨师。 不，厨师。
Yes, Chef. Yes, Chef.
是的，厨师。 是的，厨师。
Yes, Chef.
是的，厨师。
No, hold up. Hold up, Will.
不，等一下。 等一下，威尔。
Give me a second. Give me a second. I have put the orders out.
你稍等一会儿。 你稍等一会儿。 我已经下订单了。
I put the orders out. I'll give you the dishes.
我下单了。 我把菜给你。
You need more flour. Here's the fucking flour. Thank you.
你需要更多的面粉。 这是他妈的面粉。 谢谢你。
All right, here we go.
好吧，我们开始吧。
Here it was sitting on the counter.
它坐在柜台上。
You're so blind.
你太盲目了。
You're so blind. Vaughn.
你太盲目了。 沃恩。
There is counter right there.
那里有柜台。
Now, there wasn't flour on the counter that was on the plate.
现在，盘子上的柜台上没有面粉。
You literally put flour in a bucket of fucking flour.
你真的把面粉放在一桶他妈的面粉里。
I can put that in the bowl. I tried multiple times. It didn't. Work.
我可以把它放在碗里。 我尝试了多次。 它没有。 工作。
Or you saw here I didn't pull out a plate.
或者你看到这里我没有拿出一个盘子。
It was really on the plate.
它真的在盘子里。
Yeah.
是的。
You put flour alone on a plate.
你把面粉单独放在盘子里。
I can't put that in a fucking bowl. Really? It's.
我不能把它放在他妈的碗里。 真的吗？ 它的。
I really
我真的
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, Papa, can you just take it off the play, Farid?
哦，爸爸，你能把它从剧中去掉吗，法里德？
I can't.
我不能。
The game on. Let me
比赛进行中。 让我来
that seems like it might be a bit beyond us.
似乎它可能有点超出我们的范围。
You sure it's beyond us?
你确定它超出了我们的范围？
You keep it if you. If you're.
如果你保留它。 如果你是。
If you're feeling ballsy about not.
如果你对不感到胆怯。
Actually, no, I'm not feeling that ballsy.
实际上，不，我并没有那么胆小。
Yeah. I didn't think you were. You never asked.
是的。 我没想到你是。 你从来没有问过。
Oh. I was actually upset.
哦。 我其实很沮丧。
Fuck you. Oh, my dear. God, you are until.
去你的。 哦，我亲爱的。 上帝，你直到。
Don't you?
你不是吗？
Are you one of us? You are.
你是我们中的一员吗？ 你是。
You're like you feel you're you're like a five inch dildo, you know that?
你就像你觉得你就像一个五英寸的假阳具，你知道吗？
Not even not even six and still dog five you one of.
甚至连六个都没有，仍然狗五个你之一。
Those single tier.
那些单层。
People going to the fucking restaurant?
人们去他妈的餐厅？
Do I look like a double fucking rainbow to you?
对你来说，我看起来像双彩虹吗？
What's that mean?
那什么意识？
What the fuck does that mean? What are these insults are.
这他妈是什么意思？ 这些侮辱是什么。
You into a tearing up?
你成泪了？
You're tearing up.
你在流泪。
I'm like a double fucking rainbow.
我就像一条他妈的彩虹。
And you don't don't flatter
你不不奉承
yourself.
你自己。
We we can dash Maggie.
我们可以冲刺玛姬。
Sushi on Zoom.
Zoom 上的寿司。
Oh, my God. I'm fast. Look at me,
我的天啊。 我很快。 看着我，
look at me. Go look at me. Go.
看着我。 去看看我。 去。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Louis, move out of my way.
路易斯，让开我的路。
No, you bastard.
不，你这个混蛋。
I fuck in reviews. There you go.
我他妈的评论。 你去吧。
Why is it look like one of those?
为什么它看起来像其中之一？
Like, what's it called? Those on rotating.
比如，它叫什么？ 那些在旋转。
Those rotating?
那些旋转的？
Yeah, I think. I think that's, like, literally the entire point.
是的，我想。 我认为这就是字面上的全部意义。
And that's like, a really obvious joke that they're going for.
这就像，他们想要的一个非常明显的笑话。
OK, well, you don't have to be so mean about it.
好吧，好吧，你不必那么刻薄。
I mean, I mean.
我是说，我是说。
I mean.
我是说。
I mean, maybe I don't have to be, but like, you've either.
我的意思是，也许我不必是，但就像，你有。
Fucked all I can push you.
他妈的我能推你。
I can bully you like that.
我可以这样欺负你。
Then we'll get enough fucking served, boy.
然后我们会得到足够的他妈的服务，男孩。
Well, I just made an entire meal.
好吧，我刚做了一顿饭。
What have you been doing?
你这阵子都在干什么？
I've been making rice for your dumb arse.
我一直在为你的笨蛋做米饭。
What are you talking about? What have I done?
你在说什么？ 我做了什么？
Rice. Rice.
米。 米。
This is like the the essence of life.
这就像生命的本质。
For some people and food.
对于一些人和食物。
Oh, my God, you're fucking cereal. You wouldn't even know.
哦，我的上帝，你他妈的是麦片。 你甚至不会知道。
He wouldn't know. You wouldn't fucking up.
他不会知道的。 你不会搞砸的。
I what are you sleeping about?
我你睡什么？
You're sleeping on the job.
你在工作中睡觉。
Is it on the lot?
是在地段吗？
Cause, boy, you fuck you.
因为，男孩，你操你。
It's about the fuck, you. Know?
这是关于他妈的，你。 知道？
I got it, I got it, I got it. I'm not even.
我明白了，我明白了，我明白了。 我什至不是。
Not even worried and not even worried.
甚至不担心，甚至不担心。
Are you worried about
你担心吗
everything's everything's fine.
一切都很好。
Fine.
美好的。
Everything's OK sometimes.
有时一切都很好。
Sometimes you just have to.
有时你只需要这样做。
Yet can can vice be raw?
然而，罪恶可以是原始的吗？
It can be all right.
可以没事的。
You'll be raw in a minute if you shut the fuck up.
如果你他妈的闭嘴，你会在一分钟内生吃。
Maybe I don't want to shut the fuck up.
也许我不想他妈的闭嘴。
It's a good thing I like it. But I don't want me.
这是一件好事，我喜欢它。 但我不要我。
I don't want to shut the fuck up. What is your.
我不想他妈的闭嘴。 你的...是。
Why is there chopped cucumber here?
为什么这里有切碎的黄瓜？
I can't even grab it. OK, I'm going to be real with you.
我什至无法抓住它。 好吧，我会和你真诚的。
I throw it and I can't reach you.
我把它扔了，我够不到你。
I can't grab the cucumber. What's.
我抓不到黄瓜。 什么是。
Oh, no, you can't
哦，不，你不能
all now.
现在全部。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
On a on on on on on on oh, no, no, no.
On a on on on on on 哦，不，不，不。
We there's dirty dishes over here.
我们这里有脏盘子。
Lots of dirty dishes.
很多脏盘子。
Move.
移动。
Oh, my God. You're grieving.
我的天啊。 你在悲伤。
Oh, shit, dude, you're actually. You're crazy.
哦，狗屎，伙计，你真的是。 你疯了。
I was trying to sell you food.
我想卖给你食物。
You fucking me.
你他妈的我。
You actually are a devil.
你其实是个魔鬼。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
What was that?
那是什么？
Good devil.
好恶魔。
Whoa. I threw fish.
哇。 我扔了鱼。
Move out of the way. Oh, my God.
错。 我的天啊。
I lost my where's my rice?
我丢了我的米在哪里？
Dude, what's of Iraq's?
伙计，伊拉克的呢？
Well.
好。
My rice.
我的米饭。
My rice box.
我的饭盒。
Yeah. Where is your ice? Where's your it's right here.
是的。 你的冰在哪里？ 你在哪里，就在这里。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Well, why do you keep throwing my rice
好吧，你为什么一直扔我的饭
oh, here we go.
哦，我们开始吧。
You go. Ah,
你去。 啊，
watch it.
看它。
Keep track of
不要跟丢
how you want more rice or more rice, babe.
你想要更多的米饭还是更多的米饭，宝贝。
Babe.
宝贝。
I got tons of rice.
我有很多米。
Babe. More rice, tons. No, I'm good.
宝贝。 更多的大米，吨。 不，我很好。
I'm good. You're good.
我很好。 你很好。
All right, why are you talking like that or talking.
好吧，你为什么那样说话或说话。
I got a ton of. Rice highlights. Oh, my God.
我有一吨。 大米亮点。 我的天啊。
Why are you talking like that? Yes. I'm so sorry.
你为什么这样说话？ 是的。 我很抱歉。
I'm so sad.
我很伤心。
You know, you sound so sad. I'm sound.
你知道，你听起来很伤心。 我是健全的。
Why are you sad for.
你为什么难过。
Sad because. This restaurant's going to fucking shit.
伤心因为。 这家餐厅真他妈烂。
Dude. We're all.
老兄。 我们都是。
No, we're not. Fine. Wait,
不，我们不是。 美好的。 等待，
we were not fine, actually.
实际上，我们并不好。
Hold up, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持，坚持。
I can, I can, I can. We can recover.
我可以，我可以，我可以。 我们可以恢复。
We can cover to cover.
我们可以覆盖覆盖。
We can recover.
我们可以恢复。
Why do 2 minutes like I'm not even joking right now.
为什么2分钟就像我现在不是在开玩笑一样。
2 minutes passes by like it's fucking nothing.
2分钟过去了，就像他妈什么都没有。
Yeah, we got our. We got a star
是的，我们得到了我们的。 我们得到了一颗星
all right, listen,
好吧，听着，
all right, listen.
好吧，听着。
OK, ok, I'm listening. I'm listening.
好的，好的，我在听。 我正在听。
You and I
你和我
are going to have to learn how to work together, because otherwise,
将不得不学习如何一起工作，否则，这将永远行不通。
We need to make a plan.
我们需要制定一个计划。
What's our plan?
我们的计划是什么？
Let's get back in there in this figure out. OK.
让我们回到这个数字。 好的。
Ok, ok, I'm listening. I'm listening.
好的，好的，我在听。 我正在听。
I thought I. Was doing the rice.
我以为我在做米饭。
Let me do the rice.
让我做米饭。
Let me do the rice chopper. Oh.
让我做切米机。 哦。
We did. Look, the next thing.
我们做到了。 看，接下来。
But I think we need more stars from those stars.
但我认为我们需要更多来自这些明星的明星。
We need. We need to do bag.
我们需要。 我们需要做包。
Do we know how to collaborate?
我们知道如何合作吗？
What happened. To us?
发生了什么。 给我们？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Why you sound so sad.
为什么你听起来那么悲伤。
Is that why you're so sad?
这就是你如此悲伤的原因吗？
All I've got to pull is I've got a pulse.
我所要做的只是我有一个脉搏。
OK? So
好的？ 所以
you all right?
你没事吧？
We try. I'm thinking
我们试图。 我在想
I will get.
我会得到。
Um, time still ticking, even if it's players.
嗯，时间还在流逝，即使是玩家。
Yeah, it is. Oh, my fucking God. All right, fair enough. I will chop.
是啊，就是。 哦，我的他妈的上帝。 好吧，够公平的。 我会砍。
I will do nothing, but I will chop and I will wash dishes.
我什么都不做，但我会切菜，我会洗碗。
OK, you do rice and plate up ok? OK. OK.
好的，你做米饭和盘子好吗？ 好的。 好的。
I will play and do and do rice. As a rule.
我会玩，做，做米饭。 作为一项规则。
As a rule, never go the wrong way on the conveyor belt.
作为一项规则，永远不要在传送带上走错路。
That way, we'll stay out of each other's way, ok? OK. OK.
这样一来，我们就不会妨碍彼此了，好吗？ 好的。 好的。
I will also grab you rice for your fucking thing.
我也会为你他妈的东西抢你的饭。
OK? OK, we're actually going to try.
好的？ 好的，我们实际上会尝试。
Or are you going to try?
还是你要试试？
I have been trying.
我已经试了。
We have been trying. It's just hard. Yeah. Yeah.
我们一直在努力。 这很难。 是的。 是的。
This game at this game is really is really weird.
这场比赛在这场比赛中真的是真的很诡异。
OK, i think I think I.
好吧，我想我想我。
And I'll catch up with you whenever you fuck up like that. Ok?
每当你这样搞砸的时候，我都会追上你。 好的？
All right. Thanks, babe.
好的。 谢谢宝贝。
That easy you.
你那么容易。
People in your mindset ready to be done.
在你的心态中的人准备好完成。
Well done. You can drop some fucking cute.
做得好。 你可以放一些他妈的可爱。
We'll grab more rice.
我们会抓更多的米饭。
What.
什么。
Right comes to shove.
权利来了。
And now
现在
OK, that Rice's cooking got more rice from me over there.
好的，赖斯的饭菜从我那里得到了更多的米饭。
Yes, you do. Give me that. Rice is cucumber.
是的你是。 给我那个。 米饭是黄瓜。
What do I do with the cucumber?
我拿黄瓜做什么？
I will put it on some of the dishes.
我会把它放在一些盘子上。
And I'll. Put.
我会的。 放。
I don't worry about that. Don't worry about that. OK, I'll get you light.
我不担心。 别担心。 好，我给你开灯。
I'll get you the fucking.
我会得到你他妈的。
OK. OK, ok. OK. I got it.
好的。 好的好的。 好的。 我得到了它。
I'll bring in the ingredients during.
期间我会把配料带进来。
I'll get it.
我会得到它。
I'll get it. OK. I got it. I got it. I got it.
我会得到它。 好的。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。
I got it. I got it. Easy, easy, easy.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。 轻松，轻松，轻松。
Like sometimes when you release space, it just sort of like, throws it.
就像有时当你释放空间时，它有点像，抛出它。
Oh, my God. We're out of plates. Are we out of plates?
我的天啊。 我们没有盘子了。 我们没有盘子了吗？
Oh, that's my that's my bad.
哦，那是我的，那是我的坏。
My bad.
我的错。
I'll do the dishes now.
我现在去洗碗。
And more.
和更多。
Rice. You go.
米。 你去。
You come over here.
你过来。
Come over. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
过来。 哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
I said only put it back on the stove on my doing.
我说只是把它放回炉子上我做的。
Can you actually play it up like I asked you to? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
你真的可以像我要求的那样播放它吗？ 耶耶耶。
I'm doing it. I'm doing right now. I'm doing right now. I'm doing right now.
我正在做。 我现在正在做。 我现在正在做。 我现在正在做。
I think I think I did.
我想我认为我做到了。
My first order of the day
我今天的第一个订单
on the rice about burn.
关于烧焦的米饭。
Holy shit.
天啊。
This is stressful.
这是有压力的。
Boxes is so stressful.
盒子压力太大了。
We have to split up the jobs that are all right.
我们必须拆分那些没问题的工作。
Uh huh. Stop trying to take everything into your own hands.
嗯。 不要试图把一切都掌握在自己手中。
Just do what I tell you to, ok? OK, ok, ok.
照我说的做，好吗？ 好好好。
All rice on play up the dishes and serve them.
所有的米饭都在炒菜并上桌。
That's all you got to do.
这就是你所要做的。
I will wash, I will chop.
我会洗，我会剁。
I will do everything else.
我会做其他一切。
OK? OK, ok.
好的？ 好的好的。
Got the rice
拿到米饭
and chop.
并剁碎。
Yes, I'm chop this.
是的，我砍这个。
In the meantime, and.
与此同时，和。
Oh, yeah, I need I need cucumbers. Any cucumbers.
哦，是的，我需要我需要黄瓜。 任何黄瓜。
Don't worry about. Chopping.
不要担心。 切碎。
I've still chop plenty of shit.
我还有很多狗屎。
OK. Ok. OK, ok.
好的。 行。 好的好的。
The more you chop, the the more you're going to lose track of the current thing.
你砍得越多，你就越会忘记当前的事情。
We have eight. Coins.
我们有八个。 硬币。
We have aids.
我们有辅助工具。
Wait, hold up.
等等，等等。
Hold off. Wait. What happened?
等一下。 等待。 发生了什么？
What happened is you haven't been doing your jobs.
发生的事情是你没有做你的工作。
More of them.
他们更多。
Amber, hold on, hold on, hold on.
琥珀，坚持，坚持，坚持。
I don't have I don't have cucumber oh, wait.
我没有我没有黄瓜哦，等等。
No, I do have cucumber. I do have cucumber.
不，我有黄瓜。 我有黄瓜。
I've got so much fish. Boy.
我有这么多鱼。 男生。
Yeah, there you go. Good. OK, ok.
是的，给你。 好的。 好的好的。
OK. I get it. I get it now.
好的。 我得到它。 我现在明白了。
Hold on. Hold on.
坚持，稍等。 坚持，稍等。
OK. OK, ok. OK.
好的。 好的好的。 好的。
We've established. We've established the jobs.
我们已经成立。 我们已经确定了工作。
We know what to do now. Right now we can't.
我们知道现在该做什么。 现在我们不能。
OK, I can get right into it again. Right?
好的，我可以再次进入它。 对？
Easy, easy.
慢慢来。
Right
对
holy shit.
天哪。
There's so much this going gets.
这会得到很多东西。
Harder to do. This game gets harder
更难做。 这游戏对我的打击越来越大。 是的。
Ok, i'm ready this time.
好的，这次我准备好了。
We got it.
我们得到了它。
Oh, you do.
哦，你会的。
I saw I just plate and cook rice.
我看到我只是盘子煮饭。
So you cook rice on. Put rice on.
所以你煮米饭。 放米饭。
I will chop.
我会砍。
I will bring the ingredients to you.
我会把配料拿给你。
You play top and I will wash the dishes after that.
你打得好，然后我会洗碗。
All right, so we don't.
好吧，所以我们不这样做。
Get three stars.
获得三颗星。
I'm not male wife material.
我不是男配物。
So I don't listen
所以我不听不听的都是什么？
You just threw rice straight.
你直接把米饭扔了。
OK, so I'm guessing at like a high level people will just be
好的，所以我猜像一个高水平的人实际上会像定位自己可以投掷的那样。
Yeah, I saw that sheens.
是的，我看到了光泽。
Into each other's hands. That was that would be insane. All right.
交到对方手中。 那将是疯狂的。 好的。
You know, I think that's a good strategy.
你知道，我认为这是一个很好的策略。
Just throw the rice over to my side.
把米饭扔到我身边。
I'll get you the rice door. OK?
我给你送饭门。 好的？
No you see that?
不，你看到了吗？
I did you see that?
我看到了吗？
Holy shit.
天啊。
OK, and now I need it.
好的，现在我需要它。
Yup, yup, yup.
是的，是的，是的。
Yeah, I've got I've got all the ingredients for you here.
是的，我有我已经为你准备好了所有的原料。
All you got to do is chop them.
你所要做的就是把它们切碎。
All you got to do is play them up, OK?
你所要做的就是发挥他们的作用，好吗？
OK, I'm going with that.
好的，我会同意的。
OK? I need fish and chopped cucumbers.
好的？ 我需要鱼和切碎的黄瓜。
Oh, oh, yeah. I've chopped fish right here.
哦，哦，是的。 我在这里切过鱼。
I've got chopped fish, chop cucumbers.
我有切碎的鱼，切碎的黄瓜。
I got everything you need.
我得到了你需要的一切。
OK, ok, send that out.
好的，好的，发出来。
Send this one out.
把这个发出去。
Pug, ok. OK,
帕格，好的。 好的，
and I'm going to take this.
我要接受这个。
There's dirty dishes
有脏盘子
and when rice is done,
米饭做好后，
there's dirty dishes.
有脏盘子。
Babe, they've.
宝贝，他们有。
Come on.
来吧。
I'll put it over here, ok?
我把它放在这里，好吗？
And have you actually served anything yet?
你真的提供过任何东西吗？
Yeah, I have served. I have served. I got, I got. I did get that.
是的，我服务过。 我服务过。 我得到了，我得到了。 我确实明白了。
Get that one with the cucumber, ok? Yeah. Almost done.
拿那个和黄瓜的，好吗？ 是的。 快完成了。
You just need some seaweed i'll get it. I'll get.
你只需要一些海藻我会得到它。 我会得到。
I got it. Yeah, I got the seaweed for the other one.
我得到了它。 是的，我给另一个买了海藻。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
All right.
好的。
This is what that's working.
这就是它的工作原理。
Yeah, that we go out more rice.
是的，我们出去吃更多的米饭。
I mean, some more plates.
我的意思是，还有一些盘子。
We need more. Plenty of chopped fish over there.
我们需要更多。 那里有很多切碎的鱼。
Plenty of chopped fish.
大量切碎的鱼。
I've got the plate for you.
我给你拿了盘子。
Or plates.
或盘子。
More plates, more plates, more plates, more plates.
更多盘子，更多盘子，更多盘子，更多盘子。
Get the fish on it. Get the seaweed on it.
把鱼放在上面。 把海藻放在上面。
I'll put seaweed on it. Mm hmm.
我会在上面放海藻。 嗯嗯。
Next up, cucumber, cucumber, cucumber. Huh?
接下来，黄瓜，黄瓜，黄瓜。 嗯？
OK, and you put the plate in the in the sink with plate in the sink.
好的，你把盘子放在水槽里，把盘子放在水槽里。
Go get the rice going.
去拿饭吧。
Let me check the fish
让我检查一下鱼
rice on that rice on.
饭上那饭上。
That same rice.
一样的米饭。
You see.
你看。
We see when you got seaweed, you can put that in. You can see.
我们看到当你得到海藻时，你可以把它放进去。你可以看到。
We got seaweed. OK.
我们得到了海藻。 好的。
OK. I got another.
好的。 我得到了另一个。
Rice coming next fresh next, putting it.
大米下一个新鲜的下一个，把它。
On the another plate. I need another plate and another plate.
在另一个盘子上。 我需要另一个盘子和另一个盘子。
OK, I'll get it on the plate.
好的，我会把它放在盘子里。
All the plates are dirty.
所有的盘子都脏了。 所有的盘子都脏了。
I'm going to wash it.
我要洗它。
I thought I'm talking about
我以为我在谈论
fish, though.
鱼，虽然。
Listen to the timer. We're doing fine now.
听计时器。 我们现在做得很好。
We're doing great. We're doing great. We're doing great.
我们做得很好。 我们做得很好。 我们做得很好。
And I have time for another rice.
我有时间再来一份米饭。
And to put it in.
并把它放进去。
For really
因为真的很糟糕。 好的。
I'll fuck.
我会他妈的。
I'll do it.
我会做的。
I know you got it.
我知道你明白了。
You got it. You got to play that shit right now.
你说对了。 你现在必须玩那个狗屎。
Yeah, I got it. I got it.
是的，我明白了。 我得到了它。
I got it.
我得到了它。
OK, I fish fresh fish, fresh fish, fresh fish.
好的，我钓新鲜的鱼，新鲜的鱼，新鲜的鱼。
Diamonds are my fish. No.
钻石是我的鱼。 不。
Oh. Oh, my God. I think we did it, though.
哦。 我的天啊。 不过，我认为我们做到了。
I think we did it all.
我想我们都做到了。
We get. Our lives.
我们得到。 我们的生命。
My boy.
我的孩子。
Oh, my god. Oh, yeah.
我的天啊。 哦耶。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
哦，是的，是的。
Well done.
做得好。
Well, fucking John was good.
好吧，他妈的约翰很好。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, right.
啊对。
That actually felt.
确实有这种感觉。
Really good to finally. Get it.
真的好到最后。 得到它。
That's it.
这就对了。
I think the key.
我认为关键。
The key is looking for the specific recipes that are on the left, you know?
关键是寻找左边的特定食谱，你知道吗？
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
Oh, God. Down
天啊。 向下
all right,
好的，
so we got all hands on.
所以我们全力以赴。
Oh, well done. Three stars. I'm proud of us.
哦，干得好。 三颗星。 我为我们感到骄傲。
That's next.
那是下一个。
Way. Where the fuck are we going now?
方式。 我们他妈现在要去哪里？
Is that an air balloon? I believe we are.
那是气球吗？ 我相信我们是。
We're on. OK, this is really going have some weird physics.
我们在。 好的，这真的会有一些奇怪的物理学。
Huh? Physics?
嗯？ 物理？
Yeah.
是的。
This is this is really going to be a moving kitchen.
这真的是一个移动的厨房。
New recipe, possible pasta,
新食谱，可能的意大利面，
add chopped tomato meat and mushroom or fish and prawns.
加入切碎的番茄肉和蘑菇或鱼和虾。
So basically, we pay attention to the recipe on the top left.
所以基本上，我们注意左上角的食谱。
And I like before I will do the chopping.
我喜欢在我切菜之前。
You cook faster and plates up and I will do garnishes.
你煮得更快，上菜，我会做配菜。
OK? OK.
好的？ 好的。
Oh, actually, I don't think we have a choice,
哦，实际上，我认为我们别无选择，所以会上下波动。
All right, so give me my ingredients, OK?
好吧，把我的原料给我，好吗？
Actually, now I can get them like you have.
事实上，现在我可以像你一样得到它们了。
Can I just grab it?
我可以抓住它吗？
I'm cooking pasta I'm cooking pasta.
我在做意大利面 我在做意大利面。
It's not going.
它不会去。
And I move.
而我移动。
We have salts.
我们有盐。
As long as on this.
只要就这点。
This is this. Oh, no, no.
这是这个。 哦，不，不。
All right. Oh, no. That's all on my side.
好的。 不好了。 这一切都在我身边。
Let me get you pasta.
让我给你拿意大利面。 让我给你拿意大利面。
Well.
好。
There you go.
你去吧。
It's got some cooked tomato all on. Hold on, hold on.
它有一些煮熟的番茄。 等一下，等一下。
Take these off of the burner. OK? OK, that one's ready. That one's. Ready.
把这些从燃烧器上拿下来。 好的？ 好的，那个已经准备好了。 那个。 准备好。
Yeah, that one's.
对，就是那个。
That one's already. Let me. Let me grab that.
那个已经 让我来。 让我抓住那个。
All right.
好的。
I played on my past. I played with lots.
我玩的是我的过去。 我玩了很多。
More pork.
更多的猪肉。
Chops. Tomatoes.
排骨。 番茄。
Nice. OK,
好的。 好的，
I'll I guess I'll chop this.
我会 我想我会砍这个。
I'll know I'm stuck step row.
我会知道我被卡住了。
I got.
我有。
I got OK.
我没问题。
That's that's another dish done.
那是另一道菜做好了。
I got the dishes.
我拿了菜。
I mean, wash those fuckers
我的意思是，洗那些混蛋是的。 所有的意大利面都准备好了。 一切。
I'm working. We're working. Working together. Yeah. Yeah.
我在工作。 我们正在工作。 一起工作。 是的。 是的。
Great. We're doing great, baby shit.
伟大的。 我们做得很好，宝贝。
All of that.
所有的。
We have established our synergy is on.
我们已经确定了我们的协同作用。
That's amazing.
这是惊人的。
The point.
重点。
Oh. Oh, shit. Wait, there's more dirty plates here, honey.
哦。 妈的。 等等，这里有更多脏盘子，亲爱的。
You do the dirty plates.
你做脏盘子。
Yeah. Good boy. Good boy.
是的。 好孩子。 好孩子。
Yeah, good boy.
是的，好孩子。
Of course.
当然。
Shut up.
住口。
There we go.
我们去吧。
That's that plate. Not up. There we go.
就是那个盘子。 不起来。 我们去吧。
There we go. House is ready.
我们去吧。 房子准备好了。
Pops is ready to pass. Are already. Stuff. Good stuff. Good stuff.
流行音乐准备通过。 已经。 东西。 好东西。 好东西。
OK, I'm putting these back on the on the stove.
好的，我要把这些放回炉子上。
We'll grab more.
我们会抓住更多。
You can send those out.
你可以把那些寄出去。
It's on your side. It's on your side.
它就在你身边。 它就在你身边。
You do what you do, OK? Yeah.
你做你该做的，好吗？ 是的。
And I'm actually fucking all the
而我实际上是他妈的所有
fuck. Yeah. There you go.
他妈的。 是的。 你去吧。
I'll grab this myself. OK?
我会自己抓住这个。 好的？
OK. All right.
好的。 好的。
This is going fine. This is going. Really well done. Great.
这一切顺利。 这正在发生。 真的做得很好。 伟大的。
Virginia pug in here blogging.
弗吉尼亚哈巴狗在这里写博客。
I'm going to I'm going to wash the plates now.
我要去我现在要去洗盘子了。
All right? And we go.
好的？ 我们走了。
And, you know, plates here are the plates.
而且，你知道，这里的盘子就是盘子。
On that, like passed on.
在那，就像过去一样。
Like a lot of these moving around.
就像很多这样的人四处走动。
But that's another dish done.
但那是另一道菜了。
You can you can send out you can send out.
你可以你可以发送你可以发送。
You know, when it's just two ingredients.
你知道，当它只有两种成分时。
It's feel so relaxing.
感觉很放松。
So relaxing.
如此放松。
But then when we get like third.
但是当我们获得第三名时。
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. Let me.
哦，狗屎，狗屎，狗屎，狗屎，狗屎。 让我来。
Plates, plates, plates.
盘子，盘子，盘子。
Yeah, that's it. That's that plates. I was I was wondering.
是的，就是这样。 就是那个盘子。 我在想。
All right.
好的。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Following us around. All shiny. It's on. Right.
跟着我们走。 都闪闪发光。 它开着。 对。
There we go.
我们去吧。
I'm going to show. The champion.
我要展示。 冠军。
Lots more it to that girl.
对那个女孩来说更多。
That's and that's in the middle.
那是，那是在中间。
I think you just going differently.
我认为你只是走不同的路。
OK, I'll fuck.
好吧，我会他妈的。
Can we grab the
我们可以抓住
I'm the grab another plate and then we can we put the.
我是抢另一个盘子然后我们就可以放了。
The box we go input, input.
我们去输入框，输入。
Input and you're OK on the far down, but.
输入，你就可以了，但是。
Oh. OK.
哦。 好的。
All right, this is ready.
好的，这已经准备好了。
This is ready. We need a new plate.
这准备好了。 我们需要一个新盘子。
Just combine the two, combine the two. You like that?
只需将两者结合起来，将两者结合起来。 你喜欢？
OK, send it out.
好的，发出来。
Send that baby. Up. Easy, easy, then that baby out.
送那个宝贝 向上。 轻松，轻松，然后那个宝贝出来。
The past is coming up plus is coming up here. Yo,
过去来了，加上这里来了。 哟，
that one's ready as well. Let me send that.
那个也准备好了。 让我发送那个。
I need any pasta. Any pasta? Yeah, we go.
我需要任何意大利面。 有意大利面吗？ 是的，我们去。
Pasta. Pasta coming up.
意大利面。 面食上来。
I'm going to check.
我要检查一下。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
That he got me to put that there.
他让我把那个放在那里。
Oh, we were out of time. You're right. It's time.
哦，我们没时间了。 你说的对。 是时候了。
No box full. Three, three.
没有满箱。 三，三。
That might be enough.
这可能就足够了。 这可能就足够了。
Oh, yeah. That's more than enough.
哦耶。 这绰绰有余。
Oh, my God. Holy shit. What Paul going?
我的天啊。 天啊。 什么保罗去？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Shooting my boy with y'all.
和你们一起射杀我的孩子。
Take Chick taken the. Culinary world by home.
拿小鸡拿了。 家的美食世界。
Yes. Chef him.
是的。 厨师他。
Asthma.
哮喘。
It's like when Gordon Ramsay calls you a fucking bastard in the first 5 minutes.
就像戈登拉姆齐在前 5 分钟内称你为该死的混蛋一样。
Within, like, an hour later, he's like, oh, you sweet boy, you sweet baby voice.
在，就像，一个小时后，他就像，哦，你这个可爱的男孩，你甜美的婴儿声音。
What he say if that one line.
他说的话如果那一行。
Are you are you projecting at all?
你在投射吗？
No, I'm not projecting. I'm not projecting.
不，我不是在投射。 我不是在投射。
I'm just saying it's like.
我只是说它就像。
A sweet baby boy. No, don't call me as if you will.
一个可爱的男婴。 不，不要像你会的那样打电话给我。
I'll fucking bite your hand off, you bitch.
我会他妈的咬掉你的手，你这个婊子。
Do you want me to just rest rest your head on my lap and play
你想让我把头靠在我的腿上，玩弄空气，然后告诉我，告诉你一切都会好起来的。
Maybe
也许
that's a pretty something offer.
这是一个相当不错的提议。
I'll go.
我要走了。
I keep talking like that and then you'll know.
我一直这样说，然后你就会知道。
It's all right. Gorgeous.
没关系，还不错。 华丽的。
Don't worry about it.
不用担心。
Maybe I'll. Maybe I'll give you another.
也许我会的。 也许我会给你另一个。
Oh, my. He's going to caramelise me.
天啊。 他要把我焦糖化。
Yeah.
是的。
All right, let's get back to.
好吧，让我们回到过去。
Back to basics. Salad.
回归本源。 沙拉。
All right, I'm back to so, so so I will chop you playing, ok? OK.
好吧，我又回来了，所以我会砍你玩，好吗？ 好的。
Actually, yes.
其实，是。
OK. But
好的。 但
what is the why is there a fire?
发生火灾的原因是什么？
What the hell?
我勒个去？
Right.
对。
OK, so I guess that's the hazard for this one.
好的，所以我想这就是这个的危险。
I so you all right?
我这样你还好吗？
So I will do chopping you can be on, you can plates up.
所以我会切你可以上，你可以盘起来。
But also, if you could
但是，如果你能
fire extinguisher where possible.
尽可能使用灭火器。
There's no fire extinguishers.
没有灭火器。
Oh, so we just have to avoid something.
哦，所以我们只需要避免一些事情。
I think we just had to avoid it.
我想我们只能避免它。
What the fuck.
什么鬼。
Does.
做。
Yeah.
是的。
We just got to stay away from the fire.
我们只需要远离火源。
What the hell?
我勒个去？
This is such a new. Lettuce and tomato.
这是一个新事物。 生菜和番茄。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Let me tomatoes on millions of meals on the plate already.
让我在盘子里上百万餐的西红柿。
Say I was on the plane already.
说我已经在飞机上了。
You know, let us know what it say.
你知道，让我们知道它在说什么。
Let's see who cooks in these conditions.
让我们看看谁在这些条件下做饭。
We do bad. What? We're built fucking.
我们做坏事。 什么？ 我们是他妈的。
Different kind of restaurant.
不一样的餐厅。
OK, I'm going to wash the plates. Oh, my God.
好的，我要去洗盘子了。 我的天啊。
Tomato, tomatoes. Ready?
西红柿，西红柿。 准备好？
Is it tomato? That's ready.
是番茄吗？ 那准备好了。
Wasn't wet.
没湿。
It's not ready. But all right.
它还没有准备好。 不过没关系。
Alia, it's ready to be shot.
Alia，它已经准备好被拍摄了。
I would say.
我会说。
Yes. Or all right. It's that.
是的。 或者没关系。 就是它。
There's that that there's just not just.
不仅如此。
The lettuce on the floor.
地上的生菜。
Obviously.
明显地。
You have that still good.
你有那个还是不错的。
Still good.
还好。
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
Let me just play that up. Send it out.
让我玩一下。 发送出去。
Move them.
移动它们。
OK, I'm going to chop up the cucumber perfect.
好的，我要把黄瓜切碎。
Perfect. Play that up. Play that up. Yeah, yeah.
完美的。 玩那个。 玩那个。 是啊是啊。
Easy move up.
轻松向上移动。
Fuck!
他妈的！
Oh, my God. Dude, the fire is such a clock.
我的天啊。 伙计，火就是这样一个时钟。
Wait a second.
等一下。
Send it. Send all. Your hash.
发送。 全部发送。 你的哈希。
La la
啦啦而已。 天哪，还有一个。
There's a oh, my goodness. I'm going to grab it.
有一个哦，我的天哪。 我要抓住它。
I'm going to grab the the lettuce.
我要去拿生菜了。
Grab the lettuce. Oh, wait.
抓住生菜。 等一下。
We need more plates.
我们需要更多的盘子。
Fuck me. Oh, please, please, please, please.
操我。 哦，请，请，请，请，请。
Whoa.
哇。
Hop oh.
跳哦。
All right. We landed with my line.
好的。 我们降落在我的线路上。
We've landed.
我们降落了。
That's crazy.
这很疯狂。
All working. Sushi away.
都在工作。 寿司走了。
This conveyor belts right with four.
这条传送带正好有四个。
Oh, my God. All right.
我的天啊。 好的。
Oh, my. God. Let's.
天啊。 上帝。 让我们。
It's cucumber fucking.
这是黄瓜他妈的。
But some of that shit, some of that whole ennui.
但有些狗屎，有些完全厌倦。
I had to get the rice going out to get the rice going right now.
我必须把大米拿出来才能让大米马上去。
Yeah, you handle. You handle the salad right now. I'm going.
是的，你处理。 你现在处理沙拉。 我要去。
I'm going to cut rice.
我要切米饭。
We are just getting my controls reversed.
我们只是让我的控制反转。
I can't stop going on.
我无法停止继续。
But your. Control servers, we all have when.
但是你的。 控制服务器，我们都有什么时候。
Literally I'm stuck in the awkward position that way, OK?
从字面上看，我就这样陷入了尴尬的境地，好吗？
I was I was going to be like, I got it.
我是我会喜欢的，我明白了。
I think I think it bugged out.
我想我认为它出故障了。
I got to get the. Rice to get. Off.
我必须得到。 大米得到。 离开。
Right. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. OK, thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
对。 对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起，对不起。 好的谢谢。 谢谢你。 谢谢你。
I'm going to plate one of them.
我要镀其中一个。
All right.
好的。
Now, just to prepare it. Let's try.
现在，只是为了准备它。 咱们试试吧。
So if we can get some cucumber, that'll be great.
所以如果我们能得到一些黄瓜，那就太好了。
Easier.
更轻松。
Where is the cucumber?
黄瓜在哪里？
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Oh, it's the fucking tomato.
哦，这该死的西红柿。
Was covering the cucumber.
正在覆盖黄瓜。
There it is.
它在那里。
All right.
好的。
I was confused, I There we go.
我很困惑，我走了。
It's going to be OK.
一切都会好的。
I'm going to send out this roll right now.
我现在要发出这个卷。
I got some rice for you.
我给你买了一些米饭。
I'm going to wash the dishes.
我要去洗碗了。
Salad means you mean cucumber?
沙拉的意思是你的意思是黄瓜？
Cucumber for the salad.
沙拉用黄瓜。
It's about to go bad.
它即将变坏。
Come on, come on.
好啦好啦。
Come on, pick it up. There we go.
来吧，捡起来。 我们去吧。
It's doable.
这是可行的。
So not there.
所以不在那里。
We got lettuce and the another cucumber.
我们得到了生菜和另一个黄瓜。
Another cucumber,
另一个黄瓜，
other rice.
其他米饭。
I'm going get the rising and grab the rice.
我要起床，抓饭。
That rice is ready now.
饭已经做好了。
He needs cucumber for that.
为此他需要黄瓜。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We need to make it. Yeah, we need fish, too.
我们需要做到。 是的，我们也需要鱼。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
Yeah, yeah, it's on the conveyor belt is going to have us.
是的，是的，它在传送带上将有我们。
Oh, no, we're out of beer.
哦，不，我们没有啤酒了。
Out of plates. Right. A plates on. Oh, shit.
没盘子。 对。 上一个盘子。 妈的。
I mean, yeah, he's going to wash it as a plate of hair.
我的意思是，是的，他会把它当作一盘头发洗。
And of course, the acts of that.
当然，还有那些行为。
The rice is not looking so good. Yeah, none of this is.
米饭看起来不太好。 是的，这些都不是。
We can't serve any of this, like, until the whole time runs out.
在整个时间用完之前，我们不能提供任何这些。
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
Who we got.
我们得到了谁。
We got 600, dude.
我们得到了600，伙计。
We did great.
我们做得很好。
We did so good. That was insane, man.
我们做得很好。 那太疯狂了，伙计。
My God, dude, what's going on?
我的天，哥们，这是怎么回事？
Like, our synergy, like, one up by hogging some, like, a 100,000
就像，我们的协同作用，就像，一个通过占用一些，像，一个100,000个圣棚合作伙伴那里。
The onion man. He's so proud of us.
洋葱人。 他为我们感到骄傲。
Shit him bamboozled on. Yeah,
妈的，他被蒙骗了。 是的，
he's very happy
他很高兴他的眉毛我没有表现力，但他的尾巴有。
Are you unhappy don't.
你不开心吗？
You I'll know I lot you come over here and
你我会知道我很多你过来这里
my head will
我的头会
please oh.
请哦。
What was your boy.
什么是你的男孩。
Good boy good boy You happy boy
好孩子 好孩子 你快乐的孩子
goddammit.
可恶。
Stop, stop it.
停，停。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I'm trying to not you you keep making me do these things, OK?
我试图不让你一直让我做这些事情，好吗？
And then.
进而。
And then people keep thinking I'm a dog.
然后人们一直认为我是一条狗。
I'm not human.
我不是人类。
It's bad.
这是坏的。
It's so bad I'm going to get I'm going to get you
这太糟糕了，我要得到我要得到你
get my dog.
得到我的狗。
It's hard. It's hard. It's heart wrenching.
很难。 这个很难（硬。 这令人心碎。
You've only just begun.
你才刚刚开始。
There's still much to learn about cooperation.
关于合作还有很多东西要学。
We can only keep you on bread back so long and out into the wild country.
我们只能让你吃面包这么久，然后到野外去。
I hear there are flavours that I can say shake
我听说有些味道我可以说摇
back.
背部。
I sure don't hurry me.
我当然不催我。
But he's right.
但他是对的。
Let's go now.
现在走吧。
Bring back more delicious teen wild
带回更美味的青少年狂野
delicious teamwork.
美味的团队合作。
Teamwork.
团队合作。
There's no time.
没有时间了。
To lose.
失去。
Anyways.
无论如何。
We did really good.
我们做得非常好。
Good.
好的。
We struggled like during the mids middle portion.
我们像在中段一样挣扎。
But then we like, you know.
但是我们喜欢，你知道的。
We learn we learn to collaborate. Yeah.
我们学会了学习合作。 是的。
And to collaborate.
并进行合作。
We learn to collaborate.
我们学会合作。
Or is this place going to the waters?
还是这个地方要下水？
Was that one from earlier this?
是之前那个吗？
You really wanted something good? Woo!
你真的想要好东西吗？ 哇！
I think we should try that again. I think we've been doing a lot better.
我认为我们应该再试一次。 我认为我们已经做得更好了。
I think we've been doing a lot better since.
我认为从那以后我们已经做得更好了。
We got the lowdown down.
我们得到了内幕。
People. And, like, this is.
人们。 而且，就像，这是。
Honestly, like, it's still stressful as hell,
老实说，就像，它仍然是地狱般的压力，
but is it, like, harder when there's more people, like,
但是，当人越多时，它是否会变得更难，例如，如果人越多，游戏就会变得越难。
I don't honestly, I don't remember.
我不老实说，我不记得了。
I think I played it with
我想我以前为人们玩过它，但我不知道它有多热。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Steam's right.
蒸汽是对的。
OK, so remember you your job is to steam.
好的，所以记住你的工作是蒸汽。
My job is to do the boiling.
我的工作是煮沸。
So if you put the bowls in the middle so I can use the bowls
所以如果你把碗放在中间我可以用碗
and then once you steam together you do the thing.
然后，一旦你一起蒸汽，你就会做这件事。
So and then we've got to pay attention to the oil.
因此，我们必须注意石油。
Yeah, I gotcha. I gotcha.
是的，我明白了。 我明白了。
All right.
好的。
Meat and flour.
肉和面粉。
That's all we got to do.
这就是我们要做的。
Youngest. And I'm going.
最年轻的。 我要去。
Put the fish over here.
把鱼放这里。
Put some flour right here
在你有面粉的地方放一些面粉。
You've got chopping boards on your size as well. So don't don't go.
你也有适合你尺寸的砧板。 所以不要不要去。
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's true. That's true.
哦耶。 是的，这是真的。 那是真实的。
That's true.
那是真实的。
Give me that shit.
把那个狗屎给我。
Also, I need one more flour.
另外，我还需要一种面粉。
Hold on, hold on.
等一下，等一下。
Then I send it over and suckin is your flour yes.
然后我把它寄过去，吸你的面粉是的。
You're going to steamed.
你要蒸了。
I'm going to steam the fish first.
我先把鱼蒸一下。
I got some to go. Some steam ship for you.
我有一些要走。 一些蒸汽船给你。
There you go. Make sure to give me the ball back when you're done. Yeah,
你去吧。 完成后一定要把球还给我。 是的，
I'm steaming fish first, though, so once that's good.
不过，我先蒸鱼，所以一次就很好。
You go. Right, I'll send more flour.
你去。 对了，我再送点面粉。
I'm just some more flour over because I think you need more flour.
我只是多了一些面粉，因为我认为你需要更多的面粉。
I we do.
我我们做。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
We grab the fish, I'm playing the fish and we'll put your report.
我们抓鱼，我在玩鱼，我们会放你的报告。
Can you give me the bowls back? Yeah, yeah.
你能把碗还给我吗？ 是啊是啊。
Hold on. I just got a gas.
坚持，稍等。 我刚打了气。
Send these orders out
发送这些订单
OK? These guys on side here.
好的？ 这些家伙在这里。
Here's your bowl. The bulls are good. Bulls. Good.
这是你的碗。 公牛很好。 公牛队。 好的。
Thank you. Both are all good.
谢谢你。 两者都很好。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
OK, here's your bowl.
好的，这是你的碗。
You need more flour?
你需要更多的面粉吗？
I think you need more flour. I know. I've got no flour for now.
我想你需要更多的面粉。 我知道。 我暂时没有面粉。
OK. OK, here's your dishes.
好的。 好的，这是你的菜。
I need dirty, dirty dishes. Dirty dishes are good. You
我需要又脏又脏的盘子。 脏盘子很好吃。 你
dirty dishes.
脏盘子。
OK, that's ready.
好的，准备好了。
Ooh, you go.
哦，你去吧。
Yeah. All right.
是的。 好的。
Ball, ball on your side.
球，球在你身边。
Get ready for it.
为它做好准备。
Two balls of meats ready.
准备好两个肉丸。
To order is out already.
已经下单了。
All right, good. I'm going to do another dish.
好吧，很好。 我要再做一道菜。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Put these in and put this in.
把这些放进去，把它放进去。
Here's your bowl, doc. Thank you very much.
这是你的碗，博士。 非常感谢你。
And this can go until there's another bowl back.
这可以持续到有另一个碗回来。
I go, I get some fish going.
我去，我去钓些鱼。
I'm going to.
我要去。
Get a formal. Flour.
来个正式的。 面粉。
Yeah, there's.
是的，有。
Yeah, there you go.
是的，给你。
I'm going to set to flour.
我要设置面粉。
Is up, like, right here on this.
起来了，就像，就在这里。
And dirty dishes. Three dishes.
还有脏盘子。 三道菜。
So that was a burn.
所以那是烧伤。
Yeah. These two are good. I'm going to.
是的。 这两个都不错。 我要去。
I'm going to send these out he's up
我要把这些寄出去，他起来了
and then
进而
I think I can just sit it out.
我想我可以坐下来。
Yeah. And I prioritise the fish.
是的。 我优先考虑鱼。
The fish are mommy. Mommy. All right, all right, fish.
鱼是妈妈。 妈妈。 好吧，好吧，鱼。
That's fine.
没事儿。
The fun is always choice.
乐趣总是选择。
First I'll do the dishes.
首先我会洗碗。
I am, I have my job.
我是，我有我的工作。
I can't,
我不能，
I don't really have a job for a little bit, but just make sure you also
我真的没有一点工作，但只要确保你也做其中之一，然后你应该会很好。
Yeah, clean the plates in the meantime. Very young.
是的，在此期间清洁盘子。 很年轻。
Lady. More plates.
女士。 更多的盘子。
Well. Nice.
好。 好的。
OK, and then you go more flour.
好的，然后你再去面粉。
And you go. And say, good.
你走了。 并说，好。
Oof! OK.
钱币！ 好的。
A bowls back, please.
请回一碗。
Yeah, yeah, I'm about to send that in on block
是的，是的，我正要在块中发送它
here.
这里。
Go for bowls.
去买碗。
Good bowls. Good. Well, that will happen to the onion king.
好碗。 好的。 好吧，这将发生在洋葱王身上。
Just give me a little bit stimulation.
给我一点刺激。
Yeah, I don't know. I just. I got stuck.
是的，我不知道。 我只是。 我被困。
That's stuck, bro.
卡住了，兄弟。
Stop up.
堵。
Plate. That's it.
盘子。 这就对了。
Now you got it with some fish order.
现在你得到了一些鱼订单。
Yeah. One that's ready to go.
是的。 一个准备好了。
I just need more plates. Here you go. Here's 30 plates.
我只是需要更多的盘子。 干得好。 这里有 30 个盘子。
I may get some more fish ready.
我可能会准备更多的鱼。
I'm going to give you another flour.
我要再给你一个面粉。
Actually, I think you need more flour.
事实上，我认为你需要更多的面粉。
Yeah, this would be good. Yeah.
是的，这会很好。 是的。
OK. Bowls back on the dinner plate ASAP.
好的。 碗尽快放回餐盘上。
There we go.
我们去吧。
There's more flour. Are
还有更多的面粉。 是
when we got that music speeding up?
当我们让音乐加速时？
It's is going faster and faster. Going fast.
它正在变得越来越快。 走得很快。
All right, I've got to play for you.
好吧，我必须为你演奏。
Make sure you play some of these.
确保你玩其中的一些。
Something's right away, guys.
伙计们，马上就有事情了。
I'm guessing it's about a.
我猜它大约是一个。
Serve it to serve it.
为它服务。
Something's going bad.
有什么不好的。
Something's going back to
有什么事情要回来了
where. Almost wants to get three stars.
在哪里。 差点想打三颗星。
If you want more. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I can't.
如果你想要更多。 我的天啊。 我的天啊。 我不能。
I don't have enough time.
我没有足够的时间。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Fuck. Oh, we're literally 15 seconds.
他妈的。 哦，我们实际上是 15 秒。
My God. Let's do that again. Yeah, I think.
我的上帝。 让我们再做一次。 是的，我想。
I think we got it this time. We got this time.
我想这次我们明白了。 我们得到了这个时间。
We had a good run. Yeah, yeah. OK.
我们跑得很好。 是啊是啊。 好的。
Oh. Damn him.
哦。 该死的他。
In a little.
一点点。
They called me. They called me the chef.
他们打电话给我。 他们叫我厨师。
They called me too. Shit.
他们也给我打电话。 拉屎。
Because I fucking fucking.
因为我他妈的他妈的。
Bother, chef.
麻烦大厨
Oh, hold on.
哦，等一下。
Matsu. The universe.
马祖。 宇宙。
Thank you guys.
谢谢你们。
So much for all the gifts, subs holy shit.
这么多的礼物，潜艇圣洁的狗屎。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You good?
你好吗？
Yeah, I'm good. So is someone just. People are.
是的，我很好。 一个人也一样。 人们是。
There's a lot of gift subs going on right now, so.
现在有很多礼物潜艇，所以。
Say some. Income for you guys. Asians.
说几句。 给你们带来收入。 亚洲人。
That's OK.
那没问题。
All right.
好的。
Same rules as last time. We're good. OK.
和上次一样的规则。 我们很好。 好的。
Yeah, we got it. We got it.
是的，我们明白了。 我们得到了它。
I just make sure to be a little quicker on the fish.
我只是确保在鱼上快一点。
We should be fine. Yeah, the fish is also really important.
我们应该没事。 是的，鱼也很重要。
I'm going to just throw flour immediately towards you.
我要立即朝你扔面粉。
Since that's. Important. Go there.
既然如此。 重要的。 去那里。
And I'm going to get.
我会得到。
I'm going to get some fish chops.
我要去买些鱼排。
I feel like I get pretty up these fish, so.
我觉得我把这些鱼弄得很漂亮，所以。
Yeah, yeah, I know that is a good idea when they know when you don't have
是的，是的，我知道当他们知道您没有其他事情可做时，这是个好主意。
You could do with getting some fish tied right away.
你可以马上绑一些鱼。
Yeah, I'm putting them in a sub right now
是的，我现在把它们放在一个潜艇里
in the chop.
在印章中。
More fish do you need more flour?
更多的鱼你需要更多的面粉吗？
I think you do. I know I'm all good for flour right now.
我想你会的。 我知道我现在很适合面粉。
I just set it up to set it up.
我只是设置它来设置它。
Yeah. One more flour.
是的。 再来一粒面粉。
Yep. Hmm.
是的。 唔。
Yeah.
是的。
All Wait. I think I got a system whole long way.
等等。 我想我有一个很长的系统。
I just put it on the plate and then take this and your bowls.
我只是把它放在盘子上，然后把这个和你的碗拿走。
I don't even need to grab the bowls.
我什至不需要拿起碗。
Oh, share.
哦，分享。
That's helpful.
这很有帮助。
Yeah. OK, dude, women maxing.
是的。 好的，伙计，女性最大化。
Literally mean. Man.
字面意思。 男人。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, no. It's ok. It's ok. It's ok.
不好了。 没关系。 没关系。 没关系。
I don't need a mining.
我不需要采矿。
Dominic, give me. Give me some more flour.
多米尼克，给我。 再给我一些面粉。
Yeah, hold on. I'll give you that.
是的，等等。 我会给你那个。
There you go.
你去吧。
Yeah, I accidentally put the fish in with the meat and stuff.
是的，我不小心把鱼和肉和其他东西一起放进去了。
I didn't know you could do that.
我不知道你能做到这一点。
All right, well, now you go. Now, now, now.
好吧，好吧，现在你走了。 现在，现在，现在。
You know, now. Yeah.
你知道，现在。 是的。
OK, double's clean. Ready? To go.
好的，双子很干净。 准备好？ 去。
You go now.
你现在走。
The ball. Boy.
球。 男生。
Yeah, I'm going send dirty dishes. Dirty dishes,
是的，我要送脏盘子。 脏盘子，
OK, you're not really.
好吧，你不是真的。
Ready. Let me do the dishes.
准备好。 让我洗碗。
And this is good to go.
这很好。
Another
其他
this is also good to go.
这也很好。
Yeah. I just need more places.
是的。 我只是需要更多的地方。
You more dirty plates.
你更脏的盘子。
Send this out
发这个
uh, bowl is your bowl.
呃，碗是你的碗。
Slightly.
轻微地。
I need some more flour.
我需要更多的面粉。
OK, what you that.
好吧，你说什么。
Please.
请。
Oh. It's already play it up.
哦。 已经在玩了。
Oh, yeah, it is. It is.
哦，是的，是的。 这是。
It is right here.
它就在这里。
Yeah,
是的，
these these are good to go
当我为我寄出这些时，这些很好，这是盘子。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
This is going to work. Is going to work.
这将起作用。 要去上班了。
Sorry. It's focussed on fish a little bit.
对不起。 它有点专注于鱼。
Make sure you get that fish done.
确保你完成了那条鱼。
I'll do the dishes OK?
我会洗碗好吗？
OK. Yeah, I have two fish going right now on this and some flour over a
好的。 是的，我现在有两条鱼和一些面粉
ah. And I need to give you more dirty dishes right there.
啊。 我需要给你更多的脏盘子。
There you go.
你去吧。
OK, I'll plate the salt and your bowls.
好的，我会把盐和你的碗盘起来。
Ready. Your bowl is ready whenever you are.
准备好。 您的碗随时准备就绪。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
All right, let me grab the bowl of.
好吧，让我去拿碗。
Both bowls already.
已经两碗了。
Both of them are cooking.
两个人都在做饭。
And there you go.
你去吧。
There we go.
我们去吧。
These are good.
这些都很好。
There we go. We're getting mad points. Mad point.
我们去吧。 我们得到了疯狂的分数。 疯点。
I need another plate.
我需要另一个盘子。
Any another plate? Soon
有别的盘子吗？ 很快
yeah. Got to play for you.
是的。 必须为你演奏。
They got he'll grab that.
他们得到了他会抓住那个。
I'll send that out.
我会把它发出去。
Aesop dirty dishes, three dishes.
伊索脏盘，三盘。
I need another dish whenever you can.
只要有可能，我就需要另一道菜。
One sec.
1秒。
I mean, before you
我的意思是，在你之前
play it up.
发挥它。
Yeah, I'm going to send the salt dirty dish
是啊，我要送盐脏盘子
cook. I'm the cook. The fish.
厨师。 我是厨师。 鱼。
Yeah, we go.
是的，我们去。
OK, I'm go cook your thing, like, right now, since I think that's a good point.
好的，我要去煮你的东西，就像，现在，因为我认为这是一个好点。
Good idea. We are really fucking close.
好主意。 我们真的很亲密。
Here's your plates.
这是你的盘子。
Thank you. Is another plate for you.
谢谢你。 是给你的另一个盘子。
I've got some more.
我还有一些。
I've got another dish right here.
我这里还有一道菜。
That's.
那是。
You can serve. That's a fish. Special fish.
你可以服务。 那是一条鱼。 特产鱼。
Yeah.
是的。
I fish an entire plate in, you know, a plate.
我把整个盘子都捞了进去，你知道的，一个盘子。
Got one.
拿到一个。
Well, it's not something that's on.
好吧，它不是正在播放的东西。
It's not on. Oh, my God. It's almost done. It's almost done.
它没有打开。 我的天啊。 快完成了。 快完成了。
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
I think you're doing, you know, you're not, so.
我认为你在做，你知道，你不是，所以。
Wow. Oh,
哇。 哦，
yeah.
是的。
He is very down to the last second.
他到了最后一秒。
Oh, my God. I can't boy.
我的天啊。 我不能男孩。
Holy shit. VOCs.
天啊。 挥发性有机化合物。
Holy shit.
天啊。
One. Oh.
一。 哦。
Sealed
密封
fucking parking.
他妈的停车。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
All I've got that's overcooked.
我所得到的只是煮过头了。
Please, God, the plan in
拜托，上帝，计划在
God's name.
上帝的名字。
OK, where's the limestones?
好的，石灰石在哪里？
Sam, that's so good.
山姆，太好了。
I was actually. I feel something like that.
我其实是。 我有这样的感觉。
Oh, I might. I say.
哦，我可能会。 我说。
All right, let's see if we can exert. Yeah, we can.
好吧，让我们看看我们是否可以发挥作用。 是的，我们可以。
We can leave. We can leave.
我们可以离开了。 我们可以离开了。
Can we
我们可以吗
I don't know if that will be, like, the whole.
我不知道这是否会是整体。
Oh, yeah. No, it's.
哦耶。 不，它是。
Is this Kevin one?
这是凯文吗？
Yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
There we go.
我们去吧。
All right. Nice.
好的。 好的。
Oh, God damn. We did it.
哦，该死的。 我们做到了。
Oh, collaboration.
哦，合作。
Three stars.
三颗星。
All around.
在周围。
You just run somebody over again.
你只是再次撞倒某人。
Always on. I'll run you over.
始终开启。 我会把你碾过去。
I will. Yeah.
我会。 是的。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Vox He keeps saying you're going to do these things, but then you never.
Vox 他一直说你会做这些事情，但你永远不会。
You never come through with it.
你从来没有经历过它。
I don't know if you can handle them.
我不知道你能不能处理它们。
You always you. Know. That's how I know.
你永远是你。 知道。 我就是这样知道的。
But no. No, if you really, you.
但不是。 不，如果你真的，你。
Know, it's, you know, they say actions speak louder than words.
知道，这是，你知道，他们说行动胜于雄辩。
I'm not seeing a lot of action.
我没有看到很多行动。
I'm just hearing a lot of are hearing a lot of
我只是听到很多正在听到很多
honey and and like,
亲爱的等等，大哭，不管你他妈怎么称呼它，大哭，大哭。
Blubbering, all right.
流口水，好吧。
All right, well,
好吧，好吧，下一次，下次我见到你时，我会开着我的
next up, next time I see you, I shall run you over in my 1994 Honda Civic.
1994 年本田思域碾压你。
How does that sound?
听起来怎么样？
Honda Civic.
本田思域。
That's going to hurt.
那会很痛。
Yeah. That's going to. Hurt.
是的。 那会的。 伤害。
Are you sure you don't want me to be all talk.
你确定你不想让我说话。
I mean I thought you were, I thought this is a euphemism
我的意思是我认为你是，我认为这是对其他事物的委婉说法。
Like you said.
就像你所说。
Oh yeah.
哦耶。
And you said, you said like oh when you go actually going to run me over.
你说，你说哦，当你走的时候真的要撞到我。
And I was like all right, I suppose I will go and grab my Honda
我说没事，我想我会去拿我的本田
Civic and I will run you down in the middle of the street until we.
思域和我会在街中央把你撞倒，直到我们。
Get into the parking lot right.
直接进入停车场。
In the middle of the road. You little.
在马路中间。 你个小
All right.
好的。
I guess if you. Can't hold to your convictions, then I guess, you know.
我猜如果你。 不能坚持你的信念，那么我猜，你知道的。
I had a nightmare about you last night.
昨晚我做了一个关于你的噩梦。
Oh, my God. Really?
我的天啊。 真的吗？
Yeah. A nightmare about you is that it's not real.
是的。 关于你的噩梦是它不是真实的。
Oh, my God. No, it was real.
我的天啊。 不，那是真的。
It was actually real.
它实际上是真实的。
So I woke up. No, I woke up.
于是我醒了。 不，我醒了。
So what was happening? Like,
那么发生了什么？ 像，
I think
我认为这是，就像，预谋，就像，无论是在准备中
for the collar in my head, whatever was happening,
为了我脑袋里的衣领，不管发生什么，你都是在往裤子里塞生虾，对吧？
Like you were putting some into your apron.
就像你在围裙里放了一些一样。
So you, like, your apron had pockets,
所以你，就像，你的围裙有口袋，但你也出于某种该死的原因把一些放在裤子里，
but you were also yelling at me and calling me a dildo.
但你也对我大喊大叫，称我为假阳具。
So that's why I called you a dildo today.
所以这就是我今天称你为假阳具的原因。
Because you kept calling me one of my.
因为你一直叫我我的一员。
I don't know what that was about.
我不知道那是怎么回事。
A VI.
一个六。
You really. Funny?
你真的。 有趣的？
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
You really loved it? No,
你真的爱过吗？ 不，
how do I.
我如何。
There you go.
你去吧。
You go. Oh, I caught it.
你去。 哦，我抓住了。
You go throw me some chicken.
你去扔我一些鸡。
So I just want to ask you, like, hey, why are you why
所以我只想问你，嘿，你为什么
are you stuffing raw shrimp in your pants?
你在裤子里塞生虾吗？
I'm bloody trying to build up an immunity.
我正在努力增强免疫力。
Immunity to white.
对白色免疫。
Living fucking shrimp.
活该死的虾。
So what do you mean? Are you allergic to shrimp?
所以你是什么意思？ 你对虾过敏吗？
No, I just fucking hate that.
不，我只是他妈的讨厌那个。
Oh, you don't like shrimp?
哦，你不喜欢虾吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
It tastes. Tastes like tastes like arse.
它吃起来。 尝起来像屁股一样的味道。
You don't know what real arse tastes like.
你不知道真正的屁股是什么味道。
You know, we find out.
你知道，我们会发现。
I mean, why would I be offering?
我的意思是，我为什么要提供？
I don't want to help you find out.
我不想帮你找出答案。
Oh, oh, of course.
哦，哦，当然。
Because you're you. Because you're so nice like that. OK.
因为你就是你。 因为你那样好。 好的。
Also, I'm just. I'm just pissing around here.
还有，我只是。 我只是在这里撒尿。
I need more ingredients. Equals.
我需要更多的配料。 等于。
So I'm, like, isolated on my chopping station.
所以我，就像，孤立在我的切菜台上。
You sent me this chopped chicken back, you dick.
你把这切碎的鸡寄回给我，你这个混蛋。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I got you that on.
我让你穿上。
I feel like I've got more to do.
我觉得我还有更多事情要做。
Oh, yeah, you probably had more, did you?
哦，是的，你可能有更多，是吗？
I'm just sending all. My fucking awesome.
我只是发送所有。 我的他妈的棒极了。
No, but I throw the fucking plate down, you twat.
不，但我把他妈的盘子扔了下来，你这个混蛋。
What do you mean? I don't have.
你什么意思？ 我没有。
I'm talking to you. I am talking to my feet. Your whole kitchen is burning.
我在跟你说话。 我在说我的脚。 你的整个厨房都在燃烧。
Your whole kitchen is burning.
你的整个厨房都在燃烧。
Oh, this is bad. Oh, this is terrible.
哦，这很糟糕。 哦，这太可怕了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, God, this is fine.
哦，上帝，这很好。
Those go in. Those go in.
那些进去。那些进去。
Chicken in the thing chicken in my arse
鸡中之物 鸡中之物
by and then, then there we go.
到那时，我们就开始了。
Fuck. There's so much to do.
他妈的。 有很多事情要做。
I wish I could help, but I can't.
我希望我能帮忙，但我不能。
I'm just saying. You really can't. OK?
我只是说。 你真的不能。 好的？
I got overwhelmed this time.
这一次我受宠若惊。
I'm fine. I'm fine.
我没事。 我没事。
Dude.
老兄。
Know everything's on fire.
知道一切都在燃烧。
Y'all all burning oil over there.
你们都在那边烧油。
I do amongst.
我在其中。
Just take this.
就拿这个吧。
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。 嗯嗯。
Well, am I supposed to do of this?
好吧，我应该这样做吗？
Fucking chocolate, I guess.
他妈的巧克力，我猜。
I don't know.
我不知道。
You said it all here.
你在这里都说了。
Like, there was a one Sunday night when there's, like, 2 seconds left.
就像，有一个星期天晚上，还有，比如，还剩 2 秒。
And you're like.
而你就像。
Let's go again. So I can't do it again.
我们再来一次。 所以我不能再这样做了。
It's like you gave me a dog. You're like, Here, take this.
就像你给了我一条狗。 你就像，来，拿这个。
Fucking raw chicken.
他妈的生鸡肉。
You're like.
你就像。
Fuck God damn it.
他妈的该死的。
I go, OK.
我去，好的。
Let's try that again.
让我们再试一次。
Yeah, I think we can do it.
是的，我认为我们可以做到。
I wish I got a whole lot more light at least of the day.
我希望至少在一天中我能得到更多的光。
You don't need.
你不需要。
We only need 300 points. We can do that. We can do that. You.
我们只需要300分。 我们能做到这一点。 我们能做到这一点。 你。
Mm hmm. Hmm, hmm, hmm. Easy.
嗯嗯。 嗯，嗯，嗯。 简单的。
I will throw you single.
我会让你单身。
So here we go. Wow.
所以我们开始吧。 哇。
Mm oh.
嗯哦。
And more chicken
还有更多的鸡肉
bingo.
答对了。
That's right. Right. Yeah.
没错。 对。 是的。
I threw the chicken out. It's OK. It's OK.
我把鸡扔了出去。 没关系。 没关系。
I already gave him. Don't worry about it. Don't worry about. Don't trust yourself.
我已经给他了。 不用担心。 不要担心。 不要相信自己。
You know, just throw.
你知道，只是扔。
Just throw throw it, throw it.
扔就扔，扔。
I'm throwing, I'm throwing.
我投，我投。
Literally throwing and Larry throwing.
字面上投掷和拉里投掷。
Do this. A man in an inner tube out there.
做这个。 一个在外面的内胎里的男人。
What the fuck are you doing, bro?
你他妈在做什么，兄弟？
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
I keep keep same ingredients if you can, so.
如果可以的话，我会保留相同的成分，所以。
Right.
对。
One sec. Let me just pick this up. Mm hmm.
1秒。 让我把这个捡起来。 嗯嗯。
But you.
但是你。
It's ill chicken and.
它是病鸡和。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I almost, almost fell onto the water. Do.
我差点，差点掉到水里。 做。
That's crazy.
这很疯狂。
Dial fork.
拨叉。
I got got so much to do. Oh, my God.
我有很多事情要做。 我的天啊。
Yeah, it's all on you, buddy.
是的，一切都取决于你，伙计。
I song you oh.
我给你唱歌哦。
I think you knocked me over when you threw that shit at me.
我想你把那个狗屎扔给我的时候把我撞倒了。
That's. That's funny.
那是。 这是有趣的。
I think. I think.
我认为。 我认为。
Thank fuck the dishes come back clean in this one.
谢谢操盘子在这道菜里干净利落。
Yeah. So you don't have to, like.
是的。 所以你不必喜欢。
Do all of that one.
做这一切。
Literally everything
字面上的一切
that would suppose.
那会假设。
OK, potatoes. Potatoes.
好的，土豆。 土豆。
I got potatoes. Here you go. Potatoes.
我有土豆。 干得好。 土豆。
I'm in there. Something's burning.
我在里面。 有东西在燃烧。
Something potatoes burning over there.
那边有烧土豆的东西。
Chef. Chef.
厨师。 厨师。
Yes, chef.
是的，厨师。
Thank you. Want.
谢谢你。 想。
I'm just concerned I.
我只是担心我。
Heard a patient with me.
听一个病人跟我说。
Boy, I have a billion jobs to do.
男孩，我有十亿个工作要做。
Y'all.
你们。
Chef, take your potatoes.
厨师，把你的土豆拿走。
Take your fucking chicken. Yeehaw.
拿走你那该死的鸡。 呸呸呸。
I mean, what
我的意思是，什么
I feel?
我觉得？
I feel so powerful right now.
我现在感觉很强大。
I'm just watching from the side. I
我只是从侧面看。 一世
oh, fox.
哦，狐狸。
Ah, you know, we're close.
啊，你知道，我们很接近。
We're close, we're close.
我们很接近，我们很接近。
We just need one more dish.
我们只需要再来一道菜。
I think we just need one more dish.
我想我们只需要再来一道菜。
Yeah.
是的。
Should be enough.
应该够了。
Should be an make.
应该是个牌子。
You want it fucking up?
你想搞砸吗？
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。 嗯嗯。
Those get some extra.
那些得到一些额外的。
Oh. Oh, there's those potatoes sitting right there, sir.
哦。 哦，那些土豆就在那儿，先生。
No, no.
不，不。
Do the potato.
做土豆。
There's no.
没有。
Potato. I mean, there's no time.
土豆。 我的意思是，没有时间。
Why do you do this every single time?
为什么你每次都这样做？
You beggin for water? We still got three freestyle.
你开始喝水了吗？ 我们仍然得到了三个自由泳。
You let me throw an ingredient at the last few seconds expecting me
你让我在等待我的最后几秒钟扔了一个配料
like you expecting it? Do something with it.
就像你期待的那样？ 用它做点什么。
It's so far.
到目前为止。
We still got three stars is fine.
我们仍然得到三颗星很好。
I was. That was.
我曾是。 那是。
That was all me.
这就是我的全部。
You just have to chop and somebody that was old negro.
你只需要砍掉一个老黑人。
This is OK.
还行吧。
Well, if I didn't chop those ingredients for you, then, you know.
好吧，如果我没有为你切碎这些成分，那么，你知道的。
You know, if I didn't if I didn't.
你知道，如果我没有，如果我没有。
Cook plate, throw and serve all of them.
煮盘子，扔掉，然后上桌。
Come on, now. There's only two ingredients to work on.
来吧，现在。 只有两种成分需要处理。
If I was ever really that hard.
如果我真的那么难。
Oh, my finger keeps like, oh, yes.
哦，我的手指一直在说，哦，是的。
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道。 我不知道。
I think it just keeps, like, defaulting to the spacebar.
我认为它只是保持默认为空格键。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
So now we got.
所以现在我们得到了。
Time to go space. Oh.
是时候去太空了。 哦。
Yeah. Work with father throwing method now.
是的。 现在使用父亲投掷方法。
I think
我认为
that's why it's sight to do that, right?
这就是为什么这样做是有目共睹的，对吧？
We let's explore a little bit.
我们稍微探索一下。
I want to see if I can find one. Of those where he taking me.
我想看看能不能找到一个。 那些他带我去的地方。
Help.
帮助。
Help, help. Push. OK, yeah.
帮助，帮助。 推。 好的，是的。
You ever seen that?
你见过吗？
You ever seen that video where the dude. It's like.
你有没有看过那个花花公子的视频。 它像是。
Police. How?
警察。 如何？
Hell, no.
一定不行。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
I think it because we're in an RV and we're in like the middle of the desert.
我认为这是因为我们在房车里，我们就像在沙漠中间。
I'll be like.
我会像。
You know, we need to cook.
你知道，我们需要做饭。
We all know where you want to cook.
我们都知道你想在哪里做饭。
What do you want to cook?
你想做什么菜？
Did show, though we need to make fries.
确实展示了，虽然我们需要做薯条。
Is this a reference on missing.
这是关于失踪的参考吗？
Fucking breaking bad.
他妈的坏坏了。
Shoulder? I've never watched Breaking Bad.
肩膀？ 我从来没有看过绝命毒师。
Oh, you've. Never watched it?
哦，你有。 没看过？
All right, well, this is literally like the first episode.
好吧，好吧，这就像第一集一样。
They go they go and they cook it, like, in,
他们去，他们去，他们做饭，就像，在，就像，在沙漠里的房车里，他就像，哦，我想我们。
Have to cook just like you.
必须像你一样做饭。
OK, you see, this is now. That's where I'm at.
好的，你看，这就是现在。 这就是我所在的地方。
Wait, there's only one star here?
等等，这里只有一颗星？
Oh, no, I'm dumb.
哦，不，我很笨。
Ignore me. You're me. Yeah. That's right.
不理我。 你就是我。 是的。 没错。
There's three. Whoa.
有三个。 哇。
All right, pasta.
好吧，意大利面。
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
I passed that pasta going
我通过了那个意大利面去
to throw me as many ingredients as you can. Huh?
尽可能多地向我扔配料。 嗯？
Uh huh. Fish, fish going.
嗯。 鱼，鱼去。
Fish, fish, fish is going.
鱼，鱼，鱼去。
Fish is going is going fried chicken over.
鱼要炸鸡了。
I'm just going to keep chopping.
我只会继续砍。
You know, I have a lot.
你知道，我有很多。
Of shit to chop,
狗屎要砍，所以我只想砍一堆狗屎扔给你。
Go bubble up.
去泡吧。
We need shrimp. You need shrimp.
我们需要虾。 你需要虾。
Shrimp would be nice.
虾会很好吃。
OK, thank you.
好的谢谢。
All right.
好的。
Chicken
鸡
fried
油炸
hey, go.
嘿，走吧。
Chicken pasta.
鸡肉意大利面。
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜呜
Ow, ow.
呜呜呜
Yes. I'm Bo.
是的。 我是博
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going. I'm serving. I'm serving you.
我去，我去，我去，我去。 我在服务。 我在为你服务。
I'm serving
我在服务
it served.
它服务。
It's served as a chop chop more.
更被作为排骨服务。
Oh, fuck. Wait. Oh, God. This is a lot.
哦，操。 等待。 天啊。 这是很多。
There is a lot to do here.
这里有很多事情要做。
Oh, my God. I'm stuck. No.
我的天啊。 我被困住了。 不。
You're fucking my sous chef.
你在操我的副厨师长。
It's fucking dead.
真他妈死了
Oh, no, I'm back. I'm back.
哦，不，我回来了。 我回来了。
And I'm a magician.
而我是魔术师。
Here you go.
干得好。
I didn't know you could die in this fucking game.
我不知道你会死在这该死的游戏里。
All right? Pasta has to pass the pasta.
好的？ 面食必须通过面食。
I sample slice and passed that over our pasta.
我取样切片并将其传递给我们的意大利面。
Thank you. Send pasta.
谢谢你。 送意大利面。
Some pasta.
一些意大利面。
I'm stuck again.
我又被困住了。
Oh, God.
天啊。
My plates, please.
请给我的盘子。
Goodness.
善良。
Do. This is.
做。 这是。
Bad. Like it, like, is really wrong.
坏的。 喜欢，喜欢，真的是错的。
It makes me stranded on the other side, and I can't do anything by plates.
它让我被困在另一边，我不能靠盘子做任何事情。
Fish and shrimp.
鱼和虾。
There we go. There we go. There we go. That's fine.
我们去吧。 我们去吧。 我们去吧。 没事儿。
That's that's that's playable.
那就是可玩。
That's playable. This one and this one.
那是可以玩的。 这个和这个。
One of the top. Send it, send it.
顶级之一。 发送，发送。
OK, ok. OK. I'm going to send it. I'm just.
好的好的。 好的。 我要发送它。 我只是。
I'm going over. I'm going over.
我要过去了。 我要过去了。
I should. I could throw the pool.
我应该。 我可以扔水池。
Can I just. I mean, since I need some shrimp and some shrimp.
我可以吗。 我的意思是，因为我需要一些虾和一些虾。
Shrimp, you know, shrimp.
虾，你知道，虾。
OK, there's.
好的，有。
No way to put. Anything.
没办法放。 任何事物。
Yeah, there's there way.
是的，有办法。
There's a lot of space over here, to be honest.
老实说，这里有很多空间。
There's no where to.
无处可去。
Fucking put anything on the go.
他妈的把任何东西放在旅途中。
OK? Shrimp is cooking.
好的？ 虾在煮。
Shrimp is cooking.
虾在煮。
There you go.
你去吧。
I thought that was cooked. Oh, my God, I'm fucking up.
我以为是煮熟的。 哦，我的上帝，我他妈的。
Shrimps cooking. Shrimp is cooking.
虾煮。 虾在煮。
OK, I'm not saying you don't. I'm saying it over.
好吧，我不是说你没有。 我说完了。
Saying over.
说完了。
All Alyssa, send it.
所有的艾莉莎，发送它。
You've got the fucking roll pan in your hand.
你手里拿着他妈的滚盘。
Wait, what the. Oh, oh.
等等，什么。 哦，哦。
What happened? Oh, my God.
发生了什么？ 我的天啊。
Strangely, I could not tell you.
奇怪的是，我不能告诉你。
All right, well, both were both crap.
好吧，好吧，两个都是废话。
We can't get anymore, so.
我们不能再得到了，所以。
I'm just gonna put more this.
我只是要放更多这个。
Pots. OK? Oh, my God.
花盆。 好的？ 我的天啊。
I put the fucking plate on the chopping board. What am I doing
我把他妈的盘子放在砧板上。 我在做什么
Pasta, pasta.
面食，面食。
Pasta to me.
意大利面给我。
Speak to me tonight. It's amazing you to me.
今晚跟我说话。 你对我来说太棒了。
I got more. Pasta, grandma. Pasta.
我得到了更多。 意大利面，奶奶。 意大利面。
Easy, easy game.
轻松，轻松的游戏。
All right, shrimp.
好吧，虾。
We meet pasta.
我们遇到了意大利面。
I'm going to put this on the on salting.
我要把这个放在盐渍上。
I'm salting.
我在腌制。
He's salting.
他在撒盐。
This motherfucker is so.
这个混蛋就是这样。
And isn't that what you're supposed to do? No,
这不是你应该做的吗？ 不，
I tossed the fucking pasta off the do.
我把这该死的意大利面扔掉了。
This is so.
就是这样。
Dharma, what is. Happening now?
佛法，是什么。 正在发生？
Pasta. Pasta. Pasta for pasta for you, chef.
意大利面。 意大利面。 给你的意大利面，厨师。
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办。
I don't know if you did.
我不知道你有没有。
Did you die or you died?
你死了还是你死了？
Oh, no. Everything burned. Everything burned.
不好了。 一切都烧毁了。 一切都烧毁了。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK, let's roll it back.
好的，让我们回滚。
Let's roll it back a bit.
让我们回滚一点。
We're kind of. We got frazzled.
我们有点。 我们已经筋疲力尽了。
We got, you know, flustered.
你知道，我们很慌张。
It's a lot going on at once. Feel
一次发生了很多事情。 感觉
what do they want us to get?
他们想让我们得到什么？
480 points. Holy shit.
480分。 天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Listen, with a plan, this will work.
听着，有一个计划，这会奏效。
I think that the issue there are two issues with this one,
我认为这个问题有两个问题，
not enough ingredients are coming out because we keep getting stuck on one side.
没有足够的成分出来，因为我们一直卡在一侧。
Yes. Secondly, not enough space to put, you know, what.
是的。 其次，没有足够的空间放置，你知道的，什么。
I think is a good idea.
我认为是个好主意。
We should just like, hog all the ingredients from that one side
我们应该喜欢，从那一侧占用所有成分，因为，就像，它是。
Literally on the left and just whole ingredients that you
从字面上看，在左边，只是你的全部成分
OK and then you'll have everything you need.
好的，然后您将拥有所需的一切。
OK, OK.
好的好的。
I'll just ricotta what the menu is and immediately drop everything.
我将只是乳清干酪菜单是什么，然后立即放下所有东西。
Great. Yeah. Yes, yes.
伟大的。 是的。 是的是的。
I think
我认为
I'll grab I'll grab some stuff pre-emptively though.
我会抢我会抢先抢一些东西。
Like this.
像这样。
Like a good idea to pasta.
就像意大利面的好主意。
Like we need a box on the pasta that.
就像我们需要一个盒子放在意大利面上一样。
Yeah. Just throw all the plastic.
是的。 扔掉所有的塑料。
Throw all the possible.
把所有可能的东西都扔掉。
But could.
但可以。
Literally just fuck this.
从字面上看，只是他妈的。
Side of the map specifically it's.
地图的一侧特别是它的。
The ocean oddly blocked me with that.
海洋奇怪地用那个挡住了我。
Like I couldn't even get all. My cutaway here right
就像我什至无法得到所有。 我的剖面图就在这里
OK. All right.
好的。 好的。
I got the pasta going.
我把意大利面拿走了。
Possibly.
可能。
We got going too fast for a lifetime.
我们走得太快了一辈子。
Yeah,
是的，
it's an Italian woman's kitchen right now.
现在是一个意大利女人的厨房。
That's feeling that I got to make the best.
这就是我必须做到最好的感觉。
Did you hear about,
你有没有听说过，哦，你知道，你看过视频，比如，
the Italian, the old Italian guy, like, complaining that there's no fish
那个意大利人，那个意大利人，抱怨没有鱼
oh, that was the one thing I've got to get.
哦，那是我必须得到的一件事。
To take it off. It's about the one.
把它取下来。 这是关于那个。
Take it off.
把它拿下来。
I can't. I can't.
我不能。 我不能。
I can't. I can't. I can't. Oh, no.
我不能。 我不能。 我不能。 不好了。
Oh, no. Oh, no. I'm a vox rocks. Fuck. Oh, God.
不好了。 不好了。 我是一个vox Rocks。 他妈的。 天啊。
I think the fire extinguisher.
我认为是灭火器。
Where's the fire. Extinguisher?
火在哪里。 灭火器？
It's with you. It's with me.
它与你同在。 它与我同在。
Or is it? Oh, no.
或者是吗？ 不好了。
I don't know. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
我不知道。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
I can't find the fire extinguisher.
我找不到灭火器。
Bro. Well, this has not worked.
兄弟。 好吧，这没有奏效。
Oh, no. Everything's everything's burning
不好了。 一切都在燃烧
VOCs. Everything's burning.
挥发性有机化合物。 一切都在燃烧。
Where's the fire extinguisher?
灭火器在哪里？
I genuinely don't know. I'm looking at my fucking God.
我真的不知道。 我在看着我他妈的上帝。
I can't see anything. I don't.
我什么都看不见。 我不。
We do so much pasta why it so much pasta everywhere?
我们做这么多意大利面，为什么到处都有这么多意大利面？
Oh, I could not tell.
哦，我说不出来。
I could not fucking tell you.
我他妈不能告诉你。
Voxer.
沃克斯。
So we agree.
所以我们同意。
It's how we.
我们就是这样。
I'm oh, I can't find the fire extinguisher box.
我是哦，我找不到灭火器箱。
Oh, don't you?
哦，不是吗？
Oh, it's right here.
哦，就在这里。
Right here. Oh.
就在这儿。 哦。
You need you need to stop
每次出现轻微不便时，您都需要停止强迫自己达到性高潮。
I was panicking, OK?
我惊慌失措，好吗？
I was panicking. I was panicking.
我很恐慌。 我很恐慌。
I was panicking.
我很恐慌。
Sounded like. You're being stimulated.
听起来像。 你被刺激了。
I mean, you're here so
我的意思是，你在这里太难了。 敲它。
All right, all right, all right.
好的，好的，好的。
This place may be burning down, but, you know, you fly, right?
这个地方可能正在燃烧，但是，你知道，你会飞，对吧？
We'll get you everyone a flutter.
我们会让大家振作起来。
Everything's dead.
一切都死了。
VOCs. I think we got to restart this one.
挥发性有机化合物。 我认为我们必须重新启动这个。
We failed so hard early on.
我们很早就失败了。
All right, now.
现在好了。
Look at my side of the kitchen.
看看我这边的厨房。
Is going to make sure that there's enough space to put shifts
会确保有足够的空间来换班，这样你就可以从烤架上拿走屎了，好吗？
so that you can take shit off the grill, ok? OK.
好的。
The fire. OK.
火。 好的。
Yeah, you do the thing with the pasta.
是的，你用意大利面做事。
I'll start chopping
我要开始砍了
talking, bombarding the.
说话，轰炸了。
Bombardment.
轰击。
And any more. Pasta is one of each.
还有更多。 意大利面是其中之一。
One of each ok. OK,
每个都可以。 好的，
I'm fish.
我是鱼。
You got fish?
你有鱼吗？
Going to give. Me a shrimp?
要去给。 我是虾？
Meat, fish, shrimp, meat.
肉、鱼、虾、肉。
A shrimp meat.
一块虾肉。
Wait, hold on. Wait. There is the meat. OK?
等等，等等。 等待。 有肉。 好的？
No, you need to chop the meat, you dumb arse.
不，你需要切肉，你这个笨蛋。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
I thought I thought I did. Did didn't know you were
我以为我以为我做到了。 不知道你是
like.
像。
I have no room
我没有房间
here.
这里。
Holy shit.
天啊。
This is stressful. Here you go.
这是有压力的。 干得好。
Here, y'all.
在这里，你们。
Here's your excellent your meal.
这是您的美味佳肴。
Here's your meal. Yep.
这是你的饭菜。 是的。
That's a plate. More postop.
那是一个盘子。 更多的术后。
88. 88 for that.
88. 88 为此。
OK, I need. Ah, ok.
好的，我需要。 喔好吧。
Here's a meats are all the meat are what we eat.
这里的肉是我们吃的所有肉。
Why can't I mix it?
为什么我不能混合？
Oh, there you go. There you go.
哦，给你。 你去吧。
You bitch.
你个婊子
I'll grab it.
我会抓住它。
Don't worry, don't worry. Do worry. I got it.
别担心，别担心。 放心吧。 我得到了它。
I got
我有
all, dude.
所有，伙计。
All day.
一整天。
Oh, dude, all My God.
哦，伙计，我的上帝。
Did you guys see what's happening right here?
你们看到这里发生了什么吗？
Some shrimp
一些虾
make sure you get this from slaughtered shrimp.
确保你从屠宰的虾中得到这个。
Shrimps get shrimp is good right there.
虾虾就在那里很好吃。
Now I'm just cooking.
现在我只是做饭。
I'm just got 100 points.
我才100分。
We got 2 minutes is going to go fine.
我们有 2 分钟就可以了。
Yeah, I think,
是的，我想，
I think the game knows how stressful this part is.
我认为游戏知道这部分的压力有多大。
We just, we just.
我们只是，我们只是。
That is not cooked.
那不是煮熟的。
That's not cooked. Know no, this is cooked.
那不是煮熟的。 不知道，这是煮熟的。
This is cooked.
这是煮熟的。
You just threw.
你刚刚扔了。
OK, that's ready.
好的，准备好了。
That's ready.
那准备好了。
Go perfect. Perfect. Don't burn it.
去完美。 完美的。 不要燃烧它。
Don't burn it. Don't buy it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
不要燃烧它。 不要买它。 耶耶耶。
Pasta, pasta, pasta.
意大利面，意大利面，意大利面。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
It burned.
它烧了。
It burned, it burned, it burned. It fucking burned.
烧了，烧了，烧了。 真他妈烧了
It fucking burned alive. That's fine. Just get the five fingers.
活活烧死了 没事儿。 就拿五个手指。
That's fine. Fine, fine, fine.
没事儿。 不错不错不错
Don't panic.
不要恐慌。
Don't panic, don't panic. What
不要惊慌，不要惊慌。 什么
ok. OK, that's good.
行。 好的，那很好。
That's good.
那很好。
You go.
你去。
OK, this passes.
好的，这通过了。
I think this spices. Good to go.
我认为这是香料。 很好走。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
妈的。 妈的。
It's fine.
没事。
Don't go panic. Don't panic the panic. You're doing fine. You doing just fine?
不要恐慌。 不要惊慌失措。 你做得很好。 你过得好吗？
I mean, pasta.
我是说，意大利面。
Why can't I right now? Come on.
为什么我现在不能？ 来吧。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We thought that wasn't cooked. It wasn't cooked.
我们以为那不是熟的。 它没有煮熟。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There's so much prosperity everywhere.
到处都有这么多的繁荣。
OK, almost ready with this
好的，差不多准备好了
let's talk about pasta. Hmm, hmm.
让我们谈谈意大利面。 嗯，嗯。
Hmm, hmm.
嗯，嗯。
I'll give you some shrimp. There's cooked shrimp.
我给你一些虾。 有熟虾。
There's cooked shrimp right here. OK, ok.
这里有熟虾。 好的好的。
Ah, this one's ready, I think.
啊，这个已经准备好了，我想。
Why can't I combine it? It's not cooked.
为什么我不能合并它？ 它没有煮熟。
Don't the meat man
不要吃肉的人
is meat pasta.
是肉面食。
Oh, no, that's done.
哦，不，已经完成了。
That's done, that's done.
做完了，就做完了。
I'm taking over sending that one cut.
我正在接手发送那个剪辑。
There's so much stuff. Oh.
有这么多东西。 哦。
There we go.
我们去吧。
I need me.
我需要我。
Fresh pasta, fish pasta.
新鲜面食，鱼面食。
I'm. I'm trying. Oh, my God.
我是。 我在尝试。 我的天啊。
Everything's everywhere.
一切无处不在。
Everything. Everywhere.
一切。 到处。
All the time.
每时每刻。
OK, ok. This is right. It is right.
好的好的。 这是对的。 这是正确的。
Not don't grab the fucking dumb arse. OK?
不是不要抓住他妈的愚蠢的屁股。 好的？
OK, let me send this over
好的，我把这个发过去
I. I think.
我认为。
No, no, no. I mean, for.
不不不。 我的意思是，对于。
All we need 400. OK, ok. OK.
我们只需要400。好的，好的。 好的。
See, this is fine. This is fine. I reckon we could do it.
看，这很好。 这可以。 我认为我们可以做到。
Do would you like me to do more for you?
你想让我为你做更多吗？
Because I feel like. I mean, maybe. Maybe.
因为我觉得。 我的意思是，也许。 也许。
I don't.
我不。
Know.
知道。
I think I just fucked up a lot.
我想我只是搞砸了很多。
I just fucked up a lot there.
我只是在那里搞砸了很多。
OK, because there's so much.
好的，因为有这么多。
There's not enough space. There's like, no tables.
没有足够的空间。 就像，没有桌子。
It's like, puts down the. I think we can do this.
就像，放下了。 我认为我们可以做到这一点。
I think we can do this. OK, ok, we can do this.
我认为我们可以做到这一点。 好的，好的，我们可以做到这一点。
It's good to keep practising. Yeah, you got it.
坚持练习是好事。 是的，你明白了。
We got it. Easy peasy.
我们得到了它。 十分简单。
I'm going to grab it now.
我现在要抓住它。
There's so much food. On the floor.
有这么多食物。 在地上。
I couldn't.
我不能。
I was like, glued trudging through a pile.
我就像，被粘在一堆东西中跋涉。
This game is.
这个游戏是。
Making me hungry. Excuse me. Making me hungry.
让我饿了。 打扰一下。 让我饿了。
Nice. Try this again.
好的。 再试一次。
And you just have lunch.
而你只是吃午饭。
What do you have for lunch, by the way?
顺便问一下，你午餐吃什么？
I had some fried rice. Oh, egg fried rice.
我吃了一些炒饭。 哦，鸡蛋炒饭。
Chicken fried rice.
鸡肉炒饭。
Actually, you know,
其实，你知道，
yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
All right, we're not cooking.
好吧，我们不做饭。
OK? I'm going to get the pasta going right now.
好的？ 我现在就去拿意大利面。
Oh, thank you, my stars.
哦，谢谢你，我的星星。
Thank you. I've been called an expert.
谢谢你。 我被称为专家。
I need. I need meats. I need meat.
我需要。 我需要肉。 我需要肉。
Not not shrimp, but.
不是虾，而是。
Yeah, yeah, like two meats.
是的，是的，就像两块肉一样。
I need two meats.
我需要两块肉。
Always my one.
永远是我的。
Not enough.
不够。
No, it's not enough, actually.
不，实际上还不够。
Oh, why don't you want to hear?
哦，你为什么不想听？
Jesus Christ, this is the fucking kitchen.
天哪，这就是他妈的厨房。
What oh!
什么哦！
Oh, God.
天啊。
OK, Elizabeth, those meats are going.
好的，伊丽莎白，那些肉要走了。
This is ready. Order! Order!
这准备好了。 命令！ 命令！
Order!
命令！
Yep. Yeah, that would make him any good, right?
是的。 是的，那会让他变得更好，对吧？
I got
我有
to go.
去。
I think I need. I think.
我想我需要。 我认为。
I think you actually know this is good to go.
我想你实际上知道这很好。
You could go
你可以去
it's possible.
有可能的。
Just need to go in. OK?
只需要进去。好吗？
I'm not send you another meat pasta.
我不会再给你送肉意大利面了。
Oh, there you go. Oh.
哦，给你。 哦。
You got enough fish? Yeah.
你有足够的鱼吗？ 是的。
You got. You.
你得到了。 你。
I don't think.
我不这样认为。
So. This little fish I need up.
所以。 这条小鱼我需要。
This isn't chopped.
这不是切的。
Hold on. I have my I got you.
坚持，稍等。 我有我有你。
Throw it right onto the board.
直接扔到板上。
Going again?
再去吗？
Yeah. Oh.
是的。 哦。
Dude, look at our synergy girl.
伙计，看看我们的协同女孩。
There we go.
我们去吧。
OK, and then I need a shrimp.
好的，然后我需要一只虾。
Shrimp is almost done.
虾差不多完成了。 虾差不多完成了。
And you smell me
你闻到我的味道
do you mean pasta? Next, if you can.
你是说意大利面吗？ 接下来，如果可以的话。
Perfect. Perfect. Give me that. Yeah.
完美的。 完美的。 给我那个。 是的。
Excellent, excellent.
优秀的，优秀的。
Yeah.
是的。
Played pretty quick, but then I just put it down.
玩得很快，但后来我就把它放下了。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'll put it down there into Salty.
我会把它放到Salty里面。
There we. Go.
我们在那里。 去。
Fish for you.
给你钓鱼。
Thought.
想法。
Oh, you you've got me.
哦，你有我。
Just just use. Yeah. Pasta, pasta, pasta.
只是使用。 是的。 意大利面，意大利面，意大利面。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
耶耶耶。
I think you need to. Hold on, hold on.
我认为你需要。 等一下，等一下。
I need more pasta. I don't like a million pasta.
我需要更多的意大利面。 我不喜欢一百万个意大利面。
I'll plate this and I'll give you pasta.
我会把这个装盘，然后给你意大利面。
We might miss that one, but we still got a whole minute left, so it should be fine.
我们可能会错过那个，但我们还有整整一分钟，所以应该没问题。
OK. Are
好的。 意大利面是给你的吗，厨师？
Of pasta.
意大利面。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You go. More pasta.
你去。 更多的意大利面。
All the jar jar jar
所有的罐子罐子罐子
that's almost done. OK.
这几乎完成了。 好的。
Now I need to get some pasta.
现在我需要买些意大利面。
That'll be great.
那会很棒。
OK, I need shrimp and and ah.
好的，我需要虾和啊。
What's it
它是什么
there we go.
我们去吧。
Shrimp, shrimp and fish. Shrimp and fish.
虾、虾和鱼。 虾和鱼。
Shrimp and fish.
虾和鱼。
Here we go. Here we go. Get you.
开始了。 开始了。 我懂了。
Don't get to go.
不要走。
Fuck what?
他妈的什么？
What? Oh, no. Oh, stranded.
什么？ 不好了。 哦，搁浅了。
No, no, no. I think we got enough time. I think we got enough time.
不不不。 我想我们有足够的时间。 我想我们有足够的时间。
OK. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
好的。 是的，是的，是的，是的。
I'm going to me. I'm going to meet one. Ready?
我要去我身边。 我要去见一个。 准备好？
I'm going to meet one. Ready?
我要去见一个。 准备好？
Yeah, I'm coming over.
是的，我要过来了。
I'm coming over. I'm coming.
我要过来了。 我来了。
I'm coming over.
我要过来了。
No. Here you go. Here you go. Here we go. Gather me. No fire.
不，给你。 干得好。 开始了。 聚集我。 没有火。
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
来吧，来吧，来吧，来吧。
I need more pasta and more. Possibly more muscle.
我需要更多的意大利面和更多。 可能肌肉比较多。
I know any more pasta.
我知道更多的意大利面。
Go with the shit you got already.
和你已经得到的狗屎一起去吧。
I don't have any pasta, though.
不过，我没有意大利面。
I'm going to get. I'll get you the pasta right now.
我要得到。 我马上给你拿意大利面。
Oh, no, I don't.
哦，不，我没有。
All Mel VOCs. It's over. It's over.
所有 Mel VOC。 结束了。 结束了。
It's not over.
它还没有结束。
Go oh. My
去哦。 我的
I don't want to dump Hannibal.
我不想抛弃汉尼拔。
It's all right.
没关系，还不错。
450. Is that enough?
450.够了吗？
No, it's not. We have one. More. Oh, my God. Yes.
不它不是。 我们有一个。 更多的。 我的天啊。 是的。
So you need one more pasta. One more pasta.
所以你还需要一份意大利面。 再来一份意大利面。
Or I'll just make sure you've got enough pasta.
或者我会确保你有足够的意大利面。
That's OK. Now. So close.
那没问题。 现在。 很近。
Holy shit.
天啊。
OK, now.
现在没事了。
You, me, boy, you can do it.
你，我，男孩，你可以做到。
Again. Again?
再次。 再次？
Yeah.
是的。
No. Are you stressing?
不，你有压力吗？
Maybe not all.
也许不是全部。
Are you eating?
你在吃吗？
I have some information that I can be refreshing.
我有一些信息可以让我耳目一新。
Oh, yeah?
哦耶？
I'm just going
我现在只是在这里准备好这些。
This can go running.
这可以运行。
These things on the pan. Are
这些东西上锅。 是
and you get these nuts ready?
你准备好这些坚果了吗？
Yeah, these. These are ready.
是的，这些。 这些都准备好了。
Where's the shrimp? Shrimp? Shrimp.
虾在哪里？ 虾？ 虾。
Thank you. OK,
谢谢你。 好的，
this is ready.
这是准备好了。
This is ready. Perfect.
这准备好了。 完美的。
Put it down.
放下它。
Absolutely perfect.
绝对完美。
Oh, my. God. Oh, my God. It. Wait.
天啊。 上帝。 我的天啊。 它。 等待。
Holy shit. Holy shit. Holy shit.
天啊。 天啊。 天啊。
No, it's fine. Fine, fine.
不，没关系。 很好，很好。
Hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up.
顶住，顶住，顶住，顶住，顶住。
Oh, no.
不好了。
OK, well, that's on fire.
好吧，那是火。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I need another fish.
我需要另一条鱼。
I got some fish.
我有一些鱼。
We all the fish down the bottom.
我们所有的鱼都掉到了底部。
Fucking drop this.
他妈的放下这个。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you for fish.
谢谢你的鱼。
I'm going to put more pasta in now.
我现在要放更多的意大利面。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Why?
我的天啊。 为什么？
Why is there a way? How did this. Meat get onto the.
为什么有办法？ 这是怎么做到的。 肉上来。
Why? You throw that back?
为什么？ 你把那个扔回去？
You can cook it
你可以煮
the pasta.
意大利面。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯。
God, that's.
天哪，就是这样。
Right. It's ready to give.
对。 它已准备好给予。
Give me that.
给我那个。
Give me the.
给我。
Yeah, yeah, it's good.
是的，是的，这很好。
It's good.
这很好。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
All right. Me, pass. Them, me. Pass them me. Passes.
好的。 我，通过。 他们，我。 把他们递给我。 通过。
Getting is ready is getting ready.
准备好了就是准备好了。
I mean, are
我的意思是，是
I think I need to get another.
我想我需要再买一个。
I need. More pastas.
我需要。 更多意大利面。
Fish, fresh fish.
鱼，鲜鱼。
In the air.
在空中。
Poor person needs. OK, the meat meat's ready.
穷人需要。 好的，肉肉做好了。
It's ready
准备好了
here you go.
干得好。
Here you are.
这个给你。
We go. Perfect.
我们去。 完美的。
Well, we'll meet pasta if possible.
好吧，如果可能的话，我们会见意大利面。
Holy fuck.
他妈的。
Yeah. This meats. This meats.
是的。 这肉。 这肉。
Good to go. No.
很好走。 不。
Not fine. Fine.
不好。 美好的。
I'm back.
我回来了。
Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
They call me William.
他们叫我威廉。
After you always come here. Yummy.
以后你总是来这里。 好吃。
Pasta is writing me. Pulse is ready. I always come on your back.
意大利面在写我。 脉冲准备好了。 我总是站在你的背上。
Living inside.
住在里面。
That's a shame.
这是一种耻辱。
I think you really did.
我想你真的做到了。
I think you really earned again.
我觉得你真的又赚到了。
Probably earned it.
应该是赚了
OK, and
好的，并且
OK. This sore.
好的。 这个痛。
This one's ready. There you go.
这个准备好了。 你去吧。
For. It.
为了。 它。
And more regular pasta. And here it is. OK.
还有更普通的意大利面。 就在这里。 好的。
What happened to my, uh.
我怎么了，呃。
We might have to ignore that. That that pasta.
我们可能不得不忽略这一点。 那个意大利面。
What do you go? Go ahead with a meat pasta. OK.
你去做什么？ 继续吃肉意大利面。 好的。
I'll often pass that fork.
我会经常通过那个叉子。
I keep, I get my finger keeps resting on the bottom.
我保持，我的手指一直放在底部。
I don't have any meat over here, by the way.
顺便说一句，我这里没有肉。
I'll make any. One, but
我会做任何。 一，但是
I keep sending you some fish
我一直给你送一些鱼
yeah, we got time.
是的，我们有时间。
We got time.
我们有时间。
To do some fish pasta. About what?
做一些鱼面食。 关于什么？
That first one has three bars. That'll be a good tip.
第一个有三个酒吧。 这将是一个很好的提示。
OK, ok. OK,
好的好的。 好的，
I'll try.
我会尝试。
I'll try
我会尝试
I don't know.
我不知道。
I'll know. Here we go.
我会知道。 开始了。
Here we go.
开始了。
I oh, my God.
我哦，我的上帝。
OK, you got it. You got it. You got it.
好的，你明白了。 你说对了。 你说对了。
No, it's not enough. It's not enough. It's not enough.
不，这还不够。 那还不够。 这不够。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
This bar is hard.
这个酒吧很难。
It's actually quite a challenge.
这实际上是一个相当大的挑战。
What do we do or how do we improve on this?
我们该怎么做或如何改进？
I think we just have to be cleaner about it.
我认为我们只需要对此保持清洁即可。
So the mistake I made that time, it was I didn't throw you an off me.
所以那次我犯的错误是我没有把你从我身上甩开。
And then there was like, told me pasta get made, so I'll just make all go on.
然后就像，告诉我意大利面做好了，所以我会让一切继续下去。
Like, let's do it again.
就像，让我们再做一次。
I'll go on like a rotation.
我会像轮换一样继续。
All right.
好的。
OK, got it. Oh.
好的，我知道了。 哦。
I don't like rotations. I'll do meat. Fish.
我不喜欢轮换。 我会做肉。 鱼。
So the knuckleball, I had the keyboard controls
所以指关节，我有键盘控制试图，比如，拿起东西，就像它很烦人一样。
Yeah,
是的，
OK. Oh.
好的。 哦。
I remember lesson. I played this.
我记得教训。 我玩过这个。
It was on switch the controls to really get that
它是在切换控件以真正让你做意大利面。
I will start chopping right away. Yeah.
我马上开始切菜。 是的。
One thing.
一件事。
OK. These are good.
好的。 这些都很好。
Uh, effects
嗯，效果
all right.
好的。
Thank you. That's very.
谢谢你。 那是非常。
Ok. Shrimp
行。 虾
shrimp. OK.
虾。 好的。
Fish and these.
鱼和这些。
Oh, no, I don't need is good
哦不，我不需要就好
and shrimp is good.
和虾很好。
OK, meat. Pasta's ready.
好的，肉。 意大利面做好了。
Here you go. I need very. Good.
干得好。 我非常需要。 好的。
You good? Yeah.
你好吗？ 是的。
And then the right. This one's ready.
然后是右边。 这个准备好了。
Oh, perfect, boy. Yeah, well done.
哦，完美，男孩。 是的，干得好。
And now I need all.
现在我需要一切。
I need more regular pasta, like to boil.
我需要更多普通的意大利面，比如煮。
Come over to grab. Up.
过来抢。 向上。
A new another one and another one.
一个新的一个又一个。
Meat you can do fish I need. Good boy.
肉你可以做我需要的鱼。 好孩子。
You doing really well?
你真的过得好吗？
I have shrimp over here.
我这里有虾。
I need Keith for me. Another pasta yeah.
我需要基思。 另一个意大利面是的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You hungry?
你饿了？
OK, I got a I think I got it.
好的，我知道了，我想我知道了。
I got another meat one. Ready?
我又买了一块肉。 准备好？
Here you go.
干得好。
Fact fuck. Where you go?
事实他妈的。 你去哪里？
You got that one,
你有那个，
then like.
然后喜欢。
What the fuck?
什么鬼？
I think I threw it into your house. Yeah, you.
我想我把它扔进了你的房子。 是的你。
Did. That can happen.
做过。 这可能会发生。
OK? Oh, my God.
好的？ 我的天啊。
Shrimp. OK, yeah.
虾。 好的，是的。
Shrimp.
虾。
Shrimp is good. It's sitting there. Yeah.
虾不错。 它坐在那里。 是的。
I got it.
我得到了它。
I oh, yeah. We can do this one.
我哦，是的。 我们可以做到这一点。
We can do this one. Definitely.
我们可以做到这一点。 确实。
I can't pick the shit off of the ground, though.
不过，我不能从地上捡起狗屎。
OK, here we go.
好的，我们开始吧。
There we go. My fish.
我们去吧。 我的鱼。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Everything's everywhere. Oh.
一切无处不在。 哦。
Everything is everywhere.
一切无处不在。
You're
你是
OK, and the shrimp is ready.
好的，虾就做好了。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
This one's good to go.
这个很好去。
Oh, my God. This is like.
我的天啊。 这就像。
This is. Not. Sanitary.
这是。 不是。 卫生。
We're, like, violating so many health codes right now.
我们现在违反了这么多健康守则。
No, no, no.
不不不。
This is completely fine. This thing, it's their fault for ordering so much shit.
这完全没问题。 这东西，是他们点了这么多狗屎的错。
We're this way. We're innocent.
我们就是这样。 我们是无辜的。
Bystanders. OK.
旁观者。 好的。
Ok. Any more pasta? Thank you.
行。 还有面条吗？ 谢谢你。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you. So, so sexy. You're gorgeous.
谢谢你。 所以，太性感了。 你太美了。
You're so sexy. Look at you, cook.
你太性感了。 看着你，做饭。
Oh, all
哦，所有
I think I need to actually know this is ready.
我想我需要知道这已经准备好了。
Is ready.
准备好了。
OK, that's good.
好的，那很好。
That's good.
那很好。
I'm going to send this over.
我要把这个寄过去。
There's an army pass. We're at three. 80.
有军队通行证。 我们三点。  80.
We just need to not fail.
我们只需要不失败。
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。 嗯嗯。
Make sure you got some meat pasta coming, OK?
确保你有一些肉意大利面，好吗？
Yeah, that's me. Pasta. Why didn't I see that?
是的，就是我。 意大利面。 为什么我没看到？
Yeah, there's a me pasta right there.
是的，那里有我的意大利面。
OK, we might fail one, but I'll get another one then.
好吧，我们可能会失败一个，但我会得到另一个。
That will give us a big enough tip.
这将给我们一个足够大的提示。
Yeah, that's belly anything.
是的，那是肚子什么的。
That's fine. That's fine.
没事儿。 没事儿。
That's fine.
没事儿。
One more. For 17. That's enough.
多一个。  17岁。这就够了。
No, I don't.
不，我没有。
I can't get it. Oh, fuck.
我无法得到它。 哦，操。
No, no, it's fine.
不，不，没关系。
It's fine. Fine, fine, fine. I don't worry. We got it.
没事。 不错不错不错 我不着急。 我们得到了它。
No, we. Didn't.
不，我们。 没有。
Oh, it's in.
哦，进去了。
It's a harbour.
这是一个港口。
Oh, my.
天啊。
Oh, did you guys do you?
哦，你们做到了吗？
We were absolutely parking.
我们绝对停车。
You were hogging so hard.
你太拼了
Shit. Oh.
拉屎。 哦。
Oh. OK.
哦。 好的。
One issue I saw was that there's so much ingredients
我看到的一个问题是，我身上到处都是这么多的成分，所以就像，很难挑选一些东西。
So maybe not too many.
所以可能不会太多。
Yeah, not too many.
是的，不会太多。
So, yeah, definitely. So, OK, ok.
所以，是的，肯定的。 所以，好吧，好吧。
And if we fix that, then I think we got it this time.
如果我们解决了这个问题，那么我认为这次我们做到了。
I will literally, I will look at the recipes and throw exactly what you need.
我会从字面上看，我会看看食谱并准确地抛出你需要的东西。
OK, ok, we got it. We got it.
好的，好的，我们明白了。 我们得到了它。
OK, this one for sure, I believe.
好的，我相信这是肯定的。
Sure.
当然。
So much so I'm.
这么多，我就是。
Absolutely going to do it this time.
这次绝对要做。
It's pasta.
这是意大利面。
All right. Meat, pasta.
好的。 肉，面食。
Meat stuff.
肉的东西。
All right.
好的。
This and this into the that's important right now.
这个和这个到那个现在很重要。
I'll cook that as well.
我也会煮那个。
Pick it up shop, OK?
去店里取，好吗？
Yeah.
是的。
All right.
好的。
You've got you should now have enough for everything.
你已经得到你现在应该有足够的一切。
Mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
I mean, do.
我的意思是，做。
You know the customer?
你认识客户吗？
OK, that's ready.
好的，准备好了。
Our fish is ready.
我们的鱼准备好了。
It's it's it's
它是它是它
shrimp is ready.
虾准备好了。
OK, this is ready.
好的，这就准备好了。
Done. Cook more shrimp.
完毕。 煮更多的虾。
I mean, you've seen me.
我的意思是，你见过我。
It's been a bit slow.
它有点慢。
It's just the rotation of the thing.
这只是事物的旋转。
There you go.
你去吧。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, my. God.
我的天啊。 天啊。 上帝。
Oh, fuck.
哦，操。
What goat meat?
什么羊肉？
OK. Ow! Ow!
好的。 哦！ 哦！
Ow! Ow!
哦！ 哦！
Ow! No!
哦！ 不！
And this is good to go.
这很好。
It's sitting there. It's just sitting there.
它坐在那里。 它只是坐在那里。
I got it. I got it. OK.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。 好的。
And then we got more.
然后我们得到了更多。
We got more fucked. There's no room for anything.
我们更操蛋了。 没有任何空间。
Got me past the next meeting. Past me, past them. Me past that.
让我通过了下一次会议。 越过我，越过他们。 我过去了。
OK, ok. Yeah, yeah. Let me pasta.
好的好的。 是啊是啊。 让我吃意大利面。
Now. Cooks you me pastas right now.
现在。 现在给你做意大利面。
That's important.
这很重要。
And then
进而
hey, this is good.
嘿，这很好。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
OK, meat posturing.
好吧，肉摆姿势。
You pass is ready.
你的通行证准备好了。
It's sitting there.
它坐在那里。
You go.
你去。
Perfect. Perfect.
完美的。 完美的。
All right, well, I'm fine.
好吧，好吧，我很好。
I'm fine.
我没事。
Yeah,
是的，
and I got another me pasta going to your job.
我得到了另一个我的意大利面去你的工作。
OK, I'll work on the regular fish and shrimp one. Now,
好的，我会研究普通的鱼虾一号。 现在，
I got fish
我有鱼
fish going and another regular pasta.
鱼去和另一个普通的意大利面。
A regular.
一个常客。
Got you
得到你
from.
从。
OK. Fish.
好的。 鱼。
It's ready. It's ready. It's there.
它准备好了。 它准备好了。 它就在那里。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I got need.
我有需要。
All right.
好的。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Do you need another fish and shrimp.
你需要另一个鱼和虾。
That you need?
你需要那个？
Yeah. Just one more fishing trip.
是的。 再来一次钓鱼之旅。
You'll be OK.
你会没事的。
Yeah. Any more pasta? I'll get a I'll get a meet going.
是的。 还有面条吗？ 我会得到一个我会得到一个会议。
I meet one going since I think that's OK, so.
我遇到了一个，因为我认为这还可以，所以。
Yeah, yeah, ok. OK. This one's good.
是的，是的，好的。 好的。 这个不错
That shrimp.
那个虾
Yeah. And it's ready to go.
是的。 它已经准备好了。
Yeah, you can grab that.
是的，你可以抓住它。
Yeah, you grab that, you grab that.
是的，你抓住那个，你抓住那个。
You grab that one. I can grab it.
你抓住那个。 我可以抓住它。
Grab the fuck out of it. OK, all right.
把他妈拿走。 好的没问题。
This one's ready. Meet one's ready. New one's ready. Ready.
这个准备好了。 见面准备好了。 新的准备好了。 准备好。
Oh, God. Holy shit.
天啊。 天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We haven't quite finished both of these I kids get older.
我们还没有完全完成这两个我孩子长大了。
624. Absolutely fine.
624. 完全没问题。
Pretty dude.
帅哥。
Absolutely. Paul My God.
绝对地。 保罗我的上帝。
Paul Holy shit.
保罗 天哪。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Look at us.
看着我们。
Go look at us.
去看看我们。
Game The Onion, man.
游戏洋葱，伙计。
Are you still happy? Both of them were solid.
你还快乐吗？ 他们俩都很结实。
Was it to make our onion man and his dog proud?
是为了让我们的洋葱人和他的狗感到骄傲吗？
Godzilla.
哥斯拉。
Oh, that was so hard.
哦，那太难了。
Oh, my.
天啊。
Goodness. Christ,
善良。 基督，
oh, you know.
哦，你知道的。
It really was just.
真的只是。
Like all about the organisation there at that point.
就像那时那里的组织一样。
It helped Sheets and looked at Rainbow.
它帮助了Sheets，看着Rainbow。
Black, so that's to get it.
黑色，所以就是得到它。
Then I think there's a secret who we we
然后我想我们有一个秘密
you know there is a secret.
你知道有一个秘密。
Oh no, we already touched that before, haven't we just.
哦不，我们之前已经接触过，不是吗。
Jesse, Jesse are coming out.
杰西，杰西要出来了。
You're making me want to watch Breaking Bad now.
你让我现在想看《绝命毒师》。
Is it good?
好吗？
It's arguably one of the, one of the best TV shows ever made.
它可以说是有史以来最好的电视节目之一。
Like I think it was like by far the most popular show on in
就像我认为这是迄今为止美国最受欢迎的节目，就像它刚上映时一样。
I was a kid when I came out, I think.
我想，我出来的时候还是个孩子。
I don't, I don't think any show has, like, better acting.
我不，我不认为任何节目都有更好的表演。
It's really good.
这真的很好。
Jesse, we needed to. Cook.
杰西，我们需要。 厨师。
Or they cook all.
或者他们都做饭。
They cook that. OK? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
他们煮那个。 好的？ 耶耶耶。
I was like, wait. Or they actually. They cook.
我当时想，等等。 或者他们实际上。 他们煮食。
No, no. Yeah, they cook.
不，不。 是的，他们做饭。
It's all about a. Fry cook business. Wait, what?
这都是关于一个。 炒厨师业务。 等等，什么？
How do.
怎么做。
We. You got a hold control.
我们。 你有一个保持控制。
Throw it out.
把它扔掉。
Wait.
等待。
Oh, it's got to.
哦，这是必须的。
Oh, you got to put it down. The what?
哦，你必须放下它。 什么？
Wait, what is this?
等等，这是什么？
What's this all?
这都是什么？
I can't throw it because it's cooking.
我不能扔它，因为它正在做饭。
Me. Oh, no, I can't throw it.
我。 哦，不，我不能扔它。
Oh, no, you can. I'm just dumb.
哦，不，你可以。 我只是愚蠢。
What the fuck? It's stupid.
什么鬼？ 这是愚蠢的。
Yet? Wait.
然而？ 等待。
Oh, my God. This is.
我的天啊。 这是。
Yeah, it's not funny. Huh?
是的，这不好笑。 嗯？
Like it's a mushroom.
就像是蘑菇一样。
OK, ok. OK, ok. Never mind. Never mind, never mind.
好的好的。 好的好的。 没关系。 没关系，没关系。
I think I understand not a whole lot of.
我想我理解的不是很多。
Although not your fault, though.
虽然不是你的错。
I think.
我认为。
Any pasta over there.
那里的任何意大利面。
Oh, now you get to of pasta, sir.
哦，现在你要吃意大利面了，先生。
I want.
我想。
Oh, my fucking.
哦，我的他妈的。
Chops. Chop some stuff to get it. Topic get you ready.
排骨。 砍一些东西得到它。 主题让你做好准备。
Yeah, that would be really handy.
是的，那真的很方便。
Fuck me. Oh, my God.
操我。 我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Fuck me.
我的天啊。 操我。
One. Where
一。 在哪里
right after this is done, I'm going to need it for stress relief.
完成后，我将需要它来缓解压力。
OK, bye.
好的，再见。
Anymore pasta was or somewhere over there
意大利面在那边或那边的某个地方
I think.
我认为。
Yeah, yeah. That's when you played it.
是啊是啊。 那是你玩的时候。
You just put it on the thingy
你只是把它放在东西上然后把它寄给我，因为你不能把盘子扔在吃东西的时候，对吧？
We can certainly I call him now.
我们现在当然可以给他打电话了。
On over the mushroom.
在蘑菇上。
Mushroom twice here.
蘑菇在这里两次。
To me, pasta is ready.
对我来说，意大利面已经做好了。
Make another.
再做一个。
I bend it. I'm a fucking dummy.
我弯曲它。 我他妈是个假人。
No. And literally been there. Oh.
不，而且确实去过那里。 哦。
I think every time I need more time to figure that shit out.
我想每次我都需要更多时间来解决这个问题。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Yeah, it's ok. It's OK. This is the. This is the first round.
是的，没关系。 没关系。 这是。 这是第一轮。
This is just the first round. All everything on fire.
这只是第一轮。 一切都在燃烧。
Me, the fire.
我，火。
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
它在哪里？ 它在哪里？ 它在哪里？
Where is the fire? Extinguisher.
火在哪里？ 灭火器。
Hello?
你好？
Oh, there it is.
哦，是的。
Hidden with a mole. I got it.
用痣隐藏。 我得到了它。
Yeah, I.
是的，我。
There goes all the food.
所有的食物都去了。
Is all the food fucked?
所有的食物都搞砸了吗？
Oh, no.
不好了。
I was.
我曾是。
I sent you a dish.
我给你送了一道菜。
Oh, you did send me a dish. Sorry, I didn't.
哦，你确实给我送了一道菜。 对不起，我没有。
I died.
我死了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
OK, this is another scuffed round that's fine.
好的，这是另一个磨损的回合，很好。
OK. All right.
好的。 好的。
I just got a shit throw.
我刚扔了一个狗屎。
OK, negative.
好的，否定的。
60. We are in.
60. 我们在。
We are negative. Down.
我们是消极的。 向下。
Like this is an episode of Kitchen Nightmares.
就像这是厨房噩梦的一集。
You know, we're in Miami.
你知道，我们在迈阿密。
Now, OK? We're in -27 right now.
现在好了？ 我们现在在-27。
Good times seven.
好时光七。
Nice.
好的。
Nice giving back.
很好的回馈。
Like, oh
比如，哦
I'm going to keep throwing stuff
我会继续扔东西
yeah.
是的。
More pasta, more pasta,
更多意大利面，更多意大利面，
more pasta.
更多的意大利面。
All right, that's meat pasta done.
好了，肉面就做好了。
More pasta,
更多意大利面，
more pasta.
更多的意大利面。
Fucking stop.
他妈的停止。
Pasta stop or pasta stop.
面食停止或面食停止。
More now more pasta.
更多现在更多意大利面。
There's too much more pasta.
意大利面太多了。
I think more pasta.
我想更多的意大利面。
They won't let me eat more pasta.
他们不会让我吃更多的意大利面。
More I Yeah.
更多我是的。
-50,000. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I got.
-50,000。 我的天啊。 我的天啊。 我有。
We got negative.
我们得到了否定。
We got to sit this and they look appropriately upset.
我们不得不坐下来，他们看起来很沮丧。
Holy shit.
天啊。
Oh. Oh, what else?
哦。 哦，还有什么？
We sit around from our pogroms round last time
上次我们从大屠杀中坐下来
yeah.
是的。
Negative points. That's crazy, dude.
负分。 这太疯狂了，伙计。
I like that.
我喜欢。
Oh, my God. OK.
我的天啊。 好的。
All right.
好的。
Try this again. Hmm. Hmm, hmm.
再试一次。 唔。 嗯，嗯。
So this time it's all about.
所以这一次就是一切。
Yeah, I will prepare.
是的，我会准备的。
I will just make the dish, and, yeah, you chop it, throw it to me,
我会做这道菜，是的，你把它切碎，扔给我，然后我会把它放在这里。
You can.
你可以。
You can just get these in the
你可以把这些放在花盆里。
Right. Away, and I'll chop.
对。 走开，我会砍。
Actually, no, we don't need meat right now.
实际上，不，我们现在不需要肉。
You need me to
你需要我
mushrooms?
蘑菇？
Yeah.
是的。
Here you go.
干得好。
That's my mushroom.
那是我的蘑菇。
This is.
这是。
I grabbed a meat pocket. Why not?
我抓起一个肉袋。 为什么不？
Here comes another mushroom, sir.
先生，又一个蘑菇来了。
Excellent.
优秀的。
Love me a good love me.
好好爱我爱我。
Love me a sexy mushroom.
爱我一个性感的蘑菇。
Yup. Here comes another meat.
是的。 又来了一块肉。
And you're going to need another mushroom.
你将需要另一个蘑菇。
That's all the ingredients you need right now.
这就是你现在需要的所有成分。
Besides the pasta, I'll send you, I'm sure.
除了意大利面，我肯定会送你的。
Pasta right now.
现在的意大利面。
Here we go. Oh, shit.
开始了。 妈的。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Fuck will happen.
他妈的会发生。
Sorry.
对不起。
I tried to put it on the thing to plate it, and I missed it.
我试图把它放在盘子上，但我错过了。
Panicked
惊慌失措
man. Let me just.
男人。 让我吧。
Do my
做我的
shit for you.
狗屎给你。
Are you feeling it now, Mr. Crabs?
你现在感觉到了吗，螃蟹先生？
Are you feeling. Absolutely.
你有感觉吗。 绝对地。
You feel that this is for you to dish points.
你觉得这是给你的菜点。
You dishes. Or watch out. That's burning
你菜。 或者小心。 那是燃烧
nice.
好的。
Good job. Good job. Which up?
做得好。 做得好。 上哪个？
Your job, your parking, your body and your soul partners.
你的工作，你的停车位，你的身体和你的灵魂伴侣。
Your soul partners. One more. One more. Coming over now.
你的灵魂伴侣。 多一个。 多一个。 现在过来。
Three to four.
三到四。
Oh, my God. You got the dishes for your trouble.
我的天啊。 你拿了盘子来解决你的麻烦。
Three for me.
三个给我。
Holy shit. God.
天啊。 上帝。
Three, three, and one. Go. Delicious.
三、三、一。 去。 美味的。
Nice. That's one.
好的。 那是一个。
That's two.
那是两个。
I could also do with
我也可以和店里的另一个人一起做。
Another mushroom.
另一种蘑菇。
Make sure to also when you do the plates, put them back on the thing. Hmm?
确保在做盘子时也将它们放回物体上。 唔？
Yeah, the plates just came back, so you'll get them on the next run.
是的，盘子刚刚回来，所以你下次运行时会得到它们。
Yep. Yep.
是的。 是的。
That's fine.
没事儿。
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
I have to go.
我得走了。
And do the dishes and then put them put back.
做完盘子再把它们放回去。
I have to put it back.
我必须把它放回去。
I can't throw the plates. You have to put it back on the thing
我不能扔盘子。 你必须把它放回东西上
we aren't doing much about this thing.
我们在这件事上做的不多。
OK, ok. OK.
好的好的。 好的。
You got plates back. You got plates. Are you plates already? Plates already.
你拿回了盘子。 你有盘子。 你已经盘了吗？ 盘子已经。
This one's more pasta.
这个是更多的意大利面。
There we go.
我们去吧。
There you go.
你去吧。
Also, thank you for all the gifts.
另外，谢谢大家的礼物。
OK, there's more pasta.
好的，还有更多的意大利面。
You need put.
你需要放。
On. Hold on, hold on.
在。 等一下，等一下。
All uh.
都呃。
Shit,
拉屎，
shit, shit, shit.
狗屎，狗屎，狗屎。
Shit, shit.
妈的，妈的。
Oh, I don't think we're getting a mushroom one
哦，我不认为我们会得到一个蘑菇
I was about to run out.
我正要跑完。
Fuck you.
去你的。
All right, now we go as one.
好吧，现在我们合而为一。
Some meats.
一些肉。
Plate. Play it up.
盘子。 玩起来。
Meat going on,
肉继续，
pasta
意大利面
that's done.
完成了。
Fuck.
他妈的。
Play, play, play, play, play, play plate.
玩，玩，玩，玩，玩，玩盘。
Yeah. Plates are good.
是的。 盘子很好。
Plates are ready.
盘子准备好了。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Looks so stressful over on that side.
在那边看起来压力很大。
The kitchen is
厨房是
all right.
好的。
Your hands are, like, getting and getting crap. Shit.
你的手，就像，越来越垃圾。 拉屎。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Mushroom pasta done.
香菇意大利面做好了。
Meat pasta.
肉面食。
Done.
完毕。
I'm chilling.
我不寒而栗。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That the I took a glance over what.
那我看了一眼什么。
You had to do off is just, like, so chaotic.
你不得不做的只是，就像，如此混乱。
Mike, this game is like this
迈克，这场比赛就像这场比赛就像一场漫长的比赛
just series of events where one player has to do everything in the other place.
只是一系列事件，其中一个玩家必须在另一个地方做所有事情。
Yeah, because last round, it was me, like, suffering on the other.
是的，因为上一轮，是我，就像，在另一边受苦。
Yeah, it was.
是的，是的。
And now it's now.
现在就是现在。
It's now the customer has come around.
现在客户已经过来了。
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, this is all.
我的意思是，这就是全部。
I mean, this is, you know, it's like we start teaching.
我的意思是，这就像我们开始教学一样。
I saw what's exactly the stress of the kitchen.
我看到了厨房的压力究竟是什么。
When we're getting.
当我们得到。
Lubricated and caffeinated.
润滑和含咖啡因。
We're at we're actually.
我们实际上是。
Yeah, we are actually getting getting looped up and ready for what comes next.
是的，我们实际上正在为接下来的事情做好准备。
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你，先生。
Here's your mushroom.
这是你的蘑菇。
I'm on top of it this time.
这次我在上面。
Here's something we have some meats here.
这是我们这里有一些肉的东西。
Well, I'm
好吧，我很高兴你能享受一次在某事之上的幻想。
What the fuck? But.
什么鬼？ 但。
Oh, no, no, no, it's fine. It's fine. Keep walking. Come on.
哦，不，不，不，这很好。 没关系。 继续走。 来吧。
Come on, now. We're in the kitchen now. Tell me, what was that?
来吧，现在。 我们现在在厨房里。 告诉我，那是什么？
Was that comments?
那是评论吗？
Was that kind of not important?
那不重要吗？
Not relevant to the kitchen? Come on.
与厨房无关？ 来吧。
You're lucky.
你很幸运。
I'm. I'm stranded on this side of the side of the kitchen.
我是。 我被困在厨房的这一边。
I was. I'll come. Over for you over there on my.
我曾是。 我会来。 在我那边给你。
Bed. You over on the counter opened you over in the counter.
床。 你在柜台上打开了你在柜台上。
Oh, I'd like to see you fucking try.
哦，我想看你他妈的试试。
I'd like to see you fucking try. I'll put you in the ground.
我想看你他妈的试试。 我会把你放在地上。
Very literally.
非常字面意思。
Quite 1000 feet above the ground.
离地面1000英尺。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
I don't think that's happening any time soon. Sorry.
我认为这不会很快发生。 对不起。
That's not going to happen.
这不会发生。
That's how I. Look at that.
我就是这样。看那个。
Oh, good job.
哦，干得好。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Send more pasta over.
送更多的意大利面。
There you go.
你去吧。
Is your noodles
你的面条是
guys?
伙计们？
Trust me, one of these days on blocks is going to be the one barking for me.
相信我，在街区的这些日子之一将是我吠叫的日子。
It'll. It'll get there.
会的。 它会到达那里。
We'll get there. Keep dreaming going. Keep dreaming.
我们会到达那里。 继续做梦。 继续做梦。
I don't have to dream on the bigger reality.
我不必梦想更大的现实。
All right, prove it.
好吧，证明它。
All right.
好的。
I will give it, like.
我会给它，喜欢。
Even a couple more.
甚至更多。
I like. I like.
我喜欢。 我喜欢。
I like this one. Can you, boy, I like this one.
我喜欢这一个。 你可以吗，男孩，我喜欢这个。
Can you keep that going?
你能坚持下去吗？
And we'll see and we'll see what we'll see what happens.
我们会看到，我们会看到我们会看到会发生什么。
All right. Remember to wash your fucking dishes. Yeah.
好的。 记得洗你他妈的盘子。 是的。
I'm watching you right now. I'm watching right now.
我现在正在看着你。 我现在正在看。
I could get at least one box here.
我在这里至少可以得到一个盒子。
Yeah, I could get one back to you before it flies back.
是的，我可以在它飞回来之前把它还给你。
You shit, man.
你个屁，伙计。
Do you need more pasta?
你需要更多的意大利面吗？
Uh, yes, please. OK.
嗯，是的，请。 好的。
All right. I'm going to shop more.
好的。 我要去购物了。
We go mushroom passed it on.
我们去蘑菇传递它。
Let's do, like.
让我们做，就像。
We'll plate these.
我们会把这些盘起来。
These it's
这些就是
such a shot.
这样的镜头。
We go.
我们去。
OK. Three plates.
好的。 三盘。
Three plates are coming for you right now at the ready.
三个盘子正在为您准备就绪。
Excellent.
优秀的。
Good boy.
好孩子。
Here you go.
干得好。
And here you go.
给你。
To mushroom passes. Come on over.
蘑菇通行证。 过来吧。
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
是的先生。 是的先生。 是的先生。 是的先生。
We got one minute left, by the way.
顺便说一句，我们还剩一分钟。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
My left, one mil left.
我的左边，还剩一百万。
POG, pog, pog
咕咕咕咕咕咕
pissing in our over
尿在我们身上
go, sir.
去吧，先生。
I mean, chef. Yes, Chef. Sorry, Chef. Don't.
我的意思是，厨师。 是的，厨师。 对不起，厨师。 不。
Don't worry, chef. Please don't fuck me, Chef.
别担心，厨师。 请不要操我，厨师。
I'm sorry, Chef.
对不起，厨师。
I'm sorry, chef. Whatever you want. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起，厨师。 无论你想要什么。 对不起。 对不起。
I like that you told us what you want.
我喜欢你告诉我们你想要什么。
Oh, we lost points. Damn it.
哦，我们丢分了。 该死的。
Oh. That's fine.
哦。 没事儿。
I fucking binge.
我他妈暴饮暴食。
I'm dumb twice.
我傻了两次。
I'm a dumb fuck.
我是个笨蛋。
All your ads on all your ads on voice.
你所有的广告都在你所有的语音广告上。
I was. Rushing off.
我曾是。 匆匆离去。
I was rushing out.
我冲出去了。
Don't let it get. To the convoy.
不要让它得到。 到车队。
Don't let it get to your fucking head all the. Way
不要让它完全进入你的脑袋。 方式
through the order down the bin right there.
通过那里的垃圾箱的订单。
Yeah, I think we made it all.
是的，我想我们做到了。
Do we made it or do we have to get 480?
我们成功了还是必须得到480？
Please, please.
请，请。
It's costing. Things.
这是成本。 事物。
But yeah, we did. Yeah.
但是，是的，我们做到了。 是的。
Let's go, all of you.
走吧，你们所有人。
That's your vessel -30. Shit.
那是你的船-30。 拉屎。
Yeah, we did see it.
是的，我们确实看到了。
It just barely just barely.
它只是勉强。
Fuck yeah.
他妈的是的。
Hey. Yeah,
嘿。 是的，
you know, for a while you did really well there.
你知道，有一段时间你在那里做得很好。
They really well back there.
他们真的很好。
You'll do a sexy.
你会做一个性感的。
Yes, I bet your arse was really out too little.
是的，我敢打赌你的屁股真的太少了。
It's not. Very much.
它不是。 非常。
The way you handle those mushrooms, the way you toss it up, will you?
你处理这些蘑菇的方式，你把它扔掉的方式，你会吗？
Caressed that meat while you plated it.
在你装盘的时候抚摸着那块肉。
Beautiful plating, beautiful technique.
漂亮的电镀，漂亮的工艺。
So you're saying I'm not a stupid little boy then?
所以你是说我不是一个愚蠢的小男孩？
I mean, you're still stupid little boy by me.
我的意思是，你仍然是我的愚蠢的小男孩。
That doesn't mean I can't compliment you on your clothes.
这并不意味着我不能赞美你的衣服。
Ha ha ha ha ha ha. All right, all right.
哈哈哈哈哈哈。 好吧，好吧。
OK, here we go. Now.
好的，我们开始吧。 现在。
I don't actually know all we can do. We
我实际上并不知道我们能做什么。 我们喜欢这个地方。
What the fuck are we?
我们他妈是什么？
Look. What is that? The catch up dimension.
看。 那是什么？ 追赶维度。
The catch up.
赶上来。
Woven the dwarven mineshaft burritos.
编织矮人矿井卷饼。
We got to make burritos. Wow.
我们要做墨西哥卷饼。 哇。
Get some of that chocolate and salt or that.
拿一些巧克力和盐或者那个。
Make it take a tortilla, add cooked rice, then add fried chicken.
做一个玉米饼，加入米饭，然后加入炸鸡。
Meat or mushroom or.
肉或蘑菇或。
Everything looks cool down the earth.
地球上的一切看起来都很凉爽。
Oh. Hey.
哦。 嘿。
What the fuck do I boil.
我他妈的要煮什么。
Rice over here?
大米在这里？
Let me. Let me see you. The rice.
让我来。 让我看看你。 米饭。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
Yeah, yeah. You got to ask me. It's awesome rice here.
是啊是啊。 你得问我。 这里的米饭很棒。
I think you've got to go.
我想你得走了。
I'll toss you off.
我会把你扔掉。
Oh. Well, I mean,
哦。 嗯，我的意思是，
I'm in front of them.
我在他们面前。
In front of all these people.
在所有这些人面前。
You just be one
你只是一个
God. Always so embarrassing.
上帝。 总是那么尴尬。
You guys do this OK?
你们这样做好吗？
So what are you doing?
那么你正在做什么？
Step bro. Gaming.
步哥。 赌博。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
You do it down the hallway.
你在走廊里做。
Purely fucking gaming.
纯他妈的游戏。
I need.
我需要。
I need the cooked mushroom and the cooked meats.
我需要煮熟的蘑菇和煮熟的肉。
Oh, this is I. This is a dud. I fucked it up.
哦，这是我。这是一个哑巴。 我搞砸了。
What do you need?
你需要什么？
You need another mushroom, sir.
你需要另一个蘑菇，先生。
Possibly, sir.
可能，先生。
I'm Musharraf.
我是穆沙拉夫。
Chef. Chef, owner, please.
厨师。 厨师，老板，请。
Oh. No, no. It's not a problem.
哦。 不，不。 这不成问题。
Is problem with me. Not a problem with me or look for me.
是我的问题。 不是我的问题或找我。
Is there anything you'd like? One.
你有什么想要的吗？ 一。
Just. Just throw the meat on.
只是。 把肉扔进去就行了。
You can get those.
你可以得到那些。
I'll send it over. Here you go.
我会寄过去的。 干得好。
OK. OK, ok, ok. OK.
好的。 好好好。 好的。
Now, now that we've explored this a bit, we can establish the roles.
现在，既然我们已经对此进行了一些探索，我们就可以建立角色了。
Oh, time is not going.
哦，时间过不去。
That was it. Time right now.
就是这样。 现在是时候了。
Because I guess this is oil. It's teaching us how to do it.
因为我猜这是石油。 它正在教我们如何去做。
And now all.
现在所有。
We do first, as.
我们先做。
Soon as the first order goes out, it starts.
第一个订单一发出，就开始了。
OK, ok. OK, that makes sense.
好的好的。 好的，这是有道理的。
That makes sense.
这就说得通了。
There is a gift sub war happening in my shop right now.
我的商店现在正在发生一场礼物分战。
Who's going the crazy?
谁在发疯？
I wish I. Did well then.
我希望我当时做得很好。
I wish I could say thank you, but we are panicked and to actively gaming.
我希望我能说声谢谢，但我们很恐慌并积极参与游戏。
I mean, if you want, take a break to go and address that chill for you, ok?
我的意思是，如果您愿意，请休息一下，为您解决寒冷，好吗？
You sturdy plates.
你坚固的盘子。
Eight plates from a dirty boy.
一个肮脏男孩的八个盘子。
I'll have you know I shower.
我会让你知道我洗澡。
Every every evening.
每天晚上。
I'm a are you a night shower or a morning shower?
我是你是晚上淋浴还是早上淋浴？
I'm a morning shower myself.
我自己就是一个早上的淋浴。
That was.
那是。
Really. You got a bad one. It's all smelly.
真的。 你有一个坏的。 都是臭的。
Sometimes I'll do only two in the day, to be honest.
老实说，有时我一天只做两个。
I like I like an evening shower.
我喜欢我喜欢晚上淋浴。
Evening shower is a nice
晚上淋浴很不错
but there are luxury, you know, you're not busy.
但也有奢侈，你知道，你不忙。
Oh, that's true. Yeah.
哦，那是真的。 是的。
I need rice, by the way. I haven't gotten any rice.
顺便说一句，我需要米饭。 我没有吃米饭。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
I look
我看
rice. Yup.
白饭。 是的。
Rice,
米，
fog, rice.
雾，米。
OK, also, here you go.
好的，还有，给你。
Like you.
喜欢你。
Throw plate on the floor.
把盘子扔在地板上。
When you.
当你。
Rice is going in. Rice is going in.
大米进来了。大米进来了。
That was the mushroom burrito.
那是蘑菇卷饼。
OK, I'm sending this out and I need more rice and believe
好的，我把这个寄出去，我需要更多的米饭，相信
more rice.
更多的米饭。
Gotcha.
明白了。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
You know, it's ready.
你知道，它已经准备好了。
We got a plate, but.
我们有一个盘子，但是。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yeah.
是的。
So I'll just I'll just bring over, like, fried veg and meat and stuff to you.
所以我会只是我会带给你，比如，油炸蔬菜和肉之类的东西给你。
Thank you. If you. Bring me the plates.
谢谢你。 如果你。 把盘子给我。
We got the throw it, you dog.
我们得到了扔它，你的狗。
Rice throwing and talking to myself.
大米扔和自言自语。
Medium dog
中型犬
oh, god.
天啊。
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, cook faster.
快点，快点，快点，快点，快点做饭。
Rice, please.
米饭，请。
Let me, let me do the dishes.
让我，让我洗碗。
Oh, just in time.
哦，正好。
Carry some rice.
带点米饭。
I'll grab this
我会抓住这个
here. Drop it.
这里。 算了吧。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
And I'll put that up.
我会提出来的。
And I need more rice.
我需要更多的米饭。
Any more rice is up.
再有米饭了。
It's up
起来了
thank you for
谢谢你的家人。
Dude, I didn't expect to throw it.
伙计，我没想到会扔它。
I got fumbled.
我摸不着头脑。
Should you give me some mushrooms?
你应该给我一些蘑菇吗？
Yeah, actually, we got rush.
是的，实际上，我们很着急。
Yeah, if you just put rice in that any done.
是的，如果你把米饭放进去就可以了。
Yeah, i got it.
是的，我明白了。
I got. We need meat now. The other meat's cooked. The meat cooked. Right?
我有。 我们现在需要肉。 另一块肉煮熟了。 肉煮熟了。 对？
That was that was my bad. I didn't mean that.
那是我的错。 我不是那个意思。
It's done. It's done. It's done. It's done. Think
它完成了。 完成。 它完成了。 它完成了。 思考
shit.
拉屎。
You got
你得到了
this one's not that bad.
这个还不错。
Actually, we just got to get a rhythm going.
实际上，我们只需要找到节奏即可。
Yeah, we just got it.
是的，我们刚刚得到它。
We just got to figure out what each person is doing.
我们只需要弄清楚每个人在做什么。
What OK.
什么好。
Let's. We might even get a first. Right.
让我们。 我们甚至可能获得第一个。 对。
It's only six points to get through. Okay.
只有六分才能通过。 好的。
Any more rice? Any more rice ASAP?
还有米饭吗？ 有更多的米饭尽快吗？
One second.
一秒。
Oh, wait.
等一下。
Is this not cooked? It's not cooked.
这不是煮熟的吗？ 它没有煮熟。
Oh, shit. Really? Hold on.
妈的。 真的吗？ 坚持，稍等。
I'll grab this one of those ones cocked.
我会抓住其中一个翘起的。
OK, I think we can get.
好的，我想我们可以得到。
I think we can do it.
我认为我们可以做到。
OK, now
现在没事了
I just need one more off fuck and one more rice can do our time.
我只需要再吃一口，再吃一粒米饭就可以了。
Our time
我们的时间
to coordinate this.
来协调这一点。
We coordinate the small.
我们协调小。
Possibly it is lights.
可能是灯。
Mushroom, mushroom, mushroom on.
蘑菇，蘑菇，蘑菇上。
Mushroom on. OK.
蘑菇上。 好的。
A mushroom.
一个蘑菇。
I I di.
我我去。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Rice wasn't so fucking close.
赖斯没那么他妈的接近。
Oh, man. I would have been so close.
天啊。 我会如此接近。
Actually, we just fucked up two orders. Oh, my God.
实际上，我们只是搞砸了两个订单。 我的天啊。
We did so well done.
我们做得很好。
Yeah, it's fucking crazy.
是的，这太他妈疯狂了。
It's rock n roll.
这是摇滚乐。
Look at eights.
看八字。
Look, look, look, look.
看，看，看，看。
What I love. This is in the pan.
我爱什么。 这是在锅里。
Look at Ed's.
看看艾德的。
Look, look, look.
看，看，看。
Love.
爱。
His voice cracks.
他的声音沙哑。
My favourite, my favourite one.
我的最爱，我最喜欢的一个。
My favourite one.
我最喜欢的一个。
Is you cook it in a burnt pan, you fuck dick,
你是在烧焦的平底锅里煮的吗，你他妈的鸡巴，
you fucking. Dig
你他妈 挖
oh. And you just.
哦。 而你只是。
Oh, a slice of mouldy tomato.
哦，一片发霉的番茄。
He said that before he did.
他在做之前就这么说了。
And, like, it's like in the second episode.
而且，就像第二集中一样。
Have you ever seen that one? It's like the what's it called?
你见过那个吗？ 就像它叫什么？
It's Dillon's the Indian restaurant in New York,
这是狄龙在纽约的印度餐厅，
and it's where, like, there are flies in the thing,
就像，里面有苍蝇，还有那个奇怪的，令人毛骨悚然的经理等等。
It's like, that was that was a classic episode. Those little.
就像，那是一个经典的插曲。 那些小。
Huh. OK, rice pizza, rice.
嗯。 好的，米饭披萨，米饭。
Right, right. Yeah. On a plate.
是的是的。 是的。 在盘子上。
And you put the 30.
你把30。
Just throw a few things the rice over to you so you'd have to worry.
把米饭扔给你几样东西，你就不用担心了。
Yeah, I'd be really healthy.
是的，我会很健康的。
Three or so to start their orders.
三人左右开始他们的订单。
Here's your mushrooms.
这是你的蘑菇。
Thank you. It's your veggies.
谢谢你。 这是你的蔬菜。
Eat your veggies, your fungus.
吃你的蔬菜，你的真菌。
Whatever you veg.
不管你吃什么蔬菜。
OK, OK.
好的好的。
Now I'm just waiting on the mushroom and meet.
现在我只是在等待蘑菇和见面。
These two are ready. Are here already OK?
这两个已经准备好了。 这里已经OK了吗？
What's he doing there? Yeah, that's right. He played up.
他在那里做什么？ 是的，没错。 他玩了起来。
Yeah, played it up.
是的，玩过。
And then this is ready. To all go.
然后就准备好了。 都去吧。
Y'all look at us.
你们都看着我们。
Y'all look at that synergy give me more rice and more rice.
你们都看看那种协同作用，给我更多的米饭和更多的米饭。
More, more, more. More, more.
更多更多更多。 更多，更多。
Here we go.
开始了。
There we go.
我们去吧。
Look at us. Go.
看着我们。 去。
Look up. Go.
抬头。 去。
Holy shit. Hold on, hold on, hold on. I'll meet you.
天啊。 坚持，坚持，坚持。 我会来见你。
I'll put the dirty, dirty plates out here.
我会把脏脏的盘子放在这里。
I'm good. Grab your meat.
我很好。 抓住你的肉。
I grab my meat.
我抓住我的肉。
Grab me while I'm grabbing your meat.
在我抓你肉的时候抓住我。
I'm squeezing it.
我正在挤压它。
Saying out to the customers.
对顾客说。
Go mushroom.
去蘑菇。
Go. That is cooking.
去。 那就是做饭。
And OK, here we go.
好的，我们开始吧。
Let's
让我们
go and
去和
the whole meat thing. OK?
整个肉的东西。 好的？
Oh, where's the where's the frying pan?
哦，煎锅在哪里？
Can you bring the frying pan back, please?
请把煎锅拿回来好吗？
Oh, yeah, yeah. Frying pan frying pan.
哦，是的，是的。 煎锅煎锅。
Here you go.
干得好。
I'll leave out there.
我会离开那里。
I'll just grab rice warm here.
我只会在这里拿热饭。
Fuck it.
去他妈的。
Yeah, I'll there.
是的，我会在那里。
I get. The new that we have here.
我明白了。 我们这里有新的。
We're destroying this one.
我们正在摧毁这个。
Grab the rice, grab the racial,
抢米，抢种族，抢米
and go send another this and another mushroom over to your side.
去把另一个这个和另一个蘑菇送到你身边。
I think you might need that.
我想你可能需要那个。
Cute.
可爱的。
Q OK, here's more dirty dishes.
Q 好的，这里还有更多脏盘子。
Oh, she just died. Oh, my. I had my edition.
哦，她刚刚死了。 天啊。 我有我的版本。
I can't put my finger down on the fucking up arrow, and I'm using wires instead.
我无法将手指放在他妈的向上箭头上，而我正在使用电线。
Wires wise
电线明智这是一个很好的技能。
Nice. So I'm using your one.
好的。 所以我用的是你的。
Shut your mouth, shut your fucking.
闭嘴，闭嘴。
Shut your mouth.
闭上你的嘴。
Remember.
记住。
There's so much sexual tension whenever we collide.
每当我们发生冲突时，都会有如此多的性紧张。
Why is this? Why is that the case? I don't. Know.
为什么是这样？ 为什么会这样？ 我不。 知道。
I couldn't tell.
我说不出来。
I'm not complaining, though.
不过，我没有抱怨。
I put. Yeah, no, I mean me.
我放。 是的，不，我是说我。
I just come so naturally.
我就这么自然而然地来了。
I don't know what you do to me, sir, but
先生，我不知道你对我做了什么，但你每次都让它出来。
Just comes out every single time we call up.
每次我们打电话时都会出来。
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, I don't know what I do to you either.
我的意思是，我也不知道我对你做了什么。
I'll do it.
我会做的。
I'll do more of it.
我会做更多。
You talking like that, though?
不过你这么说话？
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh. Oh, hold on, hold on. I'll fix that.
哦。 哦，等一下，等一下。 我会解决的。
Oh, God, bro.
哦，天哪，兄弟。
OK, I need more rice,
好的，我需要更多的米饭，更多的米饭，更多的米饭，更多的米饭。
I think.
我认为。
One of the rice fell and.
其中一粒米掉了下来。
Projectile rice.
弹米。
I think I need meat.
我想我需要肉。
Is there cooked meat over there?
那边有熟肉吗？
There is cooked meat ready for you?
有熟肉给你准备好了吗？
OK, I'll grab it all.
好的，我会全部抓住。
Yeah, yeah. Any meat?
是啊是啊。 有肉吗？
Any meat? Real bad. And another rice.
有肉吗？ 真糟糕。 还有一个米饭。
I need another rice ASAP.
我需要尽快再来一份米饭。
And one more rice.
再来一份米饭。
Gotcha.
明白了。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Thank you, sir.
谢谢你，先生。
Four, six, six, six.
四，六，六，六。
And that's here.
这就是这里。
That's your lucky number, isn't it?
那是你的幸运数字，不是吗？
It is.
这是。
It is. And there we go. We do.
这是。 我们开始了。 我们的确是。
Clearly, we're going to win this.
显然，我们将赢得这场比赛。
Toss me a shroom.
给我一个蘑菇。
Toss me a shroom boy.
扔给我一个蘑菇男孩。
Sir. Sherm, hold on. Here we go.
先生。 谢尔姆，等等。 开始了。
Here's my mushroom.
这是我的蘑菇。
I want so badly.
我非常想要。
And I think we're good here.
我认为我们在这里很好。
I just think. Meats, more meats.
我只是想。 肉，更多的肉。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
It's a dirty dish. The inside of the meat.
这是一道脏菜。 肉的里面。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I died of the meat.
我死于肉。
That's incredible.
这是令人难以置信。
Oh, it can't be dying with my meat.
哦，它不能和我的肉一起死。
Can you not?
你能不？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Can you let me do what I need to do?
你能让我做我需要做的吗？
I was scared.
我被吓到了。
I saw the meat.
我看到了肉。
I saw the meat burning or, like, the mushroom burning on.
我看到肉在燃烧，或者，就像蘑菇在燃烧。
I'll grab that ASAP.
我会尽快抓住它。
And then you just worry about the other stuff.
然后你只担心其他的事情。
I think. I think we got this.
我认为。 我想我们得到了这个。
OK, we got this.
好的，我们得到了这个。
Five, four, one modish one more high school.
五、四、一新一更高中。
High school.
中学。
To want.
想要。
No, no. We got we still got three strikes.
不，不。 我们得到了我们仍然得到了三个罢工。
You're still with. Us?
你还在。 我们？
Yeah. We still good
是的。 我们现在的赔率仍然很高。 没事。
It's like.
它像是。
Oh, my God. Oh,
我的天啊。 哦，
that wasn't so bad.
那还不错。
Like we said. Yeah, I said.
就像我们说的。 是的，我说。
Good job.
做得好。
Yeah, baby. Oh,
是的，宝贝。 哦，
by the way, what.
顺便说一句，什么。
Happens to your apron idea.
发生在你的围裙想法上。
Is what apron?
是什么围裙？
Where do you go. From wearing it?
你去哪里。 从穿着它？
Oh, you're wearing it yeah.
哦，你穿着它是的。
All right.
好的。
I can't see it, but. Yeah.
我看不到，但是。 是的。
Yeah. No way. I didn't mean to do that.
是的。 没门。 我不是故意的。
Would I keep doing that?
我会继续这样做吗？
My my brain is just like, all right.
我的大脑就像，好吧。
We've failed. We have to go to the other one.
我们失败了。 我们必须去另一个。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm like.
我长得像。
Is is Libby blueberry is debateable right now.
是不是利比蓝莓现在是有争议的。
Let me birdie woman's mating via eight. No.
让我通过八位小鸟女交配。 不。
We haven't cooked a single burger in a lot.
我们已经很久没有煮过一个汉堡了。
I can't believe we haven't.
我不敢相信我们没有。
Bought their burger.
买了他们的汉堡。
But we get.
但我们得到。
In some french fries.
在一些炸薯条中。
Oh, no.
不好了。
We have cooked french fries. Burger,
我们做了炸薯条。 汉堡包，
no burger.
没有汉堡。
Barely
仅仅
an apple.
苹果。
When you tickle someone's.
当你挠别人的时候。
Balls, you imagine like it goes like
球，你想象它会像
like that. No.
像那样。 不。
Believe it or not, no.
信不信由你，不。
It's a it's a very valid question I had to ask.
这是一个我不得不问的非常有效的问题。
Oh, my God, this is confusing.
哦，我的上帝，这令人困惑。
This is confusing already.
这已经令人困惑了。
I think I should handle the rice as usual.
我想我应该像往常一样处理米饭。
Oh, no.
不好了。
You got to be shitting me.
你一定是在骗我。
Why are you fucking my dick?
你为什么要操我的鸡巴？
Do we really have to, like, alternate.
我们真的必须，比如，交替。
Between ingredients. Like that?
成分之间。 像那样？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I'm already stretched out.
我已经被拉长了。
I'm overstressed until I.
我压力过大，直到我。
We haven't even started.
我们甚至还没有开始。
You decided to just.
你决定只是。
Oh, I stood there and it all.
哦，我站在那里，这一切。
I will take it all now.
我现在就把它全部拿走。
OK, there's meats right there.
好的，那里有肉。
There's more meats.
还有更多的肉。
Are we don't need that meat right now.
我们现在不需要那种肉吗？
I mean, this meat's
我是说，这肉
wait,
等待，
wait.
等待。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的，是的，是的，是的。
And then you need the broth.
然后你需要肉汤。
The meat survived. The meat survived.
肉活了下来。 肉活了下来。
Dude. Pug, wait. While the meat outlived me.
老兄。 帕格，等等。 虽然肉比我长寿。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I need the burrito, the tortilla tortilla thingy,
我需要墨西哥卷饼，玉米饼玉米饼，
and then another tortilla.
然后是另一个玉米饼。
Grab the tortilla.
抓住玉米饼。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
There's so much happening.
发生了很多事情。
Yeah.
是的。
I'm hyperventilating.
我正在过度换气。
I want to go home.
我想回家。
Is this really worth saving?
这真的值得保存吗？
The kingdom over.
王国结束。
Oh, cranberry.
哦，蔓越莓。
As in this weird of an environment.
就像在这种奇怪的环境中一样。
I'm going to. OK.
我要去。 好的。
Wow. I know what that means.
哇。 我知道那是什么意思。
They got are all markets.
他们得到的都是市场。
Oh, brother.
哦，兄弟。
Got it.
知道了。
OK, we got more and more plates ready
好的，我们准备了越来越多的盘子
and then I put two rice in.
然后我放了两粒米饭。
No, that's fucking chicken.
不，那是他妈的鸡。
Jessie
杰西
are going to repeat
会重复
due to.
由于。
All I know is rice. Oh,
我只知道米饭。 哦，
OK. Those are cooking now.
好的。 那些现在正在做饭。
What? How?
什么？ 如何？
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
We filled your mom filled.
我们填满了你妈妈。
Like, got
喜欢，得到
cooking.
烹饪。
Dude. Oh, shit.
老兄。 妈的。
Oh, shit is ok.
哦，狗屎还行。
It's not looking so as a burrito.
它看起来不像墨西哥卷饼。
It's not. It's not looking so hot.
它不是。 它看起来不那么热。
I fall off.
我掉下来。
Dude, I was looking at you and I thought
伙计，我看着你，我想
you're working.
你在工作。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
Oh, fuck me. Oh, fuck, dammit.
哦，操我。 哦，他妈的，该死的。
Well, ok.
好吧，好吧。
OK, ok. OK. OK.
好的好的。 好的。 好的。
I think we do.
我想我们会的。
We just lose a saucepan forever.
我们只是永远失去了一个平底锅。
No, it comes back.
不，它回来了。
It comes back.
它回来了。
OK, hang on, hang on. Hang on.
好的，等一下，等一下。 不挂断。
Where's the fire extinguisher?
灭火器在哪里？
Fire extinguisher.
灭火器。
OK. All right.
好的。 好的。
Seems it seems like. All they. All like.
好像好像。 他们都是。 都喜欢。
Everything is is everything is going to shit.
一切都是一切都会变得糟糕。
Oh, it seems like everything's gone to shit, right?
哦，好像一切都变糟了，对吧？
Googly moodily everything's gone to fucking hell.
Googly 喜怒无常，一切都他妈的地狱。
I don't know what's the deal.
我不知道这是什么交易。
I don't know what the deal.
我不知道有什么交易。
Do something, you fucking idiot.
做点什么，你个白痴。
We're Fox or fox, bro.
我们是狐狸还是狐狸，兄弟。
I know what to do.
我知道要做什么。
Oh, fuck you.
哦，去你妈的。
Yeah.
是的。
You ever, ever stop moving in my kitchen like that again.
你永远，永远不要再像那样在我的厨房里移动。
I'll send you over and make you wish you was sorry.
我会把你送过去，让你希望你很抱歉。
Oh. You make it really, really hard.
哦。 你真的，真的很难。
Not so what I take the offer.
我接受的提议并非如此。
Is that what I'm trying to say? No.
这就是我想说的吗？ 不。
To obey, maybe.
服从，也许。
Laugh now
现在笑
now, for now, we focus on the cooking.
现在，现在，我们专注于烹饪。
All right?
好的？
Yeah. Sorry, we. Got. Plus, I got philosophy this time.
是的。 对不起，我们。 拿到。 另外，这次我得到了哲学。
I got flustered this time. Dude, the noise, the mechanics.
这次我慌了。 老兄，噪音，机械。
I don't talk to you again.
我不再和你说话了。
I'm just go grab.
我只是去抢。
All the rice that's necessary.
所有必要的米饭。
Oh, no.
不好了。
You grab all the rice
你抢了所有的米饭
the rice.
米饭。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
OK, I'll put the rice on immediately.
好的，我马上把米饭放上去。
OK, I'll start.
好的，我要开始了。
I'll start cooking the chicken in the meat.
我将开始在肉里煮鸡肉。
In the dude.
在伙计里。
He doesn't like
他不喜欢
having chicken and meat on that side. OK.
那边有鸡肉和肉。 好的。
I'll start. I'll start chopping.
我会开始的。 我要开始砍了。
Chop, chop, chop.
剁，剁，剁。
Are you ready for another little of meat?
你准备好再吃一点肉了吗？
Rice is done playing that up.
赖斯玩完了。
And throw these over.
把这些扔过去。
I think I see what I have to do now.
我想我明白我现在必须做什么了。
I know what I.
我知道我是什么。
Have to do.
必须做。
OK, these these are all cooking.
好的，这些都是做饭的。
These are all cooking right now.
这些现在都在做饭。
Wait throw those over there.
等着把那些扔在那里。
All right,
好的，
OK. This is.
好的。 这是。
Ready. No.
准备好。 不。
Yeah, yeah, you can. You can turn that. You can stand that.
是的，是的，你可以。 你可以转那个。 你受得了。
You can stand all over. Yeah, actually now.
你可以站起来。 是的，其实现在。
OK, if you focus, like, if you do that one well, let's go step one. Each
好吧，如果你专注，比如，如果你做得好，让我们迈出第一步。 每个
chicken done.
鸡肉做好了。
OK, let's get the rice is giving us a bang.
好的，让我们吃米饭吧。
But you got to rest. You have the rice, ok?
但是你要休息。 你有米饭，好吗？
OK. Yeah, if I can. Wait, wait.
好的。 是的，如果可以的话。 等等。
Let me just grab those.
让我抓住那些。
This chicken's ready. I'm going to chop more chopped, more meat
这只鸡做好了。 我要切更多切碎的，更多的肉
and I'm going to send that over to the grill.
我要把它送到烤架上。
I'm going to cook more chicken as well.
我还要煮更多的鸡肉。
Just a bunch of chicken
只是一堆鸡输了。
Wow. I wasn't
哇。 我不是
I think I got something going here.
我想我有什么事情发生在这里。
You have something special.
你有一些特别的东西。
You got something?
你有东西吗？
Something special, Dave?
有什么特别的吗，戴夫？
Yeah.
是的。
I wish I could flip back, but I'm concentrating.
我希望我能回头，但我正在集中注意力。
White rice. Rice.
白米。 米。
I'll get your rice ready.
我会为你准备好米饭。
I'll put some rice. And for you
我会放一些米饭。 而对于这里的你，你
I think my meat disappeared.
我想我的肉不见了。
OK. Ah!
好的。 啊!
Oh, my. God. There's so much. There's dirty plates, right?
天啊。 上帝。 有这么多。 有脏盘子，对吧？
We got to watch out for the dirty plates.
我们得小心那些脏盘子。
Fuck go.
去他妈的。
We need. We need burrito.
我们需要。 我们需要墨西哥卷饼。
I got to I'll need a break.
我到了，我需要休息一下。
Yeah, I'll be. I'll be the hero.
是的，我会的。 我将成为英雄。
I'll be the the the Barry tearoom.
我将成为巴里茶室。
The Barry hero.
巴里英雄。
Here, I'll throw another one out.
在这里，我将再扔一个。
You all throw another one. Fuck me.
你们都再扔一个。 操我。
Grab it, grab it.
抓住它，抓住它。
Graphic wow.
图形哇。
OK, this one's hard.
好吧，这个很难。
This one's, like, actually pretty damn hard.
这个，就像，实际上非常难。
Yeah. Yeah.
是的。 是的。
Well, you don't use timing hard on.
好吧，你不要用力计时。
You're acting like.
你表现得像。
That's beside the point, sir.
先生，那是无关紧要的。
Chef. Fuck you.
厨师。 去你的。
Such that.
这样。
Just shut up about that.
就闭嘴吧。
There are a.
有一个。
Few more dishes.
还有几道菜。
Oh, no VOCs.
哦，没有挥发性有机化合物。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, oh, no. Oh,
哦，哦，不。 哦，
Oh, I. There's so many.
哦，我。有这么多。
The bridesmaids. Wear. Them.
伴娘们。 穿。 他们。
Give me the fucking. Lights.
给我他妈的。 灯。
And cleaning. I'm cleaning the plates, chef.
和清洁。 我在擦盘子，厨师。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Bang!
砰!
Three, three, three.
三，三，三。
Yeah. Oh, dude.
是的。 哦，伙计。
Rigging belts by this one.
用这个系腰带。
All right, let's absolutely.
好吧，让我们绝对。
100 more points. We failed three orders.
还有100分。 我们失败了三个订单。
So as long as we don't do that
因此，只要我们不这样做并且我们真正专注于我们正在做的事情，我们就可以使这一工作发挥作用。
and we actually focus on what we're doing, we can make this one work. OK.
好的。
Y'all, we had it.
你们，我们有它。
We had in the beginning.
我们一开始就有。
Then all of a sudden, it just slips away.
然后突然间，它就溜走了。
Yeah.
是的。
All of a sudden, shutters meet, disappeared.
突然，百叶窗相遇，消失了。
I mean, you fell down the
我的意思是，你跌倒了，直到我成为真实的东西。
I'm going to holes. You.
我要去坑了。 你。
I like holes.
我喜欢坑。
I'm sorry that I keep falling into your hole, but.
对不起，我一直掉进你的洞里，但是。
My hole is maybe.
我的洞可能是。
Maybe it's not much.
也许不多。
If you were our.
如果你是我们的。
It's our whole share. Oh.
这是我们的全部份额。 哦。
It's our collective hole.
这是我们的集体漏洞。
Right?
对？
When you when I said I fell into your hole,
当你当我说我掉进你的洞里时，
you said that.
你之前这么说。
You said it was all.
你说都是。
So I'm like, damn, what the hell you saying?
所以我想，该死的，你到底在说什么？
I'm yours.
我是你的。
Our hole like your mine.
我们的洞和你的一样。
Stop putting words into my mouth.
别再往我嘴里塞话了。
I did not say that.
我没那么说过。
And see that
看到那个
water yourself, demon.
给自己浇水，恶魔。
OK, fine. For myself, I find myself.
好的。 对于我自己，我找到了自己。
I think you'd like me to
我想你希望我
this.
这。
All this is.
这都是。
Just for the game. This is just for the game, OK?
只是为了比赛。 这只是为了游戏，好吗？
Nothing else.
没有其他的。
You know.
你知道。
That's just because I'm. We're trying to win.
那只是因为我是。 我们正在努力取胜。
I'm trying to win. You know, that's like.
我正在努力取胜。 你知道，就是这样。
It's like nowadays. It's nothing more than about.
就像现在一样。 无非是关于。
The game. It's for the win.
游戏。 这是为了胜利。
No, I understand. I do. I do. I really do.
不，我明白。 我愿意。 我愿意。 我真的。
With your meats
用你的肉
and your chicken.
还有你的鸡。
OK. Good job.
好的。 做得好。
Good job, old guy.
干得好，老家伙。
There, rice and the grab your rice.
在那里，米饭和你的米饭。
You got it.
你说对了。
OK, this chicken's ready.
好的，这只鸡做好了。
All right? And got some days.
好的？ 并得到了一些日子。
So you knocked me off.
所以你把我打倒了。
You literally pushed me to the side.
你真的把我推到一边。
You fucking fucking. Mouth.
你他妈的。 嘴。
Shut your fucking mouth. I'll keep knocking you off.
闭上你他妈的嘴。 我会一直打倒你。
And then if you keep.
然后如果你保持。
Why you keep doing this? Why, why? Why are you yelling?
你为什么一直这样做？ 为什么为什么？ 你为什么大喊大叫？
Why you are knocking it?
你为什么敲它？
What's what's the what's the what do you get?
你得到了什么？
What do you get from this, huh? I don't understand.
你从中得到什么，嗯？ 我不明白。
It. Laugh really bad banter.
它。 笑起来真的很糟糕的玩笑。
That's that's like how you threw it onto the.
就像你把它扔到上面一样。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Wrong, wrong way.
我的天啊。 错误的，错误的方式。
You have to chop it up first.
你得先把它切碎。
Chop you up.
砍死你。
Make it,
做起来，做起来难啊，专注于厨房是一种思考。
You know, what.
你知道吗。
Do I really wirehouses?
我真的会接线吗？
It sounds it's talent.
听起来是天赋。
It's a it's really a talent of yours.
这是一个它真的是你的才能。
Russell. I'm talent. I am, too.
拉塞尔。 我是人才。 我也是。
I have a natural talent for distracting you.
我有一种让你分心的天赋。
Wow. You could be more obvious if you tried.
哇。 如果你尝试过，你可能会更明显。
Just just take the meat here.
就拿这里的肉吧。
Here you go. Actually, not delivering meat.
干得好。 其实，不送肉。
I don't think I want to take yours. You can take mine.
我不认为我想拿走你的。 你可以拿我的。
You grab the chicken, you grab the chicken, grab the chicken.
你抓鸡，你抓鸡，抓鸡。
Fuck. I'll grab the chicken. I got. I got it.
他妈的。 我会抓鸡。 我有。 我得到了它。
I got it. Oh,
我得到了它。 哦，
ok. OK.
行。 好的。
Rice, rice, rice.
米饭，米饭，米饭。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I almost fell off of the order because you fucking threw the me in my face.
我差点从订单上掉下来，因为你他妈的把我扔到我脸上了。
It literally. No. Oh, my God. It
从字面上看。 不，哦，我的上帝。 它
all my own luck.
我自己的运气。
Oh, that's fucking karma of karma, bitch.
哦，那是该死的因果报应，婊子。
No, no.
不，不。
We'll get them.
我们会得到他们的。
We'll get. All.
我们会得到的。 全部。
We got all that.
我们得到了这一切。
We got it. Don't panic. Don't panic.
我们得到了它。 不要恐慌。 不要恐慌。
Oh, God.
天啊。
Oh, it was your pot down here.
哦，这里是你的锅。
There you go.
你去吧。
OK, meat's ready.
好了，肉做好了。
It's ready.
它准备好了。
Borderline black rice noodles.
边缘黑米粉。
Await today.
等今天。
I fuck up. No, I didn't fuck up. Hey.
我他妈的。 不，我没有搞砸。 嘿。
Hey, pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa pa.
嘿，爸爸爸爸爸爸爸爸爸。
Listen, the BSF might be listening.
听着，BSF 可能在听。
Don't violate the programme, OK?
不要违反程序，好吗？
Fuck the visa.
去他妈的签证。
Oh, don't don't tell Sunny.
哦，不要不告诉Sunny。
Please don't tell Sunny.
请不要告诉Sunny。
He doesn't know prison.
他不知道监狱。
You as you know.
你如你所知。
That's that's a thought crime you're going to get.
那就是你将要犯的思想犯罪。
You're going to go away for a long time.
你会离开很长时间。
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
妈的。 妈的。
Do we got it.
我们明白了吗。
By the way?
顺便一提？
I think. I think we might have done.
我认为。 我想我们可能已经做到了。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, that's definitely just barely.
哦，那绝对只是勉强。
Oh, barely above.
哦，勉强在上面。
I like 14 points.
我喜欢14分。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
That was really good. I like those grunts.
那真是太好了。 我喜欢那些咕噜声。
You do it again
你再做一次
a little slower.
慢一点。
A little bit more like, you know, passion, like.
有点像，你知道的，激情，像。
Oh, you can do some eating and do some for me too.
哦，你可以吃点东西，也可以给我做点。
If you do it first.
如果你先做。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, no.
不好了。
I mean, maybe, maybe you got to get them out of maybe.
我的意思是，也许，也许你得把他们赶出去。
You do it first, if you don't mind.
你先做，如果你不介意的话。
You don't want to be that easy.
你不想那么容易。
Maybe. I mean, I know it works for you,
也许。
but I don't really know if I want to be that easy.
我的意思是，我知道它对你有用，但我真的不知道我是否想要那么容易。
Let me be that easy.
让我这么轻松。
This is an agreement.
这是一个协议。
We're making a deal, you know.
我们正在达成协议，你知道的。
As a business man doing business
作为一个做生意的商人
oh, my God.
我的天啊。
We get to make burger
我们开始做汉堡
all of that stuff.
所有这些东西。
Yeah, what the fuck was that noise?
是啊，那是什么鬼声音？
I've been I've been going I've been going slightly silly mode,
我一直在我一直在走我一直在走有点傻的模式，我只是一直在用愚蠢的方式说话，我想。
I think it's all right.
我认为没关系。
Wait, wait, wait, wait. OK, so the time is frozen, right?
等等，等等，等等，等等。 好的，所以时间被冻结了，对吧？
Let's just figure out how this is working for us, ok? OK.
让我们弄清楚这是如何为我们工作的，好吗？ 好的。
Brains are going to be silly.
大脑会变得愚蠢。
And every time something ends in an E.R.
每次事情都以 E.R. 结尾。
or an O.R., I keep like, saying weird.
或者手术室，我一直喜欢说奇怪。
Like, whenever I make something with a pepper, I'll just pick it up
就像，每当我用胡椒做东西时，我都会把它捡起来。
We bought a play board. And.
我们买了一个游戏板。 和。
Boogie. Boogie anything.
布吉。 布吉什么的。
Interesting. Together?
有趣的。 一起？
All right, so it looks like this is going to, like, rotate, basically.
好的，所以看起来这基本上会旋转。
Yeah. There you go. All
是的。 你去吧。 全部
this is cool.
这很酷。
This is cruel and unusual punishment.
这是残酷和不寻常的惩罚。
Lockouts, and it's all it's going to lock us in a certain segment.
停工，这就是将我们锁定在某个细分市场的全部。
So how are we going to do this?
那么我们将如何做到这一点呢？
We have to worry right now because the time is not.
我们现在必须担心，因为时间不是。
Yeah, if I put it on the plate, it doesn't even start yet.
是的，如果我把它放在盘子里，它甚至还没有开始。
So we could, like.
所以我们可以，喜欢。
Pre-Plan and it doesn't start until you do the first order.
预先计划，直到您完成第一个订单才开始。
Yeah. So we could,
是的。 所以我们可以，你知道，我们可以。
Begin like that.
就这样开始。
And then we can also throw
然后我们也可以抛出
we can throw like that
我们可以这样扔
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
I'd like to make sure.
我想确定一下。
OK, so the main thing is making sure that we don't get stuck on the same side
好的，所以主要的事情是确保我们不会被困在同一边，因为那样的话某些事情就是不可行的。
Oh, wait, you.
哦，等等，你。
You could, you could just walk around.
你可以，你可以到处走走。
All of us are. No.
我们都是。 不。
Here.
这里。
We all. Know. Where's the chopping block.
我们都。 知道。 砧板在哪里。
The over on your side.
在你身边。
Oh, why is the cheese on it.
哦，为什么上面有奶酪。
I can't cut. It out that the cheese over there and I happen to land on it.
我不能剪。 那里的奶酪和我碰巧落在了上面。
Oh, fuck. OK.
哦，操。 好的。
All right.
好的。
There go.
去吧。
All we have to cut the cheese.
我们只需要切奶酪。
Oops.
哎呀。
You know, I think I think burgers are a bit better
你知道，我认为我认为汉堡更好一点
if you if you melt the cheese while you're frying the burger.
如果你在煎汉堡的时候融化了奶酪。
Yeah, I like that idea.
是的，我喜欢这个主意。
I don't know why we're let's say we're not even
我不知道我们为什么会说我们甚至不是
maybe, like, having the whole cheese on a burger.
也许，就像，把整个奶酪放在一个汉堡上。
Sounds so gross to me. Yeah, I, like.
对我来说听起来很恶心。 是的，我喜欢。
Know, melt the cheese.
知道，融化奶酪。
That's that's over.
那就是结束了。
That's a real man's way of doing it.
这才是真正的男人的做法。
That's already dude, I think we can just finesse this.
那已经是老兄了，我想我们可以巧妙地解决这个问题。
Yeah, we can.
是的，我们可以。
We can just get a ton of burgers, right? There's, like.
我们可以得到一吨汉堡，对吧？ 有，像。
My, my, my, my, my, my way.
我的，我的，我的，我的，我的，我的方式。
But some of them don't. Want some cheese.
但其中一些没有。 想要一些奶酪。
Fine.
美好的。
It's fine. We'll have them ready.
没事。 我们会让他们准备好。
Let's have three with cheese and one with out.
让我们三份加奶酪，一份不加奶酪。
OK? OK, so this one can go there.
好的？ 好的，所以这个可以去那里。
Yeah,
是的，
someone's talking about creamy burger.
有人在谈论奶油汉堡。
A creamy burger.
一个奶油汉堡。
What's
什么是
I think?
我认为？
I just think that she's off
我只是觉得她不在了
the I just through the cheese off.
我只是通过奶酪关闭。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
That's OK. It's OK.
那没问题。 没关系。
We can recover.
我们可以恢复。
We have one with me.
我们和我有一个。
Two to one with me, one with just cheese.
和我一对一，一个只有奶酪。
All right, wait. One sandwich.
好吧，等等。 一个三明治。
OK, hold on.
好的，稍等。
You know, some people like that.
你知道，有些人就是这样。
Some people just like having a grilled cheese like that. And there we. Go.
有些人就是喜欢吃这样的烤奶酪。 我们在那里。 去。
We have full plate burgers. All right, do you want to do get going?
我们有全盘汉堡。 好的，你想开始吗？
OK, hold on, hold on. Hold on.
好的，等一下，等一下。 坚持，稍等。
Let me just prep some mouth.
让我准备一些嘴巴。
Let me just move, bitch.
让我动起来，婊子。
Move my just so much cheese.
移动我这么多的奶酪。
I'm just I'm just prepping I'm just prepping.
我只是我只是在准备我只是在准备。
I'm preloading
我正在预加载
You ever heard of pre-loading,
你听说过预加载，
sir? Shut.
先生？ 关闭。
God, why do I keep doing that?
天啊，我为什么一直这样？
I keep calling you sirens, though, chef.
不过，我一直叫你警笛，厨师。
I think it might be just sort of ingrained.
我想这可能只是有点根深蒂固。
You know?
你知道？
I mean, you haven't ever heard of Freudian slip.
我的意思是，你从来没有听说过弗洛伊德的失误。
Yeah, I heard of burning slips.
是的，我听说过烧单。
It happens all the time. I mean. I mean. I mean.
它一直在发生。 我是说。 我是说。 我是说。
I mean, I might as well call using Freud at this point.
我的意思是，我不妨在这一点上使用弗洛伊德。
Sir, chef, sir.
先生，厨师，先生。
Lord, Master Chef, sir lord.
大人，大厨，大人。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Now, that's a real Freudian slip. Holy shit. Fair enough.
现在，这是一个真正的弗洛伊德式失误。 天啊。 很公平。
I don't if.
我不如果。
We all get stuck here, we can't even serve.
我们都被困在这里，我们甚至不能服务。
Yeah, we can't serve.
是的，我们不能服务。
We're stuck on one side, which is very chill.
我们被困在一侧，这很冷。
Just chill. We'll wait for it.
冷静一下。 我们会等待它。
Yeah, I'll.
是的，我会的。
I'll also the rest of what we got.
我也将我们得到的其余部分。
OK, ok, I'll wait. We need plates.
好，好，我等着。 我们需要盘子。
Dirty place. There's dirty places. Dirty plates.
肮脏的地方。 有肮脏的地方。 脏盘子。
Yeah, just.
是的，只是。
Just put it here. Just put it here. I'll clean them up. Yeah.
把它放在这里。 把它放在这里。 我会把它们清理干净。 是的。
All done.
全部做完。
Oh, chopper to g.
哦，菜刀到g。
Chopper to. Cheese.
斩波器到。 起司。
Well, I threw the cheese into the oblivion.
好吧，我把奶酪扔进了遗忘。
Did not mean to do that.
不是故意的。
You did. OK, we just wait.
你做到了。 好的，我们就等着吧。
We have three regular hamburgers.
我们有三个普通的汉堡包。
What's
什么是
hold on.
坚持，稍等。
OK, this one's ready.
好的，这个准备好了。
This one's ready.
这个准备好了。
I think.
我认为。
Yep. So that.
是的。 以便。
And that one is.
那就是。
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等。
You know, the plates are fake. Why? We can't get the meat.
你知道，盘子是假的。 为什么？ 我们买不到肉。
Oh, my God, we're stuck.
哦，我的上帝，我们被困住了。
Wait, can you watch them from the side? I think I can.
等等，你能从侧面看他们吗？ 我觉得我可以。
Yeah.
是的。
Oh, it makes zero sense, but I don't give a shit.
哦，这是零意义，但我不在乎。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
OK. And
好的。 和
I just need a plate for that.
我只需要一个盘子。
I mean, so plates already.
我的意思是，已经盘子了。
You plates are ready.
你的盘子准备好了。
All right. Oh, ok. I'll grab more meat.
好的。 哦好的。 我会抓更多的肉。
We need more meat.
我们需要更多的肉。
Yeah, that's it.
是的，就是这样。
Yeah, I'll throw that.
是的，我会扔那个。
Let me just add the right to me.
让我把权利加给我。
There you go.
你去吧。
That's over there.
那是那边。
OK. Have
好的。 有
I have it back. I have it back.
我把它拿回来了。 我把它拿回来了。
You've earned it.
你已经赚到了。
You've earned some raw meat.
你赚了一些生肉。
This is good.
这很好。
Yeah.
是的。
It's just a bunch of regular burgers.
这只是一堆普通的汉堡。
No cheese.
没有奶酪。
No, she's not. She's OK.
不，她不是。 她没事。
And again, we're on different sides.
再说一次，我们站在不同的一边。
It's good
这很好
oh, ok. OK.
哦好的。 好的。
This one's running. This one's ready. This one's ready.
这个正在运行。 这个准备好了。 这个准备好了。
OK, there you go. Take it, take it, take it, take it.
好的，给你。 拿，拿，拿，拿。
Take it.
拿着。
And it's got
它得到了
the chopped.
切碎的。
More meats.
更多的肉。
Oh, look at that.
哦，看那个。
See work you there, baby?
看到你在那里工作吗，宝贝？
Baby.
婴儿。
Here you go.
干得好。
More plates are getting ready.
更多的盘子正在准备中。
I think we have two cheeses next
我想我们接下来有两个奶酪
to cheese.
奶酪。
Confirm some cheese.
确认一些奶酪。
Yeah, I got you.
是的，我得到了你。
Can I throw it?
我可以扔吗？
I can
我可以
and there's a plate here for some goddamn reason,
出于某种该死的原因，这里有一个盘子，
I can drop it here.
我可以把它放在这里。
She has a cheeseburger.
她有一个芝士汉堡。
Yeah, that one's ready. Helen's ready.
是的，那个已经准备好了。 海伦准备好了。
He's gonna.
他会。
Put a.
放一个。
Black.
黑色的。
We'll put this in.
我们会把这个放进去。
Put this in off.
把这个关掉。
Oh, God. Oh, wait. How that happened?
天啊。 等一下。 那是怎么发生的？
All right, well, I guess we're on the opposite side now.
好吧，好吧，我想我们现在在对面。
Yeah, ok.
是的，好的。
OK. Well, damn it.
好的。 好吧，该死的。
Plates up, plates up.
盘子，盘子。
Come on.
来吧。
I'm dropping me.
我正在放弃我。
Oh, God.
天啊。
OK, I want that burgers ready to get
好的，我想准备好汉堡
cooked so long. I put this on.
煮了这么久。 我穿上这个。
They go get to go on the dirty plates.
他们去弄脏盘子。
The chops, cheese again.
排骨，奶酪。
It's a regular burger. It's about to expire.
这是一个普通的汉堡。 它即将到期。
Do a cheeseburger next.
接下来做一个芝士汉堡。
OK, cheeseburger next.
好的，接下来是芝士汉堡。
Cheeseburger next. It's ready. It's right.
接下来是芝士汉堡。 它准备好了。 这是正确的。
Yeah, it.
是的，它。
Good boy.
好孩子。
Is that OK? Yeah, I got that.
那样可以么？ 是的，我明白了。
I don't want you eating. Plate.
我不想让你吃。 盘子。
Oh, plate. Play, play, play.
哦，盘子。 玩，玩，玩。
I didn't. I can't see them from this angle. I thought it would lend
我没有。 我从这个角度看不到他们。 我以为会借
you know, I think we still got it, and we.
你知道，我认为我们仍然得到它，而且我们。
I think we still it. He's not bad.
我想我们还是这样。 他并不坏。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Really? 740 now we can do it.
真的吗？  740 现在我们可以做到了。
We can go in a bunch of mistakes that. He
我们可能会犯很多错误。 他
we can be close.
我们可以接近。
Yeah, we could do that.
是的，我们可以这样做。
Yeah, maybe we could do that.
是的，也许我们可以这样做。
Customers are so impatient though.
不过客户实在是太不耐烦了。
Slowly.
慢慢地。
They want their food in, like, seconds flat.
他们想要他们的食物，就像，秒平。
OK, so we just got to finish this one of them.
好的，所以我们只需要完成其中一个。
We can go back. Nice.
我们可以回去了。 好的。
Yeah.
是的。
And talk to doctor old crusty onion. Boy
和老脆皮洋葱医生谈谈。 男生
bring big
带来大
thing.
事物。
It's not that there is something about tomatoes.
并不是说西红柿有什么东西。
You anything about tomato?
你有什么关于番茄的吗？
Probably.
大概。
Just, like, later on, we'll have to do with tomatoes as well. OK,
就像，稍后，我们也将不得不与西红柿有关。 好的，
there are quite a lot of ingredients.
有相当多的成分。
They're on me, sir. Thank you.
他们在我身上，先生。 谢谢你。
Go. You go.
去。 你去。
That's right. You picked up.
没错。 你接了。
OK, how. About we just you.
好吧怎么办。 关于我们只有你。
Get ready. How about we just get ready?
做好准备。 我们准备好怎么样？
Yeah. And stuff here.
是的。 还有这里的东西。
Regular burgers, 22 cheeseburgers.
普通汉堡，22 个芝士汉堡。
You know?
你知道？
Yeah. Hold on. You just.
是的。 坚持，稍等。 你刚才。
I'm going to get I'm just going to put the plate down here.
我要得到 我只是要把盘子放在这里。
Get it ready ahead of time.
提前准备好。
And to a regular burger.
和一个普通的汉堡。
You said it.
你说的。
So here's a cheeseburger right here.
所以这里有一个芝士汉堡。
Regular lines.
规律的线条。
And this is a regular burger place.
这是一个普通的汉堡店。
I saw the voice, and I just long it into a into oblivion.
我看到了那个声音，我只是把它变成了遗忘。
First place to pick it up.
第一个捡起来的地方。
You want.
你要。
I'm trying to put the plates down, you whore.
我正试图放下盘子，你这个婊子。
No, no, no. I'm talking to you. I'm talking to the game.
不不不。 我在跟你说话。 我在和游戏说话。
All the moves, OK?
所有的动作，好吗？
I didn't mean to call you a whore then. OK?
那时我不是故意叫你妓女的。 好的？
I know
我知道
stuff.
东西。
That's all this other stuff.
这就是所有其他的东西。
I mean, stop throwing stuff.
我的意思是，停止扔东西。
Why are you throwing the shredded cheese back at me?
你为什么把切碎的奶酪扔给我？
Know it's kind of just kind of why I'm out.
知道这就是我出局的原因。
OK, ok, let me. I'm going to send the burgers in.
好，好，让我。 我要把汉堡送进去。
And this one, the burgers. And are you ready?
还有这个，汉堡。 你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
OK, let's go. Let's go.
好的，我们走吧。 我们走吧。
Easy peasy.
十分简单。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Gaming.
赌博。
Is quite awkward.
相当尴尬。
Were stranded
被搁浅
oh. Well, while he's.
哦。 好吧，虽然他在。
We have three plates of clean and ready that real quick.
我们有三盘干净的盘子，很快就准备好了。
I'll go on the opposite side.
我会去对面。
It's shaking.
它在颤抖。
All right, here we go.
好吧，我们开始吧。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Well, it doesn't.
好吧，它没有。
Let me break.
让我打破。
I got.
我有。
I got it. I got. It. I thought I was yelling at the guy.
我得到了它。 我有。 它。 我以为我在对那个人大喊大叫。
Yeah, yeah, I saw. I saw
是的，是的，我看到了。 我看见
there's a bunch of a
有一堆
bunch of shit in the way.
一堆狗屎在路上。
We have three regular burgers actually on.
我们实际上有三个普通汉堡。
I'm going to send this one out pre-emptively, but I got regular burgers.
我要先发制人地把这个送出去，但我有普通的汉堡。
Yeah. All right. Good side. Good side.
是的。 好的。 好的一面。 好的一面。
It splits. OK, it's.
它分裂。 好的，是的。
Not good split, so I just need bread.
不好分开，所以我只需要面包。
I just need bread with that one.
我只需要那个面包。
Bread right. One.
面包对。 一。
Yeah, that's bread with this one is bread.
是的，这是面包，这个是面包。
I'll send it out as soon as you put plate it.
你一装盘，我就发出去。
What? What, what?
什么？ 什么什么？
I was confused.
我很困惑。
OK, ok.
好的好的。
More regular, more. Right.
更规律，更多。 对。
Here's more dirty dishes.
这里有更多脏盘子。
There's murder dishes. I mean, don't let me do them.
有杀人菜。 我的意思是，不要让我这样做。
All right? I'll stay on this side.
好的？ 我会留在这一边。
This this is Philip on my speed.
这是菲利普对我的速度。
I'll stay on the side. Yeah.
我会留在一边。 是的。
Ok. You can grab the plate whenever you're ready.
行。 只要你准备好了，你就可以抓住盘子。
We just like. Yeah.
我们只是喜欢。 是的。
Thank you. All right.
谢谢你。 好的。
OK, I'll chop more meats right here.
好的，我会在这里切更多的肉。
So we're not even toasting.
所以我们甚至不敬酒。
This is pretty wack.
这很古怪。
Oh, I didn't mean to throw that.
哦，我不是故意扔那个的。
She's
她是
forgive me, chef.
原谅我，厨师。
Oh, nice.
不错哦。
You got it.
你说对了。
But you got it this time.
但这次你明白了。
Finally.
最后。
OK, she's ready.
好的，她准备好了。
Eric mean for you?
埃里克对你意味着什么？
I mean, you see on the other side. See on the other side.
我的意思是，你在另一边看到。 见另一边。
Stay on the other side.
留在另一边。
Yeah, yeah. OK.
是啊是啊。 好的。
You OK to radio?
你可以广播吗？
Nice. On in another burg.
好的。 在另一个堡。
Send some meat over. I can chop that.
送点肉过来。 我可以砍那个。
How would you feel about this game if they would just like randomly?
如果他们只是随意地喜欢这个游戏，你会怎么看？
86 certain meals like that. You just got to send it back.
86 次这样的饭菜。 你只需要把它寄回去。
It's like they said it was dry and then you don't get the points for it.
就像他们说它是干的，然后你没有得到它的分数。
That's fucked up.
那是完蛋了。
I don't know.
我不知道。
I don't I think I would mauled. Or that
我不认为我会受到伤害。 或者那个
I think that's bullshit.
我认为那是胡说八道。
86. My meal is just because it was too dry.
86. 我的饭菜只是因为太干了。
I'll show you dry.
我会告诉你干的。
Jesus.
耶稣。
God. You know, bite the pillow oh.
上帝。 你知道，咬枕头哦。
Thank you for the cheese, babe.
谢谢你的奶酪，宝贝。
You're welcome.
不客气。
Why are you throwing the buttons at me?
你为什么把纽扣扔给我？
OK, I'm not at all. I'm losing it.
好吧，我一点也不。 我正在失去它。
Like losing my mind in it.
就像在其中失去理智一样。
You. Oh, no.
你。 不好了。
Oh, no. Oh, no.
不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no, you're not.
哦，不，你不是。
Oh, no. We're trying not to have anything wrong.
不好了。 我们正在努力避免出现任何问题。
There's no. It's OK. It's ok.
没有。 没关系。 没关系。
We can prepare so much together over here.
我们可以在这里一起准备这么多。
You can't even access one of the top moves
您甚至无法访问顶级动作之一
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
But there
但是那里
you go.
你去。
That's a burger. Ready not really.
那是一个汉堡。 真的没有准备好。
Burger ready.
汉堡准备好了。
I'll grab that. Oh.
我会抓住那个。 哦。
I put the.
我把。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Yeah, I got it.
是的，我明白了。
I put the fucking fire extinguisher there for some reason.
出于某种原因，我把该死的灭火器放在那里。
OK, is this ready?
好的，准备好了吗？
Yeah, this is ready. Let's go. Dirty dishes.
是的，这已经准备好了。 我们走吧。 脏盘子。
Dirty dishes. Are regular boring burger.
脏盘子。 是普通无聊的汉堡。
Regular burgers coming all man.
普通汉堡来了所有的人。
We could get another one.
我们可以再买一个。
We need the dirty dishes. Three dishes.
我们可以再买一个。 我们需要脏盘子。 三道菜。
Yeah. 24 seconds.
是的。  24 秒。
Just gets you. Regular burgers to regular burgers. Ready?
只是得到你。 普通汉堡到普通汉堡。 准备好？
I think we can have time for that.
我想我们可以有时间。
Yeah,
是的，
I just need a place where it.
我只需要一个地方。
Any place.
任何地方。
Yeah. Please. Oh.
是的。 请。 哦。
Oh, my fucking God.
哦，我的他妈的上帝。
No, oh. Ok.
不，哦。 行。
Oh, look, can we. Can we go?
哦，看，我们可以。 我们可以去吗？
No, no, no. Washes.
不不不。 洗涤。
Yeah. Oh, the dolphins.
是的。 哦，海豚。
Such a good strike points.
这么好的打击点。
Four points. The way. Not really.
四点。 道路。 并不真地。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Oh. Oh,
哦。 哦，
my. Oh, my.
我的。 天啊。
Just because you got stuck on the same side of
只是因为你被困在同一边
this way.
这边走。
Smells like shit in here one more time.
再来一次闻起来像屎一样。
Smells like shit in here.
这里闻起来像狗屎。
What a pickle. It smells like.
什么泡菜。 它闻起来像。
Not about my room. It's most fine in my room.
不是关于我的房间。 在我的房间里最好。
I was just thinking about, like, just the process of being in the game
我只是在想，就像，只是在比赛中并让这种情况发生的过程。 我只是。
I don't know my opinion on it.
我不知道我对此的看法。
I was like, it smells like shit, you know?
我当时想，它闻起来像屎，你知道吗？
OK, you're your brain. Is truly miraculous.
好吧，你就是你的大脑。 真是神奇。
Fox Thank you. Thank you. Soto Thank you.
狐狸 谢谢。 谢谢你。 索托 谢谢。
Drama. OK, you ready?
戏剧。 好的，你准备好了吗？
Prep. We're going to prep everything again.
准备。 我们将再次准备一切。
One word
一个词
allowing more meat.
允许更多的肉。
More meat. Good. One moment when meat.
更多的肉。 好的。 一瞬间当肉。
I am laying out the buttons.
我正在布置按钮。
Be patient. Boy.
耐心点。 男生。
This is unrealistic.
这是不现实的。
I feel like they would probably ask for a bottomless burger
我觉得他们可能会在某个时候要求一个无底汉堡。
OK, we really need.
好的，我们真的需要。
We really need to imagine if they had, like
我们真的需要想象他们是否有，比如
I mentioned, you know, never new go to war.
我提到过，你知道，从来没有新的战争。
Have you played that. The god of war?
你玩过吗。 战神？
No, I haven't. Actually.
不，我没有。 实际上。
You know, I like the new game is all about what's kind of new.
你知道，我喜欢这个新游戏就是关于什么是新的。
Like, the newest one is about, like, Kratos taking his, like,
就像，最新的一个是关于，就像，奎托斯带着他的，像，这个儿子上山。
He's like, boy, you must not hunt and all that kind of stuff.
他就像，男孩，你不能打猎之类的东西。
You do that with us.
你和我们一起做。
You know, I'm creatures and you like the boy.
你知道，我是生物，你喜欢这个男孩。
And the boy.
还有那个男孩。
Boy and boy.
男孩和男孩。
I'm just a boy.
我只是一个男孩。
Boy do you have much to learn, boy?
男孩，你有很多东西要学吗，男孩？
OK, let's chop more meat and cheese.
好吧，让我们切更多的肉和奶酪。
Chop more meat, and she's cheese. Get that ready.
切更多的肉，她就是奶酪。 准备好。
Yeah. OK. I call it. Do I call you?
是的。 好的。 我叫它。 我打电话给你吗？
Was he say, do I call you dad or do I call you mother?
他是说，我叫你爸爸还是叫你妈妈？
Father, father?
父亲，父亲？
Yeah, I'll do that.
是的，我会那样做。
My father.
我的父亲。
Makes good. How to prepare a father.
做的很好。 如何准备一个父亲。
Father and brother.
父亲和兄弟。
Father, father.
父亲，父亲。
Father. Father. Father,
父亲。 父亲。 父亲，
father. You.
父亲。 你。
Do you have a step?
你有台阶吗？
Father? You're right.
父亲？ 你说的对。
Father. Father, I'm such father of fuck.
父亲。 父亲，我就是这样的他妈的父亲。
OK, ok. You give me the cheese. Father, do.
好的好的。 你给我奶酪。 父亲，做。
Not make an I'm stuck step father joke.
不做一个我被困步父的笑话。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
You should not.
你不应该。
I was actually. About to get stuck.
我其实是。 快要卡住了。
Minimum.
最低限度。
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不，不。
OK, meat.
好的，肉。
We need all the plate meats.
我们需要所有的盘子肉。
Meat business.
肉类业务。
And again, I send this in and get ready. Ship
再一次，我把这个寄过去，做好准备。 船
OK, this meat's ready.
好了，这肉做好了。
This and then another one.
这个，然后是另一个。
Action.
行动。
Oh, there you go. That's cooking.
哦，给你。 那就是做饭。
Oh, you throw it in.
哦，你扔进去。
Yeah. Body of the.
是的。 的身体。
Baby.
婴儿。
He come, baby. Wow.
他来了，宝贝。 哇。
I was already done that before.
我以前已经这样做了。
Like I've heard, babe.
就像我听说的那样，宝贝。
I've never heard baby.
我从来没有听说过宝贝。
We go.
我们去。
I got it saved.
我把它保存了。
So I'm good on.
所以我很擅长。
Yeah, it's good to go.
是的，去就好了。
Good to go. All right, let me get those dishes for you.
很好走。 好吧，让我给你拿那些菜。
Yeah.
是的。
Sure. Oh.
当然。 哦。
I got that.
我明白了。
I got that. Don't worry, don't worry.
我明白了。 别担心，别担心。
Oh, you got it. OK.
哦，你明白了。 好的。
Oh, you're sexy when you catch it inside.
哦，当你抓住它时，你很性感。
Are we only a plane
我们只是一架飞机吗
the sensory dish is right over here.
感官菜就在这里。
I got that she.
我明白了她。
Looks. Already right.
看起来。 已经对了。
We're looking good. Look at us, girl. Look at us.
我们看起来不错。 看看我们，女孩。 看着我们。
Who would have thought
谁曾想到
the place?
地方？
Ready to thank you?
准备好感谢你了吗？
Look, all synergy.
看，所有的协同作用。
Can't do anything like that.
不能做那样的事。
Can do with that. It just needs a bun.
可以这样做。 它只需要一个面包。
That just needs a bun. Now.
那只需要一个面包。 现在。
That's all right.
没关系。
It's about to move my thanks to make sure you know what.
它即将移动我的感谢，以确保你知道什么。
I'm saying on the side. I understand, but don't do it.
我说的是一边。 我明白，但不要这样做。
Put a dirty dish right there.
把脏盘子放在那里。
Oh, ok.
哦好的。
OK, ok, ok.
好好好。
Oh, my God. I almost got stuck.
我的天啊。 我几乎被卡住了。
Came on time. Good job.
准时来了。 做得好。
I did. Come on, time. I always come on time.
我做到了。 准时来。 我总是准时来。
I always come.
我总是来。
As William often says, right off his line.
正如威廉经常说的那样，就在他的线下。
I always come close enough. It's close.
我总是足够接近。 它很近。
I always come on your back.
我总是站在你的背上。
Who's back.
谁回来了。
With you in.
有你在。
All these games?
所有这些游戏？
So don't play the Potter Fishy Moe when our son
所以当我们的儿子说它很糟糕时，不要玩Potter
when you said that it's pretty bad.
Fishy Moe。
There it is.
它在那里。
Look at our teamwork.
看看我们的团队合作。
Tossing it back and forth. On this thing.
来回折腾。 在这件事上。
Oh, no, I OK.
哦，不，我没事。
I fucked it up.
我搞砸了。
I think I need a regular burger this time.
我想这次我需要一个普通的汉堡。
Like no cheese.
就像没有奶酪一样。
You're going to get a.
你会得到一个。
Was ready
准备好了
there's a regular burger for you.
有一个普通的汉堡给你。
Yeah. I'm coming. I'm going.
是的。 我来了。 我要去。
I got it. I got it. Thank you.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。 谢谢你。
Good job up.
干得好。
Here's your dirty plates.
这是你的脏盘子。
That burgers ready to go.
那个汉堡准备好了。
Let's get that regular burger done.
让我们把那个普通的汉堡做好。
I'm going to come back and.
我要回来了。
Do that regular burger right now.
现在就做那个普通的汉堡。
It's an outright. Now. Yup, yup.
这是一个彻头彻尾的。 现在。 是的，是的。
And you put that in the pan.
然后你把它放在锅里。
Put that in the dish over here.
把它放在这边的盘子里。
Put on the fire.
放在火上。
Here's some shredded cheese. Like you.
这是一些碎奶酪。 喜欢你。
And I'm gonna grab.
我要抢。
I'm gonna grab the da da da burger.
我要抢 da da da 汉堡。
Let's start cooking PA.
让我们开始烹饪 PA。
So I'm reading another the regular burger, if possible.
因此，如果可能的话，我正在阅读另一个普通汉堡。
Dirty dishes. Here you go.
脏盘子。 干得好。
Three regular burgers in a row.
连续三个普通汉堡。
Oh, OK.
哦好的。
I don't know why threw that one. Good.
我不知道为什么扔了那个。 好的。
OK, yeah.
好的，是的。
Oh, where's all the suspense?
哦，所有的悬念在哪里？
Oh, here's one
哦，这里有一个
another dirty plate
另一个脏盘子
it's gonna rotate.
它会旋转。
It's going to rotate soon. Get rotating.
它很快就会旋转。 旋转起来。
We got the stuff. We got this
我们得到了东西。 我们得到了这个
all right.
好的。
Be ready to get this one right away. Is going no time left.
准备好马上得到这个。 时间不多了。
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, she's.
是的。 是的。 哦，她是。
No, she's not.
不，她不是。
She's not. She's got it.
她不是。 她明白了。
OK, it's in. It's in, it's in.
好的，它进来了。它进来了，它进来了。
We've got it.
我们明白了。
Now we just have to not fuck up oh.
现在我们只需要不要搞砸哦。
We have enough time. We're going to buy one more volume.
我们有足够的时间。 我们打算再买一卷。
One more. Bun. When we're born. When we're born. I think we could get it.
多一个。 包子。 当我们出生时。 当我们出生时。 我想我们可以得到它。
We can get it. Seven.
我们可以得到它。 七。
Yeah, yeah. We have time. We have time. Five.
是啊是啊。 我们有时间。 我们有时间。 五。
Four, three, two, one.
四、三、二、一。
Oh, it's so close.
哦，它是如此接近。
Oh, that's so close.
哦，那是那么接近。
Well, we still did it
好吧，我们还是做到了
let's go even need it.
让我们去甚至需要它。
We don't even need that. Said we did it.
我们甚至不需要那个。 说我们做到了。
To we're so clean.
对我们来说是那么干净。
We get so. Good at. These. They're clean.
我们是这样的。 擅长。 这些。 他们很干净。
Oh, O'Keefe's shifty Chete.
哦，奥基夫狡猾的切特。
Oh, that was a really good job.
哦，那真是一份好工作。
You were sexy back there.
你在那里很性感。
You handled that me real well.
你处理得很好。
Well, thank you, you guys.
嗯，谢谢各位。
I can back that yeah.
我可以支持是的。
And the buns.
还有包子。
Very good bun work. Yeah, I think.
非常好的面包工作。 是的，我想。
I think you were the handling, the me and I was handling the buns.
我想你是搬运工，我和我在搬运包子。
Yeah, that's true.
是的，这是真的。
Wait a second.
等一下。
Wait a.
等一个。
Second. I'm
第二。 我是
not a jokester.
不是开玩笑的。
You're going to be a fucking comedian.
你会成为一个他妈的喜剧演员。
I am very comedian.
我很喜剧。
He has a. Quest for us.
他有一个。 为我们寻找。
What's next on the hmm?
嗯，下一步是什么？
I though I.
我虽然我。
Bring you. Chefs.
带你。 厨师。
You're in one piece, Kevin. I didn't think you'd make it.
你是一体的，凯文。 我没想到你会成功。
Who's Kevin?
凯文是谁？
Dog? Oh, that's a dog.
狗？ 哦，那是一条狗。
His name's Kevin and all.
他的名字叫凯文。
Is he. Is he, like, the ruler?
是他。 他是，像，统治者吗？
Oh, no, why are you running all your own in Ryder?
哦，不，你为什么要在莱德自己经营？
You're qualified, but look how your skills have grown.
你是合格的，但看看你的技能是如何增长的。
It's not just.
这不仅仅是。
Your bowl, your balloon that's on the up and up.
你的碗，你的气球，向上和向上。
There's still much to do.
还有很多事情要做。
The umbrella, they're getting hungrier with each passing moment.
雨伞，他们越来越饿。
Maybe the strange lions.
也许是奇怪的狮子。
To the east will hold the secret to moderating their munchies.
东边将掌握控制他们的零食的秘诀。
There are curious rumours about the place.
关于这个地方有一些奇怪的谣言。
Many myths and legends.
许多神话和传说。
Do you dare you do?
你敢吗？
Oh, my guts.
哦，我的胆量。
Sick astronomers.
生病的天文学家。
Well, make sure you stick together.
好吧，确保你们团结在一起。
And remember.
记住。
Not everything is as it seems.
并非一切都像看起来那样。
In the onion kingdom.
在洋葱王国。
As everything as it seems in the ultimate kingdom.
一切尽在终极王国中。
A dog, a doggy dog washing up.
一只狗，一只正在洗碗的小狗。
Was that mean.
是不是很刻薄。
I'm talk to the dog.
我正在和狗说话。
Or wife in there.
或者里面有老婆。
So I keep I keep like when I nudge my mike, it just goes really.
所以我一直保持我在轻推我的麦克风时的样子，它真的很好。
A little disloyal.
有点不忠。
The jury deal.
陪审团协议。
Yeah.
是的。
Do you do. Want.
你会吗。 想。
By the way, out of question one?
顺便说一句，毫无疑问的？
Do you want to stop?
你想停下来吗？
I don't mind.
我不介意。
I imagine we probably can't play this game for quite as long as it takes to
我想我们可能无法长时间玩这个游戏，因为它真的很有压力。
So it it's up to you.
所以这取决于你。
I don't mind personally. It's up to you.
我个人不介意。 它是由你决定。
OK, how about we do a couple more
好的，我们如何在新区域再多做几次，然后在那里调用它。
As it's going to.
正如它所要发生的那样。
Because it takes to Israel.
因为它需要到以色列。
It's it's someone in a way, it gets relaxing up once
它在某种程度上是一个人，一旦有它就会放松，就像它一样，你知道，它就是它。
A very emotional and this is like this is just this is.
一个很情绪化的，这就像这就是这样。
Just like stress. It keeps.
就像压力一样。 它使。
Getting more stressful via the second.
通过第二个变得更加紧张。
Real man but all real dick in the arse butterball.
真正的男人，但都是真正的鸡巴。
You know what I'm saying?
你知道我在说什么？
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, that's why that's why we're lubricated. Mood.
我的意思是，这就是我们被润滑的原因。 情绪。
What is it?
它是什么？
Stonehenge, it seems 820 points.
巨石阵，好像是820分。
It looks really cool.
它看起来真的很酷。
Like the design.
喜欢设计。
Yeah. Pizza.
是的。 比萨。
It's up.
它起来了。
Well, you can. Order pizza after this.
嗯，你可以。 在此之后订购披萨。
I haven't had a good pizza in a bit.
我已经有一段时间没有吃到好吃的披萨了。
You asked it. Oh, now.
你问的。 哦，现在。
I want to order pizza.
我想点披萨。
Ricardo with a knife. And you know what?
里卡多拿着刀。 你知道吗？
I actually kind of want to go out and get pizza, like, go to a restaurant,
我其实有点想出去吃披萨，比如去餐馆，去餐馆吃披萨，好吧，让我们想想我们是怎么做的。
Over here now.
现在这边
And you're completely like.
和你完全一样。
Father, I'm stuck over here.
父亲，我被困在这里了。
Help me out.
帮帮我。
Boy, you must learn to deal with imprisonment.
男孩，你必须学会​​处理监禁。
Boy, oh, boy.
男孩，哦，男孩。
Here you go.
干得好。
All right, so one way.
好吧，只有一种方式。
So what do I do with the tomorrow? I think
那么明天我该怎么办？ 我认为
all right, Dough.
好的，面团。
I think.
我认为。
I think you put the dough on the board. Yeah. There you go. You got to.
我想你把面团放在板上了。 是的。 你去吧。 你必须。
One. Got to chop. It, though, for all.
一。 该砍了 不过，对于所有人来说。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Here you go.
干得好。
Yeah, yeah. There you go.
是啊是啊。 你去吧。
And then cheese.
然后是奶酪。
Cheese boxes.
奶酪盒。
Wait, what's OK?
等等，什么可以？
Yeah. Oh, no way.
是的。 哦，没办法。
It's it's pushing away. Why?
它正在推开。 为什么？
They're pushing you away for OK.
他们把你推开就好了。
So we got to do with that, then afterwards. No.
所以我们必须处理那个，然后。 不。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
We Pizzarelli cream
我们 Pizzarelli 奶油芝士披萨。
Oh. Oh, it's going in the oven.
哦。 哦，它要进烤箱了。
OK, pizzas in the oven.
好的，烤箱里的比萨饼。
All right, let me get some let me get some will do for you.
好吧，让我得到一些让我得到一些会为你做的。
I like the way he said dough there.
我喜欢他在那里说面团的方式。
Da da da da da da.
哒哒哒哒哒哒。
OK, some.
好的，一些。
Of you in chat.
你在聊天。
You hope aspiring chefs who want to make pizza.
您希望有抱负的厨师想要制作比萨饼。
This is just to let you know
这只是为了让你知道你不是用刀子敲打披萨面团来准备披萨面团的。
I got a loft over here.
我在这里有一个阁楼。
I've never seen that before.
我以前从未见过。
It was like a first fire seeing someone chop. It's got a.
看到有人砍人就像是第一场火灾。 它有一个。
Few ready because it looks like the cheese pizza is like one of the only recipes.
很少有人准备好，因为看起来奶酪披萨就像是唯一的食谱之一。
Are in Harry Potter.
在哈利波特里。
Where the fuck are we?
我们他妈在哪里？
The council's, like, discussing.
理事会正在讨论。
All right. Paul, I read.
好的。 保罗，我读过。
I heard you playing over today.
我听说你今天在玩。
You stop throwing the fucking don't be Harry Butler.
你停止扔他妈的不要是哈利巴特勒。
Fuck you throw dough.
他妈的你扔面团。
I do if I want. See? Reporter Don't look at me.
如果我愿意，我会这样做。 看？ 记者别看我。
Look at me.
看着我。
Look at me every hour.
每隔一小时看看我。
I go high grade.
我去高年级。
You lost the plate.
你丢了盘子。
It's my plate now, dumb arse row.
现在是我的盘子了，笨蛋行。
I'll if you can't fucking back out now.
如果你现在不能他妈的退出，我会的。
Oh, Harry, I re Paul Guy, are you.
哦，哈利，我是保罗盖伊，你呢。
Harry. Potter is Eric.
哈利。 波特是埃里克。
You probably know what happened.
你可能知道发生了什么。
The place in the corner now. You know it's OK.
现在在角落里的地方。 你知道没关系。
We're not going somewhere where we got plenty of time.
我们不会去我们有足够时间的地方。
I'm where I send this. Oh, here you go.
我在我发送这个的地方。 哦，给你。
Needs a plate.
需要一个盘子。
Four on a plate you've located you fuck.
四个在你找到的盘子里，你他妈的。
Right, Joe, stay and shout.
对，乔，留下来大喊大叫。
Always fucking dead. Oh, my God. Wait.
总是他妈的死。 我的天啊。 等待。
Tony, um.
托尼，嗯。
Who's on the oven?
谁在烤箱上？
Yeah, I got you. I got no, it's floating. It's floating.
是的，我得到了你。 我没有，它是浮动的。 它是漂浮的。
Vauxhall, you monster the way it's so slow the way it's like we.
沃克斯豪尔，你这个怪物，就像我们一样慢。
We we we re.
我们我们我们。
OK, put that in the oven.
好的，把它放在烤箱里。
You can you can put that order out now.
你现在可以下订单了。
You got plates right out.
你有盘子。
Plates, babe, let's begin
盘子，宝贝，让我们开始吧
oh, we don't even get started.
哦，我们甚至没有开始。
There gonna be breach
会有违约
and they re all but oh, no, vokey, not rebar.
他们都只是哦，不，vokey，不是钢筋。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Something's happening to my brain.
对不起。 对不起。 我的大脑发生了什么事。
No, no, it's OK.
不，不，没关系。
I like I.
我喜欢我。
Like I'm feeling like.
就像我感觉一样。
I'm sure it's very it's very sexy.
我敢肯定它非常非常性感。
You know, I said that to you.
你知道，我对你说过。
It's very sexy when you do those accents. I don't. Know.
当你做这些口音时，它是非常性感的。 我不。 知道。
Or, like.
或者，像。
I usually think.
我通常认为。
Oh, you want me to use the hybrid accent?
哦，你想让我用混合口音吗？
Yeah, please.
是的，请。
We can talk to you like your Harry Potter.
我们可以像您的哈利波特一样与您交谈。
You call me Harry Potter again, ok? OK.
你再叫我哈利波特，好吗？ 好的。
OK, let's calm down there.
好吧，让我们冷静下来。
Oh, all right, sir, I expect that one.
哦，好的，先生，我期待那个。
If we still can't get that pizza that's down there.
如果我们仍然无法得到下面的披萨。
This is our. It's on what.
这是我们的。 它是关于什么的。
It ok, plate by table. Here is the. Play.
没关系，一桌一桌。 这里是。 玩。
I put the plate right there.
我把盘子放在那里。
I put the boy right there at the bottom of a.
我把男孩放在了底部。
Burger up above the book.
汉堡在书上。
Page.
页。
I'm ordering
我正在订购
data plate for that. You
数据板。 你掉级了。 好吧，如果你发现了，你这个白痴。
I can't grab it. Oh, no, I can't.
我抢不走 哦，不，我不能。
I can't grab it.
我抢不走
Oh, shit.
妈的。
What is this?
这是什么？
Justine, are we OK? Dad?
贾斯汀，我们还好吗？ 爸爸？
Dude, there's a plate right here of a food.
伙计，这里有一盘食物。
It can grab. It can go out and serve it to the customer.
它可以抓住。 它可以出去并为客户服务。
Maybe I you a picture right now.
也许我现在给你一张照片。
You know, I feel like I should.
你知道，我觉得我应该这样做。
I can actually stay on the other side of you.
我其实可以留在你的另一边。
You don't have to be separated.
你不必分开。
We just like that.
我们就是这样。
You know, it's a good shot. Would you grab a bunch of these?
你知道，这是一个很好的镜头。 你会抓住一堆这些吗？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Big brain. Oh, no, no, no way. Well, we can't that we can't.
大脑袋。 哦，不，不，不可能。 好吧，我们不能，我们不能。
So we can't. We can't. We can't. So
所以我们不能。 我们不能。 我们不能。 所以
what do you mean?
你什么意思？
Because that thing of, like,
因为那个东西，比如，如果你在这边，你就不能上下楼梯。
I can't. Yeah.
我不能。 是的。
Oh, I think I recognise too much planning, to be honest.
哦，老实说，我想我承认计划太多了。
I like in concept.
我喜欢概念。
Yes. But
是的。 但
I don't know if we have. OK.
我不知道我们有没有。 好的。
Well you might not have the brain part but.
好吧，您可能没有大脑部分，但是。
I know I think I'm just making an accurate.
我知道我认为我只是在做一个准确的。
Estimation of what both of us together are capable of.
估计我们两个人的能力。
Yeah, you're right.
是的，没错。
OK. All oh, we are with the customer cook.
好的。 哦，我们和客户厨师在一起。
I'm Patty.
我是帕蒂。
No. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
不，哦，不。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。 不好了。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Oh, crap. OK.
哦，废话。 好的。
I'm crabbing.
我在吃螃蟹。
I'm squid game.
我是鱿鱼游戏。
Squid game, crab game, crab game.
鱿鱼游戏，螃蟹游戏，螃蟹游戏。
You ever watch that?
你看过吗？
You ever watch the crab game.
你曾经看过螃蟹比赛。
I've watched the squid keep them.
我看过鱿鱼饲养它们。
It's I want to watch the rest of it. I never got around to it.
我想看剩下的。 我从来没有解决过它。
Critical thought and the cheese can go on this one.
批判性思维和奶酪可以继续这一点。
Right? Yeah. Cheating on that.
对？ 是的。 欺骗那个。
And that's what.
就是这样。
Oh, Frank, the icon was in place and.
哦，弗兰克，图标就位了。
It's been pretty well. On the go.
这是相当不错的。 在旅途中。
We go. OK, put down a plate.
我们去。 好的，放下一个盘子。
I don't have a plate.
我没有盘子。
There is a plate up to the plate.
盘子上有一个盘子。
Why was there no on the floor?
为什么地板上没有？
Because I don't take those kind of cake.
因为我不吃那种蛋糕。
It's a little pressure
有点压力
get off. OK.
下车。 好的。
Oh, oh, oh.
哦哦哦。
Yo, yo, yo.
呦呦呦。
We're watching our plate washing our plate.
我们正在看着我们的盘子洗盘子。
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。
I got it.
我得到了它。
I got it. I got it.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。
Pop. Another one for you.
流行音乐。 另一个给你。
Another one.
另一个。
You can another monkey put in three.
你可以再放三只猴子。
I can put in there.
我可以放进去。
Yo, I put it in.
哟，我放进去了。
I don't know. I don't know. I push it away.
我不知道。 我不知道。 我推开它。
I make sure we make sure we got a plate.
我确保我们确保我们有一个盘子。
There's no plate. There's no plate.
没有盘子。 没有盘子。
No seventh day.
没有第七天。
Was that enough. Was it 720.
够了吗。 是720吗？
Eight 2820.
八个2820。
We can do that chef. We can.
我们可以做那个厨师。 我们可以。
Oh go. We have to do it slowly. OK, maybe.
哦去。 我们必须慢慢来。 好吧，也许吧。
We can do that. Yeah.
我们能做到这一点。 是的。
Yeah we can do that.
是的，我们可以做到。
Oh boy, oh, boy.
哦，男孩，哦，男孩。
All right. All right. OK.
好的。 好的。 好的。
I see how it is. Oh.
我明白了。 哦。
We got you, dude.
我们抓住了你，伙计。
Hill, what was I, new chef?
希尔，我是什么，新厨师？
I wasn't even looking
我什至没有看
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
Here's how we do it, is that we go just.
我们是这样做的，就是我们去。
I think we have it down.
我想我们已经搞定了。
We just need to be a little bit quicker.
我们只需要快一点。
Yeah.
是的。
Boy, doh.
男孩，呵呵。
Cheese
起司
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm hmm.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm. Oh.
嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。 哦。
Fuck me.
操我。
Oh, what I did there
哦，我在那里做了什么
I legitimately think we can be on the same.
我有理由认为我们可以保持一致。
We could be on, like, the same side over there, right?
我们可以在那边，就像，同一边，对吧？
I don't know about I don't know about it.
我不知道我不知道。
Like, I, I agree that it seems like it makes sense. But
就像，我，我同意这似乎是有道理的。 但
like, let's try.
喜欢，让我们试试。
Let's try it.
让我们试试看。
Yeah.
是的。
It's not served just yet.
它还没有服务。
I'll come on over you.
我会来找你的。
Can you put the plate on my side? I don't know.
你能把盘子放在我这边吗？ 我不知道。
They'll grab the plate sill
他们会抓住窗台
oh, fuck.
哦，操。
Yeah.
是的。
So I think we just chop a bunch of tomatoes.
所以我想我们只是切碎一堆西红柿。
I'll do that first, and then
我会先这样做，然后
just hoard it. Right?
只是囤积它。 对？
Only the only real thing we can do is jump tomatoes.
我们唯一能做的就是跳西红柿。
Snap a bunch of these little dudes
抓拍一堆这些小家伙，把它们放在角落里。
They don't go bad, right? No.
他们不会变坏，对吧？ 不。
I didn't mean do that.
我不是故意的。
Repair it go up
修上去
and show up oh,
并出现哦，
look at that.
看那个。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
我的天啊。 我的天啊。
It could be big green. Yeah, it could be Big Green.
它可能是大绿色。 是的，它可能是大绿。
Could be big green. Oh, I love
可以是大绿。 哦，我爱
you. Look, all these fucking tomatoes did.
你。 看，所有这些该死的西红柿都做了。
And here we go.
现在我们开始。
And then chop wood. Don't want that.
然后砍木头。 不想那样。
I do.
我愿意。
Lots of dough. Dough is the important part, I think.
很多面团。 我认为面团是重要的部分。
Yeah, just
是的，只是
a few moments later.
片刻之后。
I'll go.
我要走了。
I'll sit up.
我会坐起来。
I'll sit up here.
我会坐在这里。
The I think we need.
我认为我们需要。
Yeah, well, we'll alternate between that
是的，好吧，我们将在这之间交替
that's the one down
那就是我们看不到的东西就像卡住一样
OK that's good to go.
好的，这很好。
I'll grab doughnuts down here for some reason
出于某种原因，我会在这里吃甜甜圈
and it's at the cheese tomato that one needs tomato.
正是在奶酪番茄上，人们需要番茄。
I'll put this in the oven though.
不过我会把这个放在烤箱里。
Oh, fuck. Me.
哦，操。 我。
All right.
好的。
Then.
然后。
Don't threaten me with the good time.
不要用美好的时光来威胁我。
It's not fox
这不是狐狸
I'm going to choke you.
我要让你窒息。
Oh, are you all right?
哦，你还好吗？
All right.
好的。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
I can go for a bit. Spice with excitement.
我可以去一会儿。 兴奋地调味。
Move out of the way.
错。
Oh, my God. Your fat arse is in the way.
我的天啊。 你的肥屁股挡道了。
Sorry that my cake is disrupting you.
对不起，我的蛋糕打扰了你。
It is disrupting me.
它正在扰乱我。
I needs a plate.
我需要一个盘子。
My cake does not need to play God.
我的蛋糕不需要扮演上帝。
So needy.
太需要了
All right?
好的？
I mean, I'm going.
我的意思是，我要去。
To go over here.
去这里。
I'm going to sit here, and he's on the other side,
我要坐在这里，他在另一边，
and I can transfer that directly.
我可以直接转移。
To the plate. Who's going play? Yeah.
到盘子里。 谁去玩？ 是的。
So there's cheese on that.
所以上面有奶酪。
I'll drink.
我会喝。
I'm going to serve
我将为客户提供服务，这样他们就不会生我的气。
About.
关于。
Yeah, that needs to be cool.
是的，那必须很酷。
A minute less shit
少一分钟的狗屎
well, you got one minute left.
好吧，你还剩一分钟。
You doing. A transfer?
你在做。 转会？
I was trying to clean the dirty plate.
我试图清理脏盘子。
I got eight.
我得到了八个。
I think this is working.
我认为这是有效的。
Back when I was Harry Potter.
回到我还是哈利波特的时候。
All way suck
一路很烂
for some reason,
由于某些原因，
I couldn't clean it while that things were
我无法清理它，而那些东西正在花费。
OK, I'm serving, so I'm serving.
好的，我在服务，所以我在服务。
Serving it OK?
服务好吗？
Yeah.
是的。
I mean, this way.
我的意思是，这样。
We did so much better last time.
上次我们做得好多了。
What happened. Here?
发生了什么。 这里？
Yeah.
是的。
We that will happen this time.
我们这一次会发生。
I'm confused.
我很困惑。
Yeah,
是的，我们上次有 700 次，我觉得我们最后一次挣扎得更多。
What we did because it was last night.
我们做了什么，因为那是昨晚。
Maybe we put the pizza on too soon.
也许我们把披萨放得太早了。
We put the pizza in as what we should do.
我们按照我们应该做的那样把披萨放进去。
Let's make like 20 because all of the orders are the same.
让我们做 20 个吧，因为所有的订单都是一样的。
Yeah, it's all the same.
是的，都是一样的。
Like 30 pizzas before we start the timer.
就像我们开始计时之前的 30 个比萨饼。
All you mean like just put it on the floor.
你的意思就是把它放在地板上。
All I see.
我所见。
What you're talking about and then we just clean plates entirely.
你在说什么，然后我们就彻底清洁盘子。
Yeah.
是的。
All right. All right.
好的。 好的。
See, that's.
看，就是这样。
How we game works.
我们的游戏如何运作。
This is how we gamed the system.
这就是我们游戏系统的方式。
This is how we gain the advantage.
这就是我们获得优势的方式。
Also, I just finished all my team this is so silent.
另外，我刚刚完成了我所有的团队，这太沉默了。
My man. My man just got 20 left.
我的男人。 我的男人只剩下20个。
How much time do you have?
你有多少时间？
I've got a big old, like,
我有一个大老头，至少，就像，我想拿胡子茶开玩笑。
Jesus Christ is in the thermos. Do you?
耶稣基督在保温瓶里。 你？
How are you all those people to have a thermos?
你们这些人怎么有热水瓶？
I do. Yeah, it's great. It's great. I can do it.
我愿意。 是的，这很棒。 太好了。 我能做到。
I can do an endurance stream in my tea will still be hot.
我可以在我的茶中进行耐力流仍然很热。
By the end.
到最后。
But didn't you drink all the tea like one time when we were like I did?
但是你不是像以前那样喝了所有的茶吗？
Yeah. During on third it takes to stream.
是的。 在第三个它需要流。
I drank that entire thing of tea.
我喝了整杯茶。
It was pretty bad.
这很糟糕。
Pretty bad.
很糟糕。
No, no, it was good tea.
不，不，这是好茶。
That's why I drank it all about, like, the fact that I drank the entire thing
这就是为什么我把它全部喝掉的原因，就像我在
in, like, 2 hours. Probably not good for my
2 小时内喝完整个东西的事实。 可能对我不好
go. I
去。 我又要抓一堆西红柿了。
But with the tomato over there, well. One.
但是那里有番茄，嗯。 一。
Should remind me.
应该提醒我。
Thank you very much for the expert. Thank you. Thank you.
非常感谢专家。 谢谢你。 谢谢你。
I mean.
我是说。
Don't
别
throw it at your face, apparently.
显然，把它扔到你的脸上。
How Al
阿尔是如何弄伤番茄的
bleep or the don't go
哔哔声或不走
pug, pug, pug.
哈巴狗，哈巴狗，哈巴狗。
Take it out of the thing. Take it out.
把它拿出来。 把它拿出来。
Good boy.
好孩子。
I think I could just place it here.
我想我可以把它放在这里。
I'm going to place these things on the just taunt them with the
我要把这些东西放在上面，用披萨来嘲讽它们
on the floor.
在地上。
Yeah.
是的。
Floor pizza
地板披萨
and got all the cheese over just throwing it over because like,
把所有的奶酪都扔了，因为喜欢，
I know it's faster that way and
我知道这样更快
I'll go over on the other side
我会从另一边过去，这样我就可以抓住哦，
plus. Is this OK?
加。 这个可以吗？
Is this this fine fox?
这是这只好狐狸吗？
No, it's fine. Yeah.
不，没关系。 是的。
The time hasn't even started yet.
时间甚至还没有开始。
So we're chillin,
所以我们很冷静，
which
哪一个
I got the zone.
我得到了区域。
OK, nice.
好的，不错。
Good job.
做得好。
Well, is this actually going to work?
那么，这真的会奏效吗？
We are so many pizzas just stacked up up there.
我们有太多的比萨饼堆在那里。
Way they're not going cold. Oh,
方式他们不会变冷。 哦，
it's ok.
没关系。
It's OK. It's OK.
没关系。 没关系。
What's not cooked?
什么不熟？
It's the pizza on the floor. It's the pizza on the floor.
这是地板上的披萨。 这是地板上的披萨。
Oh, I took it out too early. Oops.
哦，我太早拿出来了。 哎呀。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
I'll yeah.
我会的。
It was that you on the verge of being cold? It was like two.
是你快要凉了吗？ 这就像两个。
It was like two. Sends me away.
这就像两个。 把我送走。
You ended it really bad.
你结局真的很糟糕。
I'm good at.
我擅长。
I walk, I say I'm good at edging.
我走路，我说我擅长磨边。
And fast on the not my experience but you know
并且快速不是我的经验，但只要您认为我是，您就知道。 好的。
Motherfucker, would you prefer me.
混蛋，你会喜欢我吗？
He my cheese.
他是我的奶酪。
To. Not like yeah,
到。 不像是的，
I know exactly what you're thinking of You are soul your soul.
我确切地知道你在想什么你是灵魂你的灵魂。
Viva sly along with your calling cocks and.
万岁和你的公鸡一起狡猾。
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
停，停，停，停。
Oh, ha ha ha.
哦，哈哈哈。
Oh. Bugs.
哦。 错误。
Oh. Sorry.
哦。 对不起。
Sorry.
对不起。
Shot all oh, you re sorry.
全部开枪哦，对不起。
I know I you know, I don't worry about me.
我知道我你知道，我不担心我。
You're fine. You're fine.
你很好。 你很好。
Oh, my God, you arsehole.
哦，我的上帝，你这个混蛋。
Pull this fucking all this fucking pizza watch.
拉这他妈的所有这该死的披萨手表。
It's on the fuck.
它在他妈的。
Up, up, up. On the left one.
上，上，上。 在左边一个。
You got it.
你说对了。
I got it.
我得到了它。
There's so floor if you'd stop.
如果你停下来，那就有地板了。
All right. You reckon we could just stop now?
好的。 你认为我们现在可以停下来吗？
Now let's let's.
现在让我们来吧。
Do a couple more.
多做一两。
Let's do a couple more.
让我们再做几个。
Yeah.
是的。
Emotional damage.
情感伤害。
There's some strategies on the floor right there.
那里有一些策略。
Just grab that
抓住那个
when you shift.
当你换班时。
Oh, that's new strategy.
哦，那是新策略。
What do. I do?
做什么。 我愿意？
This is nuts.
这是疯了。
Pick it out here.
在这里挑出来。
It's OK.
没关系。
This this is exactly how. Restaurants do it.
这正是如此。 餐馆这样做。
I'm pretty sure. Yeah,
我很确定。 是的，他们是专业人士，伙计们。
Not absolutely the most pro fashion professionals.
绝对不是最专业的时尚专业人士。
They hired a dog in a sea turtle to cook their food for them.
他们雇了一只狗在海龟里为他们做饭。
I think that's there on them.
我认为那是在他们身上。
If anything.
如果有什么。
I thought for a second I forgot who you're playing as.
我想了一会儿我忘了你在扮演谁。
I think you're talking about a real life events. Like. No.
我想你在谈论一个现实生活中的事件。 像。 不。
Yeah, yeah.
是啊是啊。
That was like a sea turtle who did, like, all of this cooking.
这就像一只海龟，做了所有这些烹饪。
It was incredible.
实在太棒了。
I was like, what OK.
我当时想，什么好。
So, you know, I think.
所以，你知道，我想。
He's starting to see pizzas, not so much pizzas.
他开始看到比萨饼，而不是比萨饼。
We're like a Domino's right now, just waiting to like, you know, express that.
我们现在就像多米诺骨牌，只是等着喜欢，你知道，表达出来。
How can I help you?
我怎么帮你？
All right.
好的。
Are you ready? Yeah, I'm ready. I'm ready.
你准备好了吗？ 是的，我准备好了。 我已经准备好了。
Yeah. OK.
是的。 好的。
We got it. Like, so it's all about cleaning the plates
我们得到了它。 就像，所以这都是关于清洁盘子
oh. Oh,
哦。 哦，
oh, we were the plates.
哦，我们是盘子。
Olivia we.
奥利维亚我们。
There's one plate down there. Do you see that?
下面有一个盘子。 你看到了吗？
Yeah, I get there.
是的，我到达那里。
Yeah.
是的。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me grab this and clean it
让我抓住这个并清理它
I got cooked.
我煮熟了。
I got cocktails.
我点了鸡尾酒。
It's OK. I'll make. I'll just.
没关系。 我会做的。 我只。
I'll just make another pizza.
我会再做一个披萨。
In the meantime, there we go.
与此同时，我们开始了。
And I get the plates
而且我得到的盘子有很多缺失的盘子。
When all the plates go where they put you.
当所有的盘子都去了他们把你放在哪里。
I just threw some dough. You
我只是扔了一些面团。 你
now I the dough I you got me.
现在我是你给我的面团。
All the dude we have
我们所有的奶酪丝，面团或西红柿，
good.
好的。
The job. The job. You're doing great, babe.
工作。 工作。 你做得很好，宝贝。
I can't thank you.
我不能感谢你。
Can only provide you support as I'm stuck on the other side.
只能为您提供支持，因为我被困在另一边。
And we went through all the pizzas already.
我们已经吃完了所有的比萨饼。
That's crazy. No,
这很疯狂。 不，
odds.
赔率。
You guys want to miss the.
你们想错过的。
This is insane.
疯了吧。
This is such we we keep it.
这就是我们保留它的方式。
Strategic, chefs. We.
战略, 厨师. 我们。
You know, you know.
你知道，你知道。
You know, this is like, dumb arse like the virgin traditional chef,
你知道，这就像处女传统厨师一样的笨蛋，它将食物保持在卫生的位置。
So we just got to work smarter, not harder.
所以我们只需要更聪明地工作，而不是更努力地工作。
The charred, efficient, overcooked chef leaves 10,000
这位烧焦的、高效的、煮过头的厨师会在地上留下
copies of the same food on the ground until they have enough to.
10,000 份相同的食物，直到他们有足够的时间。
So right in. Front of the customer to.
所以就在客户面前。
Shred cheese off the ground, put on a fucking pizza Larry.
把地上的奶酪切碎，放上一个他妈的披萨拉里。
Right in front of them.
就在他们面前。
It is official.
这是官方的。
It is efficient. Yeah.
它是有效的。 是的。
And they're getting their food.
他们正在得到他们的食物。
That's all the letters. On my screen.
这就是所有的字母。 在我的屏幕上。
Is spent on the screen.
是花在屏幕上。
Then I was, like, frothing for cocaine.
然后我就像可卡因一样起泡。
It's been. Like, spitting.
它是。 比如，吐口水。
That's it. That's disappointing. I looked at
这就对了。 这是令人失望的。 我在看
I got locked in.
我被锁了
I'll grab the pizza.
我会拿披萨。
Pizza?
比萨？
The pizza.
披萨。
What are you expecting? Threes.
你在期待什么？ 三人行。
What do you expect, by the way?
顺便说一句，你期待什么？
I just want to ask, is there
我只想问，有没有
is there is there a certain preference
吐口水比吞咽有一定的偏好。
Or are you doing like if someone like were to were to swallow for me?
或者，如果有人要为我吞咽，你会这样做吗？
No, I mean, if you were it's
不，我的意思是，如果你是这样的话，就像你可以在吐痰和吞咽之间做出选择。
Oh, I'd. Swallow.
哦，我愿意。 吞。
OK, yeah. Hey, what's that part?
好的，是的。 嘿，那是什么部分？
Yeah,
是的，
no, I'm.
不，我是。
Not even a top or bottom.
甚至没有顶部或底部。
It's just it's just like. Yeah, I like it where.
就是这样。 是的，我喜欢它在哪里。
If you if you're mad enough to take a shot in the mouth, you should get
如果你疯到嘴里开一枪，你至少应该让他们体面地把它当作食物。
You know? Mm hmm. Yeah. It's a lot of protein.
你知道？ 嗯嗯。 是的。 这是很多蛋白质。
Lots and lots of protein.
很多很多的蛋白质。
I think we're talking about the same thing, right?
我想我们说的是同一件事，对吧？
To the same thing. Yeah, of course you are.
对于同样的事情。 是的，你当然是。
And can you get that fucking bitch?
你能得到那个该死的婊子吗？
Oh, yeah. It's just a little overcooked.
哦耶。 只是有点煮过头了。
Get it?
得到它？
Why do we have 1300 points?
为什么我们有1300分？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This is, like, our best.
这是，就像，我们最好的。
Squirrel is going to look at me.
松鼠会看着我。
Like, do you guys cheat? And we're like, no.
比如，你们作弊吗？ 我们就像，不。
No, you didn't.
不，你没有。
She see, he's happy. Oh.
她看到了，他很开心。 哦。
Look at that.
看那个。
31 more point.
还有31点。
And it would have been kind of cool.
这会很酷。
Oh, yeah, it would have been really cool.
哦，是的，那会很酷。
Probably kind of wheat, if anything.
可能是小麦，如果有的话。
You always, always like your back.
你永远，永远喜欢你的背影。
The knuckles.
指关节。
Oh, no, that was. That was my water bottle.
哦，不，那是。 那是我的水瓶。
Right? I thought that was your back. Oh, no.
对？ 我以为那是你的背影。 不好了。
Oh, I'm no
哦，我不是
VOCs.
挥发性有机化合物。
I'm nowhere near that.
我离那还很远。
I mean, you might be.
我的意思是，你可能是。
You're like 400, but for me.
你就像400，但对我来说。
I still got, like, what, 80, 90 years ahead of me?
我还有，比如，什么，比我早 80、90 年？
I'm chilling.
我不寒而栗。
I'm great.
我很好。
And I.
和我。
I guess, I guess that's true.
我猜，我猜这是真的。
I mean, not all of us can have.
我的意思是，并非我们所有人都能拥有。
Not all of us can have. Have.
不是我们所有人都能拥有。 有。
Why are we backing out of them?
为什么我们要退出他们？
Because I keep accidentally hit the fucking spacebar.
因为我一直不小心按到他妈的空格键。
Here, get.
来，得到。
I mean, this is my bag, you know, I'm sorry.
我的意思是，这是我的包，你知道，我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
What's the subject?
主题是什么？
Me to the pizza. That's where you're at.
我去吃披萨。 那就是你所在的地方。
Harry Potter's Hogwarts School of of mockery.
哈利波特的霍格沃茨嘲讽学校。
Visuals. I thought it was or something.
视觉效果。 我以为是什么。
There is a bone.
有一块骨头。
Yeah, it's one of the Kevin Love ornaments.
是的，它是 Kevin Love 的装饰品之一。
Given how. Many?
鉴于如何。 许多？
We have a three fucking wait.
我们他妈的等了三个。
There's Kevin's. There's a lot of Kevin.
有凯文的。 凯文有很多。
It's looking Kevin's.
它正在寻找凯文的。
Have we missed brother brother.
我们有没有想念哥哥哥哥。
Brother, brother.
兄弟，兄弟。
I'm an occasional brother. Hmm.
我是一个偶尔的兄弟。 唔。
I partake in a brother.
我参加了一个兄弟。
You know, I. We going to draw, right?
你知道，我。我们要画画，对吧？
Why do you have to be the one that drives?
为什么你必须成为开车的人？
Why can't I drive?
为什么我不能开车？
Because I'm because I'm a bowler.
因为我是因为我是投球手。
Because I'm a gangster like that.
因为我就是这样的黑帮。
Made zero sense.
零意义。
Actually made zero sense there.
实际上在那里零意义。
Why are you why who made you put.
你为什么是谁让你放的。
You in control of the steering wheel?
你在控制方向盘？
But you on the planet.
但是你在这个星球上。
I love the SpongeBob references.
我喜欢海绵宝宝的参考资料。
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。
I can't find the other Kevin levels.
我找不到其他凯文级别。
Do you want to do the John do?
你想做约翰做的事吗？
Let's do the super difficult Kevin level and then we'll see.
让我们做超级困难的凯文级别，然后我们会看到。
Yeah, let's try and do the Kevin one.
是的，让我们试着做凯文的。
And then we call it there.
然后我们在那里调用它。
Yeah. Only 580. How bad could it be?
是的。 只有580。能有多糟糕？
Yeah. How bad could it be?
是的。 到底能有多糟糕？
Steve.
史蒂夫。
Oh you said steamed. I said steamed them.
哦，你说蒸。 我说蒸了。
Oh, we're doing steamed again.
哦，我们又开始蒸了。
Well, we're. Masters.
嗯，我们是。 大师。
You're on Oddfellow but I must say, you seem a good ham.
你在 Oddfellow 但我必须说，你看起来是个好火腿。
You do that very well, you know that.
你做得很好，你知道的。
It's like you watched. It was times.
就像你看过一样。 这是时代。
I kind of have all this.
我有点拥有这一切。
All this is confusing me. Oh, no. Oh, no.
这一切都让我感到困惑。 不好了。 不好了。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, and there is fire everywhere. OK.
哦，到处都是火。 好的。
Really, it's gone. Do that to us.
真的，没了。 对我们这样做。
All right, well.
好吧，好吧。
Good luck, sir.
祝你好运，先生。
Let's start steaming some fish.
让我们开始蒸一些鱼。
When there are carrots.
有胡萝卜的时候。
We got carrots.
我们有胡萝卜。
You got carrots? Oh,
你有胡萝卜吗？ 哦，
I think.
我认为。
I think we should make use of the fire extinguisher this time, though.
不过，我认为这次我们应该使用灭火器。
I think that's what you have to do.
我认为这是你必须做的。
So we don't like
所以我们不喜欢
I'll just have you on sound bite.
我只会让你在原声带上。
Fuck you. Oh, my God.
去你的。 我的天啊。
Look at all these.
看看所有这些。
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit. Oh, look.
该死，该死，该死，该死，该死，该死，该死，该死，该死。 哦，看。
Yeah.
是的。
The fires.
火灾。
Oh, I'm literally trapped, dude.
哦，我真的被困住了，伙计。
On a on a on a hot. I'm coming, I'm coming, babe.
上一个上一个热。 我来了，我来了，宝贝。
I'm coming.
我来了。
It's trying to trap you can.
它试图诱捕你可以。
Godzilla it
哥斯拉吧
ok. Ah.
行。 啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This is confusing.
这令人困惑。
Carrot and flowers. Oh.
胡萝卜和鲜花。 哦。
I want
我想
this looks like shoe. My.
这看起来像鞋子。 我的。
I had you my before every for sum.
我有你我之前的每一个总和。
You ever had them some. I've had them some. Yeah.
你曾经有过一些。 我吃过一些。 是的。
It's like
它像是
for sure has shrimp inside of it.
里面肯定有虾。
It's like a dumpling, but not really a dumpling.
它就像一个饺子，但不是真正的饺子。
It's like has one on are dropping all these yeah.
就像有一个正在丢弃所有这些是的。
It's really good.
这真的很好。
Fuck OK,
他妈的好吧，
this one's good to go on a plate. It
这个很适合放在盘子里。 它
well, that's very beautiful.
嗯，那很漂亮。
I thought we were having steamed clams.
我以为我们在吃蒸蛤蜊。
You're silly.
你好笨。
You're silly. Little did you know that, right?
你好笨。 你对此知之甚少，对吧？
Oh, no, no. We're trapped again.
哦，不，不。 我们又被困住了。
Blow it, blow it. Thank you. The job
吹吧吹吧 谢谢你。 工作
and we have
我们也必须同时洗碗，兄弟。
Brah.
布拉。
Yeah, this this level is going to be the end of me.
是的，这个级别将是我的终结。
We do only have to get 500 to be fair. OK,
我们只需要得到 500 就可以公平。 好的，
oh, fuck me.
哦，操我。
Oh, fuck you.
哦，去你妈的。
You can kind of the grass
你可以种草
boo ha.
嘘哈。
Drop and everything.
下降和一切。
But I got it. I got it.
但我明白了。 我得到了它。
I got it. I got it. I got it. OK, just calm down.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。 我得到了它。 好吧，冷静点。
Calm down, calm down, calm down. There we go.
冷静，冷静，冷静。 我们去吧。
OK, it's cooking.
好的，正在做饭。
It's cooking.
它正在做饭。
I'm putting out the fucking fires are so annoying.
我正在扑灭他妈的大火太烦人了。
OK, thank you for the plates.
好的，谢谢你的盘子。
Thank you for the fresh clean plates.
感谢您提供新鲜干净的盘子。
I need
我需要
oh, my.
天啊。
Got it.
知道了。
I'm not mad, Maxine, as much as I want to.
玛克辛，我没有生气，尽管我想生气。
That's OK. I'm your nurse. We know.
那没问题。 我是你的护士。 我们知道。
All right, we need.
好吧，我们需要。
We need. We need shrimp and shrimp. Shrimp.
我们需要。 我们需要虾和虾。 虾。
Fuck, I need.
他妈的，我需要。
I need the fire extinguisher. Holy shit.
我需要灭火器。 天啊。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The plate.
碟子。
Overdue plate.
过期盘。
Wait a second. What? What do I do?
等一下。 什么？ 我该怎么办？
I put the shrimp in the dirt and I put.
我把虾放在泥土里，然后放了。
The inside
里面
wow. Wow.
哇。 哇。
Oh, 10, oh, oh, oh, no.
哦，10，哦，哦，哦，不。
I got to chop the shrimp up.
我得把虾切碎。
Sholto you fucking dumb arse.
Sholto你他妈的愚蠢的屁股。
OK, now, now we're bugging
好的，现在，现在我们正在窃听
30 seconds.
30秒。
30 seconds. This one's off. This one.
30秒。 这个下架了 这个。
This one's really rough.
这个真的很粗
I got trapped. I'm trapped. Oh, no.
我被困住了。 我被困住了。 不好了。
I got it.
我得到了它。
All right, OK.
好的，好的。
General.
一般的。
Clinically and strangely.
临床和奇怪。
All. There's one right there.
全部。 那里有一个。
There's one right there is one right there.
那里有一个，那里有一个。
This is a disaster.
这是一场灾难。
Oh, no, I can't grab it because the fire is in the.
哦，不，我不能抓住它，因为火在里面。
Oh, no, wait. That's the other one.
哦，不，等等。 那是另一个。
Yeah, this is bad. Is really bad.
是的，这很糟糕。 真的很糟糕。
Paul Shetler. Pizarro style zero.
保罗·谢特勒。 皮萨罗风格零。
One star.
一星。
Hmm. I mean, technically, beat it.
唔。 我的意思是，从技术上讲，打败它。
But like. You.
不过喜欢。 你。
There's just so much fire going around. What are you guys now?
周围有这么多火。 你们现在是什么人？
You think we can do it?
你认为我们能做到吗？
Can we do it?
我们能做到吗？
I think we do it.
我认为我们做到了。
OK, all right.
好的没问题。
Gay, gay, homosexual, gay.
同性恋，同性恋，同性恋，同性恋。
Thank you for the song.
谢谢你的歌。
About The.
有关。
Fonz.
方兹。
Yeah, I like the fact that at least not on mic.
是的，我喜欢至少不在麦克风上的事实。
Like, not on call.
就像，不随叫随到。
I haven't heard you've had you've thanked, like, subs, but not by name.
我还没有听说你曾感谢过，比如，潜艇，但不是按名字。
And so all of a sudden, like, the first gay, gay, homosexual,
突然之间，就像，第一个同性恋，同性恋，同性恋，同性恋，就像，我只是没有为此做好准备。
I had to read out that name.
我不得不读出那个名字。
It's golden.
它是金色的。
Is it?
是吗？
Is it is a golden boy. Yeah.
难道是金童。 是的。
Okay, what's up? What's up, fish?
好的，怎么了？ 怎么了，鱼？
That you fish? I'm good at fish.
那你钓鱼？ 我擅长鱼。
Grab this fire extinguisher and put it close by just in case
拿起这个灭火器，把它放在附近以防万一
this is bullshit.
这是胡说八道。
I'll grab the flower flower and bring flowers and carrots.
我会抓住花花，带来鲜花和胡萝卜。
Flowers and carrots carrots and flowers.
鲜花和胡萝卜 胡萝卜和鲜花。
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
天啊。 天啊。 天啊。
Wait.
等待。
Where's the fire extinguisher and the extinguisher?
灭火器和灭火器在哪里？
Extinguisher. Thanks.
灭火器。 谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
There we go.
我们去吧。
We'll see each shrimp
我们会看到每只虾
ok? OK.
好的？ 好的。
A plate
一个碟子
we. Oh, while I was cooking there
我们。 哦，当我在那里做饭的时候
shrimp uncovered some shrimp.
虾发现了一些虾。
Right now
现在
oh, sorry.
哦对不起。
All right,
好的，
I'm going to put this in the bowl.
我要把这个放在碗里。
That's fine.
没事儿。
Do it. All this fucking fire.
去做吧。 所有这该死的火。
That's some fire.
那是一些火。
All this bullshit blazing
所有这些废话都在燃烧
OK. Shrimps going in there.
好的。 虾进去了
And I'm going to put that's all
我要把所有的面粉、面粉和虾都放进去。
From some church, from church.
来自某个教堂，来自教堂。
I have a plunger. Oh, I know you can do another one.
我有一个柱塞。 哦，我知道你可以再做一个。
Yeah, I got this. I got the shrimp. I got the shrimp.
是的，我得到了这个。 我得到了虾。 我得到了虾。
I can. I can cook this one.
我可以。 我可以煮这个。
Please. No.
请。 不。
Oh, no, no.
哦，不，不。
My the microseconds away.
我的微秒。
Oh, I'm so pissed.
哦，我好生气。
I got it. I got it.
我得到了它。 我得到了它。
Oh, no, no. The fire.
哦，不，不。 火。
Oh, no.
不好了。
Oh, sell it.
哦，卖掉。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Parker, this is hard.
帕克，这很难。
The fire is such a clock.
火就是这样一个时钟。
Oh, I've never been so, like, I've never.
哦，我从来没有这样，就像，我从来没有。
Been so caught by fire. Before.
就这么着火了。 前。
It's even cooked the flour or not the flour.
它甚至是煮面粉或不煮面粉。
All of it.
所有的。
Jesus,
耶稣，
and we work together now.
我们现在一起工作。
Do you think it's logical for one of us to always have the the,
你认为我们中的一个人总是拥有这个是合乎逻辑的，
you know, the fire extinguisher on.
你知道，灭火器开着。
In it go around with the fire extinguisher just getting rid of fire?
在它周围用灭火器摆脱火灾？
Yeah.
是的。
Like, one person handles fire extinguishing and, like,
就像，一个人处理灭火，就像，
I don't know, cleaning plates, and maybe that'll work,
我不知道，清洁盘子，也许这会起作用，
like, get, like, some kind of system there, because, like,
喜欢，得到，喜欢，某种系统，因为，喜欢，我们不能只保留，喜欢，有一个人，喜欢，
each of us, like, go back and forth with this extinguisher right.
我们每个人，就像，带着这个灭火器来回走动。
What do you think?
你怎么看？
Emotional damage.
情感伤害。
Yeah, I think if he's.
是的，我想如果他是的话。
There's a lot going on, we keep failing orders as well.
发生了很多事情，我们也不断失败订单。
Yeah.
是的。
Like, I can prioritise taking out the fire
比如，我可以优先灭火
and like when I can, I'll help you out with the smaller things about that.
如果可以的话，我会帮你解决一些小问题。
But that sounds good. Yeah. All right. Let's try that.
但这听起来不错。 是的。 好的。 让我们试试看。
OK, we start
好的，我们开始
all right.
好的。
All right. You that.
好的。 你那个。
Oh, right.
啊对。
Yeah, I got to be maybe like that guy from fire force. So
是的，我得像消防队的那个人一样。 所以
she never watch the the me.
她从不看我。
I don't. Know.
我不。 知道。
I was going.
我正想。
I show you this picture.
我给你看这张照片。
I know I can help
我知道我可以帮忙
we're always in need of, like.
我们总是需要，喜欢。
Flowers
花朵
like that.
像那样。
He goes one.
他去一个。
Put some flowering carrot.
放一些开花的胡萝卜。
Good.
好的。
Grab the shrimp and put it in here. With the sweet good. Yeah.
抓住虾，把它放在这里。 与甜蜜的好。 是的。
Yeah. And I'm going start taking out some fires.
是的。 我将开始扑灭一些火灾。
Oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Can you take out this one, please?
请把这个拿出来好吗？
Really quick
真快
thank you.
谢谢你。
That's one dish.
那是一道菜。
Balance. Good.
平衡。 好的。
I'm gonna put it inside.
我要把它放进去。
It's a flower
这是一朵花
shit.
拉屎。
Clay fish. Fresh fish.
泥鱼。 鲜鱼。
Yeah, fish.
对，鱼。
The fish ones are really easy.
鱼的真的很简单。
Yeah,
是的，
I got that.
我明白了。
I got that a plate up.
我拿了一个盘子。
Like, right now,
比如现在，
send it out fucking way. Why?
发送出去他妈的方式。 为什么？
We just got to Justin them straight away, OK?
我们马上就去找贾斯汀他们，好吗？
I can you get the higher overhead, please?
我能得到更高的开销吗？
Yeah. Yeah, I got you. I got you. Yeah, yeah.
是的。 是的，我得到了你。 我接到你了。 是啊是啊。
Right now, like I need to before it burns.
现在，就像我需要在它燃烧之前一样。
Yeah, you got it. You got it.
是的，你明白了。 你说对了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
The three plates right now, since that's a priority.
现在三个板块，因为这是一个优先事项。
I have to go
我得走了
finally to fish.
终于可以钓鱼了。
Once.
一次。
OK, now plate's going.
好的，现在盘子开始了。
It's already. Meat. Me, me, me, me, me.
已经是了。 肉。 我，我，我，我，我。
I got.
我有。
I'm going to put the fish, the plate, the fish one.
我要放鱼，盘子，鱼一个。
You're doing a really good job of the day place, by the way.
顺便说一句，你在日常工作中做得非常好。
Thank you.
谢谢你。
Oh, shit.
妈的。
Look, I was going to.
看，我本来打算的。
Park here and clean the plates right now.
在这里停车并立即清洁盘子。
Ah. I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
啊。 我被困住了。 我被困住了。
Oh, yeah. I got you, I got you, I got you.
哦耶。 我得到你，我得到你，我得到你。
Shit.
拉屎。
You're OK.
你还行。
Oh, nice. Nice.
不错哦。 好的。
This is all right,
没关系，花
let's meet.
咱们见面吧。
This and some flower down pre-emptively.
这和一些花落先发制人。
Cute into that.
可爱到那个。
Yeah, I'm going to handle to meet.
是的，我要去处理见面。
Wants to meet once again.
想再见面。
Yeah, dirty dishes. I got three dishes.
是的，脏盘子。 我点了三个菜。
We need some more dishes.
我们需要更多的菜。
It looks like
看起来像
I. Got you fired. One
I. 让你被解雇了。 一
please.
请。
Please. This one. This one.
请。 这个。 这个。
This one right now. Or.
现在的这个。 或者。
I just have to take that off of the two.
我只需要从两者中删除它。
Got off. OK, ok. This one's got this one. Good.
下来。 好的好的。 这个有这个。 好的。
Yeah, that's that's right.
是的，这是正确的。
And let me just quickly point that I think we've got time.
让我快速指出我认为我们有时间。
Yeah,
是的，
oh, nice, nice, nice.
哦，不错，不错，不错。
OK, this plate's ready to pull this back.
好的，这个盘子已经准备好把它拉回来了。
Yep. That's ready.
是的。 那准备好了。
That's ready.
那准备好了。
Oh. Gaming.
哦。 赌博。
Gaming.
赌博。
Yeah, we're getting we're getting more gaming.
是的，我们得到了更多的游戏。
There's a fish ready to cut.
有一条鱼可以切了。
There's a fish already cut.
一条鱼已经切好了。
Yeah, I'll got that. I'll get the.
是的，我会得到的。 我会得到的。
I'm going to clean up the plate real quick.
我要快速清理盘子。
Yep. OK. OK.
是的。 好的。 好的。
I've seen all. No, I'm stuck.
我都看过了。 不，我被困住了。
I'm stuck. I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
我被困住了。 我被困住了，我被困住了。
Let me get.
让我拿。
It. OK.
它。 好的。
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I can play this. You go get the ball.
谢谢你。 谢谢你。 谢谢你。 我可以玩这个。 你去拿球。
Get the fish. Get the fish.
得到鱼。 得到鱼。
Yeah. Oh, no, I got the fish.
是的。 哦，不，我有鱼。
Fucking keeps me from getting the fish.
他妈的让我抓不到鱼。
Then we go.
然后我们走。
Play.
玩。
Oh, it was. Oh, glory, isn't it?
哦，原来如此。 哦，荣耀，不是吗？
No. Oh, my God.
不，哦，我的上帝。
I think we got one more. I think we need one more.
我想我们还有一个。 我想我们还需要一个。
Oh, dude.
哦，伙计。
The fire literally specifically cooked the fish. 10.
火确实专门煮熟了鱼。  10.
I was really. Oh, so close.
我真的。 哦，那么近。
Oh, my gosh.
天啊。
Oh, all right. Oh.
哦那好吧。 哦。
Don't try one more. Enjoy.
不要再尝试一个。 享受。
I want to be one more.
我想再成为一个。
I want to do one more. One more.
我还想做一个。 多一个。
Yeah, just one more.
是的，就多了一个。
OK, last one last one for a moment.
好的，最后一个最后一个。
All right.
好的。
This is our last attempt, and we'll call it there.
这是我们的最后一次尝试，我们会在那里调用它。
Let's get.
让我们得到。
Young men
年轻人
this is the fire specifically
这是火专门曾经有过的那个，就是这样一个。
Wooden arse
木屁股
grab a. Flower.
抢一个。 花。
Just get that going.
就这样吧。
Yeah, I'll get a flower going over here for eating crab.
是啊，我会拿一朵花去这里吃螃蟹。
So we got a meat one.
所以我们得到了一个肉的。
We got a carrot one.
我们有一个胡萝卜。
OK, meat
好，肉
carrot.
胡萝卜。
This flower and the other one right there for you to.
这朵花和另一朵就在那里等着你。
Suck now.
现在吸。
Fish. Yeah, I got fish.
鱼。 是的，我有鱼。
But another Carol.
但另一个卡罗尔。
I got that.
我明白了。
I'm going put in the steam.
我要投入蒸汽。
I go handle the fires right now.
我现在去处理火灾。
Three, up, three.
三，上，三。
So, OK, you know, it's not that's not what it was.
所以，好吧，你知道，这不是它原来的样子。
I can you extinguish this for me?
你能为我熄灭这个吗？
Yeah, I got you.
是的，我得到了你。
But at the last.
但最后。
Go here, the swans get Scott Anderson out.
去这里，天鹅把斯科特·安德森弄出来。
There we go.
我们去吧。
Youngest son out the carrot mm.
小儿子出萝卜mm。
Perfect.
完美的。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Yeah, grab that. Thank you.
是的，抓住那个。 谢谢你。
The extinguished fire's over here.
扑灭的大火就在这里。
Do the carrot with this one.
用这个做胡萝卜。
It locked me in. It locked me in.
它把我锁在里面。它把我锁在里面。
Oh, no, I'm fine.
哦，不，我很好。
OK, you.
好的，你。
Bought a.
买了一个。
Dirty place.
肮脏的地方。
I'm going around every place.
我到处走走。
Can you fish inside?
里面可以钓鱼吗？
Fish? Yep. Inside you.
鱼？ 是的。 在你的内心。
And then I can I can prepare your prawn.
然后我可以准备你的虾。
I do that.
我这样做。
Excellent, excellent, excellent.
优秀，优秀，优秀。
Handle my shrimp.
处理我的虾。
Perfect.
完美的。
Now the is you're having.
现在是你拥有的。
Yeah, I got you.
是的，我得到了你。
I got you.
我接到你了。
A fucking
一个他妈的
and. I.
和。 一世。
Was ready.
准备好了。
OK? There's more dirty plants up.
好的？ 上面有更多的脏植物。
Thanks.
谢谢。
And when I put another flower in the mix.
当我在混合物中放另一朵花时。
We got you already got shrimp for.
我们已经为您准备好了虾。
Me, but I'm playing shrimp
我，但我在玩虾
nice birds.
好鸟。
Yeah, OK.
是的，好的。
Got it.
知道了。
Nice warm water coming really close. Really close.
漂亮的温水真的很近。 真的很近。
All right.
好的。
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me. Next
我，我，我，我，我，我，我，我。 下一个
I'll give you plates and give you plates.
我会给你盘子，给你盘子。
We need more plates. One
我们需要更多的盘子。 一
shrimp is ready to go.
虾准备好了。
Yeah, yeah. Plates. Plates.
是啊是啊。 盘子。 盘子。
Uh, excuse me.
呃，对不起。
Let me just
让我只是
that one.
那个。
Yeah, you got it.
是的，你明白了。
You got it.
你说对了。
You go.
你去。
I'm going to go, and I'm going to go and start these fires over here.
我要去，我要去这里生火。
How many more fish
还有多少鱼
yeah.
是的。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Let me clean more plates.
让我清理更多盘子。
Real thing.
真实的东西。
I get at least two more plates up OK?
我至少再弄两个盘子好吗？
If one plates, you're not a plate right there.
如果一个盘子，你就不是一个盘子。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Yeah. I'm going to take it.
是的。 我要接受它。
Everything else I fish for fish. Yep.
其他一切我都是为了鱼而钓鱼。 是的。
Yeah.
是的。
Put more plates in
放入更多盘子
all right.
好的。
We got the 500.
我们拿到了500。
Just keep it going. Keep going, keep going, keep going.
只要继续下去。 继续，继续，继续。
Just keep going.
尽管继续。
And don't fuck up.
不要搞砸了。
There we go.
我们去吧。
Shrimp, shrimp, shrimp. OK, we got it right there.
虾，虾，虾。 好的，我们就在那里。
OK, we'll go focus on fire and grill.
好的，我们将专注于火和烧烤。
That's when Karen.
那是凯伦的时候。
Fucks up because the fire
搞砸了，因为火
just keep your momentum up.
只要保持你的势头。
You got this?
你有这个吗？
Yeah.
是的。
I've got back.
我已经回来了。
Yeah, on the.
是的，在。
Thank you. Got it.
谢谢你。 知道了。
I got it.
我得到了它。
We got it.
我们得到了它。
We got it, got it. Got it.
我们明白了，明白了。 知道了。
I think it's 540. Yeah.
我认为是540。是的。
No nuts.
没有坚果。
Oh, yeah. 80.
哦耶。  80.
We need one more.
我们还需要一个。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I felt like we were so cracked that right?
我觉得我们很崩溃，对吧？
Yeah. We did so well too.
是的。 我们也做得很好。
What's so hard Alonso? Difficult
阿隆索有什么难的？ 难的
oh, kinky.
哦，变态。
Thank you for this. Super glad you're enjoying this stream.
这次真是万分感谢。 非常高兴你喜欢这个流。
We did our best there.
我们在那里尽力了。
We did our best yeah.
我们尽力了是的。
That fucking dog.
那条该死的狗
Oh, oh.
哦，哦。
But yeah, I'm down. You want to wrap. It, though?
但是，是的，我下来了。 你想包装。 不过呢？
Yeah, I'm. Done. So wrap it up there. That's all for. Now.
是的，我是。 完毕。 所以把它包起来。 这就是全部。 现在。
I'm sleepy now.
我现在困了。
I've already done that. Have you done two stories today?
我已经这样做了。 你今天做了两个故事吗？
Yeah. You have. You should get some rest there.
是的。 你有。 你应该在那里休息一下。
Two streams. Yeah, I will, I will.
两条流。 是的，我会的，我会的。
I'm going to get ready for tomorrow.
我要为明天做准备。
I've been out of thing because we didn't manage to finish Jump King a few days ago.
我已经出局了，因为我们几天前没能完成 Jump King。
I'm thinking tomorrow I might, like, start a little early,
我在想明天我可能会早一点开始，看看我能不能跳完。
If you like an endurance, you're at the church now or I'm.
如果你喜欢耐力，你现在在教堂，或者我在。
At the church.
在教堂。
And I recall that the reason it took me so long to beat it was because, like,
我记得我花了这么长时间才打败它的原因是，就像，我的大脑在那个时候被打破了，我只是，
like, I was getting carpal tunnel in my thumb.
就像，我的拇指进了腕管。
So, like, every, every time I did a jump
所以，就像，每次，我跳的时候，我的拇指都会抽搐，我就会跳。
my thumb would twitch and I would just jump. Yeah, you're.
是的，你是。
Tired. You're getting, like, really twitchy, and, like.
疲劳的。 你变得，就像，真的很抽搐，而且，就像。
I was hungry.
我饿了。
Like, I'd been on a string for 17 hours straight.
就像，我已经连续 17 个小时在弦上。
It was not good. Yeah. Oh, good.
这不好。 是的。 哦，很好。
So I was thinking, like, on a better health, more healthy sound of,
所以我在想，就像，关于更好的健康，更健康的声音，
like, mind and body.
比如，思想和身体。
I reckon I'd be able to beat it in, like, 2 hours, so I might start tomorrow.
我估计我能在 2 小时内击败它，所以我可能明天开始。
Just do jump King really early and then switch to Minecraft in the afternoon.
早点跳King，然后在下午切换到Minecraft。
All right. Yeah. OK, thank you so much for.
好的。 是的。 好的，非常感谢。
Coming out to overcoat with me in. Shelton.
出来和我一起穿大衣。谢尔顿。
It's been a lot of fun. I really enjoyed.
这很有趣。 我真的很喜欢。
It. Turned from moulding to, like.
它。 从成型变成了像。
Sexual to like coordinating like 100%.
性喜欢协调喜欢 100%。
I quite genuinely these are the most advanced call outs
我非常真诚地这些是最先进的呼唤
I've made in a game which I used to play like really sweetly.
我制作了一款我曾经玩得很甜的游戏。
Like, I like this is kind of this is more call.
就像，我喜欢这样，这是更多的电话。
That's what I hear in most Apex matches. This is insane.
这是我在大多数 Apex 比赛中听到的。 疯了吧。
You know, I had a lot of fun with this yeah.
你知道，我玩得很开心是的。
I a lot of fun to do one.
我做一个很有趣。
Thank you for cooking with me.
谢谢你和我一起做饭。
Well, it's uncanny. Thank you. All right.
好吧，这太不可思议了。 谢谢你。 好的。
Have a good day, dude. Take care and get some rest.
祝你有美好的一天，伙计。 保重并休息一下。
We worked really hard. All right.
我们真的很努力。 好的。
I'll see you around.
我会看到你的。
Bye bye.
再见。
Bye bye. VOCs secure. Bye bye.
再见。  VOC 安全。 再见。
OK, let me close out of
好的，让我结束这件事，我会暂时摘下厨师的帽子。
So give me a monumental all right?
所以给我一个不朽的好吗？
So I can so we can talk about what happened earlier,
所以我可以所以我们可以谈谈之前发生的事情，因为不认为不认为我没看到
what our one sound and shot the entire time.
我们的一个声音和整个时间都在拍摄。
I just I couldn't adjust the I can moment
我只是无法调整我可以的时刻
Hmm. Hello?
唔。 你好？
Yeah.
是的。
Matsuura and Hepner. Both of you.
松浦和赫普纳。 你们俩。
What was I, huh?
我是什么，嗯？
Machida.
町田。
You have nerves.
你有神经。
What was that, guys? Oh, my God.
那是什么，伙计们？ 我的天啊。
Like, hundreds upon hundreds of hundreds,
就像，成百上千，就像排在第一位的肠道真空吸尘器一样。
Yeah, I was insane.
是的，我疯了。
Yeah, it was like a sub war that was happening the entire time.
是的，这就像一场一直在发生的子战争。
Meanwhile, me and Vox were just, like, fucking around and just, like, tossing
与此同时，我和 Vox 只是，就像，他妈的，只是，就像，折腾
bread and cheese all over the place, like, oh, my God, guys, you're insane.
面包和奶酪到处都是，就像，哦，天哪，伙计们，你疯了。
You should do it. It.
你应该这样做。 它。
Thank you so much for all the gift subs. Hold on.
非常感谢你所有的礼物潜艇。 坚持，稍等。
Let me see the actual number, because I was a lot like 700. 600
让我看看实际数字，因为我很像 700. 600
Jesus guys.
耶稣伙计们。
Oh, my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
For real.
真的。
Thank you so much for all the support and the gifts up during the stream.
非常感谢您在直播期间的所有支持和礼物。
And I apologise.
我道歉。
I can say thank you earlier.
我可以早点说谢谢。
I'll go through now and read through some of them.
我现在将通读其中的一些。
Oh, because I think I feel bad I didn't get to say I thank you.
哦，因为我觉得我很难过，所以我没能说谢谢。
For many of them, it's all thank you for the 100 bits.
对于他们中的许多人来说，这一切都感谢您提供的 100 位。
You did great today. Thank you for the hard work. Simple.
你今天做得很好。 感谢您的辛勤工作。 简单的。
No problem.
没问题。
I'm glad you guys enjoyed our little cooking session with the demon
我很高兴你们喜欢我们与恶魔的小烹饪课
grease. Thank you for the bits.
润滑脂。 谢谢你的比特。
Um, I remember.
嗯，我记得。
Thank you for the thank you guys for the results.
谢谢你们，谢谢你们的结果。
And that's your one cage.
那是你的一个笼子。
Thank you for. That's all the chicken nuggets.
谢谢你。 这就是所有的鸡块。
Thank you for the five gift subs. Your ghosts problem.
谢谢你的五个礼物潜艇。 你的鬼问题。
Thank you for the 105 gift subs, by the way.
顺便说一句，谢谢你的 105 份礼物。
My God, you're Enzo Galea.
我的上帝，你是恩佐·加利亚。
Thank you for the $50 donation.
感谢您捐赠 50 美元。
I hope you enjoy the stream. Thank you for sticking around for so long.
我希望你喜欢这个流。 谢谢你这么久的陪伴。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
I wonder if Vox is still.
我想知道Vox是否还在。
No, I don't have his thingy. Fuck.
不，我没有他的东西。 他妈的。
I was going to bring him up and kiss him on the cheek.
我打算把他抱起来亲吻他的脸颊。
But no, I can't do that right now.
但是不，我现在不能这样做。
Enzo, I see her
恩佐，我看见她了
oh, yeah.
哦耶。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
So on the eve of the bids or I thank you for the bits till Matsuda,
所以在投标前夕，或者我感谢你直到松田的比特，
I think for the 10th thousand bits as well.
我认为也是第 10000 位。
Thank you for all the bits for all the gift subs.
谢谢你所有的礼物潜艇。
Still, like you guys give so much, you don't have to give real uri, provide
尽管如此，就像你们付出了这么多一样，你不必给真正的
some mushy community and for for everybody that hangs out here.
uri，为在这里闲逛的每个人提供一些糊状的社区。
So thank you so much for that.
所以非常感谢你。
All right, you don't have to, guys. It's OK.
好吧，伙计们，你不必这样做。 没关系。
It means a lot, though. For real.
不过，这意味着很多。 真的。
Just so much.
就这么多。
There's just so much love to the community, man.
对社区有太多的爱，伙计。
There's a lot.
有很多。
Yagi. Thanks for the doll.
八木。 谢谢你的娃娃。
Now, it's hot as a summer.
现在，酷热如夏。
Summer today, and I'm in intense heat because you've to my heart.
今天夏天，我在酷暑中，因为你有我的心。
Thank you for the call.
谢谢你的来电。
Thank you so much for dropping by, dude.
非常感谢你的光临，伙计。
And hope you're having a great night.
并希望你有一个美好的夜晚。
That's all.
就这些。
That's just back.
那是刚回来。
And for if I see right here, guys.
如果我看到这里，伙计们。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
And Hyperion, thank you for the gift subs as well.
Hyperion，也感谢您提供的礼物。
And so chicken nuggets.
还有鸡块。
Thank you for five more GIF subs in. No, no, thank you. For five years.
谢谢你的另外五个 GIF 订阅。不，不，谢谢。 五年。
I've done you a UTI.
我给你做了尿路感染。
Thank you for the bits and college.
谢谢你的比特和大学。
Thank you for the tier one and run.
感谢您的第一层并运行。
Thank you for the donation.
感谢您的捐赠。
Big donations, hill and thicker.
大捐款，山更厚。
Oh, thank you for the sub and Marcy I think for 10,000 more bits as well.
哦，谢谢你的 sub 和 Marcy，我想还有 10,000 位。
And Michael thank you for the five to one gifts ups
迈克尔感谢您提供五对一的礼物
night period.
夜间时段。
Thank you for five more gift
谢谢你还有五个礼物潜艇和幸运鸡，所以他左轮手枪给我们的礼物太多了
obvs guys is just so many gifts comes after gifts loves after gifts subs
obvs 伙计们就是这么多的礼物是在礼物之后的礼物爱之后的礼物
I don't know what to say and like for real thank you for all the love
我不知道该说什么，真的很感谢你所有的爱，我希望每个收到礼物的人
subs enjoys all of your all of your emails.
subs 喜欢你所有的电子邮件。
Like I said before we're going to get more email soon OK I might as well spoil
就像我之前说的，我们很快就会收到更多的电子邮件
because you guys are like really supportive today
因为你们今天真的很支持
I can tell you like what kind of gift subs that
我可以告诉你，我们没有给我们什么样的礼物潜艇，但我们很快就会收到什么样的电子邮件。
Uh, let me see
嗯，让我看看
ok, so we're gonna be getting
好的，所以我们会得到一个，一个抽泣的，一个适当的抽泣的，一个头拍。
I know we are. You have a head pat one, but like,
我知道我们是。 你有一个拍头，但喜欢，
I want to hear like a happy head pat right.
我想听到像一个快乐的头拍的权利。
Because the current head pat is like, you know, like an embarrassed one.
因为目前的拍头就像，你知道的，就像一个尴尬的人。
So we're going to be getting one that's a little bit more, you know, like
所以我们会得到一个多一点的，你知道的，比如
you know, happy to get ahead.
你知道，很高兴取得成功。
Pat, there's a here gal.
帕特，这里有一个女孩。
It's like
它像是
if, you know, miss, those are hey gal, it's going to be something like that.
如果，你知道，小姐，那些是嘿女孩，它会是这样的。
We're like bowels. Oh, hey, go.
我们就像肠子。 哦，嘿，走吧。
There's going to be an here
这里会有一个像，你知道，你的手指在一起。
It's like. Hey, hey. Oops.
它像是。 嘿，嘿。 哎呀。
I do that, you know, like you're a little shit is going to be a note taking one.
我这样做，你知道，就像你是个小屁孩一样会记笔记。
I think and a disgust one I think yeah.
我认为和厌恶的一个，我认为是的。
One of the new discussed one there's going to be a cotton for K one.
其中一个新讨论的将是 K 号的棉花。
There's going to be an angry one like a different kind of angry like
会有一个愤怒的人，就像另一种愤怒的人一样
not like the one with the fire, but it's going to be
不像带火的那个，但它会是
I don't know how to describe it.
我不知道如何描述它。
You'll see there's also will be a salute emote.
你会看到还有一个敬礼的表情。
Ah, like,
啊，就像，
like when you do the
就像你做的时候
07 thing in chat, it's going to be like, you know, he's giving you a salute.
07 聊天中的事情，就像，你知道的，他在向你敬礼。
Like it's going to be like an F because people can't see you off
就像它会像 F 一样，因为人们不能送你走，现在可以这样做了。
Instead, there's also going to be a cheer emote,
相反，还会有欢呼的表情，就像荧光棒一样，就像你们看到的那些带灯的电子邮件一样。
Thanks we're going to get those to be all waving around.
谢谢，我们会让那些都在挥手。
I think those would be really cute.
我想那些会很可爱的。
And it's all. Boy one Yeah.
这就是全部。 男孩一是的。
You know, there's a short bulldog.
你知道，有一只短斗牛犬。
Boy one because I feel like at this point
男孩一，因为我觉得在这一点上
not having one be kind of weird, so there'll be at least one dog.
没有一只狗有点奇怪，所以至少会有一只狗。
Boy, you might sell yeah.
男孩，你可能会卖是的。
There's a lot of emotes. I'm really excited for it.
有很多表情。 我真的很兴奋。
I'm super duper excited
我超级兴奋
and they're all going to be done by Chico you since I trust you.
因为我信任你，所以它们都将由 Chico 你来完成。
A lot of my R of my email work,
我的很多电子邮件工作，
she does a lot of emotes for a lot of other humans. Oh.
她为很多其他人做了很多表情。 哦。
God. And I have done some for, like, a lot of my friends.
上帝。 我已经为我的很多朋友做了一些事情。
So yeah,
是的，
I'm excited for them.
我为他们感到兴奋。
OK, but I'm going to end the stream off here.
好的，但我要在这里结束直播。
Thank you guys for coming by and thank you for watching my moulds
谢谢你们的光临，谢谢你们看我的模具
Adventures of Vox say holy shit dude.
Vox 历险记说天哪，伙计。
It was crazy. Like,
这太疯狂了。 像，
I really do enjoy clubbing with him and with all my other friends.
我真的很喜欢和他以及我所有的其他朋友一起泡吧。
I'll be sure to go support him as well.
我也一定会去支持他的。
OK, go give him some love and be sure to.
好吧，去给他一些爱，一定要。
Oh yeah.
哦耶。
If you haven't followed
如果您还没有在 Twitter
already on Twitter, be sure fallen sorter join the discord it's discord.
上关注，请确保堕落的分拣员加入不和谐的不和谐。
Dodgy social poll.
狡猾的社会民意调查。
That's our guild official discord server for people
那是我们的公会官方 Discord
to know, talk and interact and hang out there.
服务器，供人们了解、交谈、互动和闲逛。
And also subscribe on YouTube.
并在 YouTube 上订阅。
There's going to be a new video coming out later today too.
今天晚些时候也将发布一个新视频。
So keep your eyes out, OK?
所以请注意观察，好吗？
There's a new YouTube upload coming up later for this Sunday.
这个星期天晚些时候会有一个新的 YouTube 上传。
I missed the collab from this Tuesday so yeah, I'll be.
我错过了这个星期二的合作，所以是的，我会的。
Guys are excited for that one.
伙计们为此感到兴奋。
Really close.
真的很近。
The 400 K on Sawyer two ends are 300 on here
Sawyer 两端的 400 K 在这里是 300
and 400 on YouTube and that's
和 YouTube 上的 400，就是这样
a lot of milestones are coming up soon, so those are exciting.
许多里程碑即将到来，所以这些都是令人兴奋的。
I'll definitely do a celebration for that
我一定会为此庆祝
but I'm not going to keep you guys around for too much longer
但我不会让你们呆太久，因为我确实想去吃点东西，然后在下午剩下的时间里放松一下。
So take care guys and thank you for all the love
所以保重，谢谢你们所有的爱
Emotional, emotional damage.
感情上，感情上的伤害。
Yeah, good. A good night shop.
好耶。 一家晚安店。
I'll see you tomorrow for the dull no ends.
我明天见，无聊的没完没了。
Have a good night.
祝你晚安。
You take care
多保重
take care, guys.
保重，伙计们。
Love you.
爱你。
Bye bye. OK,
再见。 好的，
right.
对。
Well,
好，
I actually go and read now and take a look.
我现在真的去读了，看看。
Sees who is available
看看谁有空
yeah.
是的。
I'm going to play a quick ad break,
我将播放一个快速的广告插播，但我会在我们这样做时寻找一些可以阅读的内容。
OK, so Barbie
好的，所以芭比
you guys do this, by the way, like
顺便说一句，你们这样做，就像
make a pop noise of your mouth.
发出砰砰声。
Yeah, you do that.
是的，你这样做。
I really like doing that
我真的很喜欢这样做，当我只是，你知道，
hibernate no fermenting, just sitting there.
冬眠没有发酵，只是坐在那里。
It's like my it's like when I go like it's like when you say, ah,
就像我的 就像我去的时候 就像你说的时候
you don't want to say next, but it's more like a gesture, like I do a lot.
啊，你不想说下一句，但它更像是一种姿态，就像我做了很多一样。
It's kind of like it's not a bad habit.
这有点像这不是一个坏习惯。
It's just a behavioural things like
这只是一种行为上的东西
I'm, I describe it so.
我是，我是这样描述的。
It's really silly
真的很傻
also of, of.
也的，的。
Of that.
其中。
Before I head off I want to say
在我离开之前我想说
we're not going to, we're going to have our summer shrooms tomorrow.
我们不会，明天我们要吃夏天的蘑菇。
Right.
对。
I might start a little bit earlier
我可能会早一点开始，它会像往常一样长 2 小时。
I'll try to write a script like you are, you know, as planned and
我会尝试写一个像你一样的脚本，你知道，按计划和
I'll know how this is going to go.
我会知道这将如何进行。
It's going to be another chill, comforting summer day and I, I'm
这将是又一个寒冷，舒适的夏日，我有点紧张，因为我们的剧本写作不是我的强项，
but I'll try my best to ah, you know, have another.
但我会尽力的啊，你知道的，还有一个。
Good night.
晚安。
Comforting summer session and we'll see how that goes.
舒适的夏季会议，我们将看看情况如何。
So if you guys like the previous summer sessions, be sure.
所以如果你们喜欢以前的夏季课程，请确定。
Show for that, OK?
为此展示，好吗？
All right.
好的。
I'm going to go and look for so-and-so right now.
我现在要去寻找某某。
So take care, guys. Yeah, OK.
所以保重，伙计们。 是的，好的。
Let's see who's live right now.
让我们看看现在谁在直播。
Who is live and wants to get rated.
谁在直播并希望获得评分。
We have a
我们有一个
mm hmm.
嗯嗯。
OK. Oh, we can go and rage shy.
好的。 哦，我们可以去生气害羞。
Lily, I don't think we've ever rated Lily before.
莉莉，我认为我们以前从未评价过莉莉。
Now become a nice right.
现在成为一个不错的权利。
Yeah.
是的。
Let's go read Lily
我们去读莉莉
take care, everybody, and be sure to rest.
大家保重，一定要休息。
Well, I know it's like Night-Time for a lot of you, so go to sleep.
好吧，我知道这对你们很多人来说就像是夜间，所以去睡觉吧。
Soon, all right? Don't stay up too late.
很快，好吗？ 不要熬夜太晚。
And if you haven't already, please, again, go support my friends.
如果你还没有，请再次支持我的朋友。
Go support Vox's Journal and subscribe to him.
去支持 Vox 的日记并订阅他。
If you haven't done so, he is a wonderful person.
如果你还没有这样做，他是一个很棒的人。
And in order to show
并且为了展示
some love
一些爱
and a big thanks to him for loving again with me, it's always fun.
非常感谢他再次爱我，这总是很有趣。
No matter what.
无论。
It's always an enjoyable time when it comes to him.
对他来说，这总是一个愉快的时光。
No, I love you.
不，我爱你。
I love you guys till.
我爱你们直到。
Take care, OK?
照顾好？
As well.
同样。
And they'll see you tomorrow.
他们明天见。
Bye bye.
再见。
Bye bye. Love
再见。 爱
turn this music off because it's the YMCA.
关掉这个音乐，因为它是基督教青年会。
Bye bye.
再见。
All right, let's go.
好吧，我们走吧。
Where's my button?
我的按钮在哪里？
My button.
我的按钮。
Well, there it is. OK.
嗯，就是这样。 好的。